-=When I was a child, I traveled here from the future.=-
-=Long long time ago, aliens imprisoned their prisoners inside human beings=-
-=My father and Thunder were responsible for regulating these prisoners.=-
-=One day, Designer, leader of the prisoners escaped from the prison.=-
-=The whole city was full of the alien gas called 'Haba'.=-
-=People began to die one by one.=-
-=Those alien prisoners inside human beings began to wake up.=-
-=Designer wants to=-
-=release the rest Haba to change the earth atmosphere=-
-=so that all the human beings would die=-
-=and the earth would belong to them.=-
-=48 minutes to go before the outbreak of Haba.=-
Go to the next period.
-=We had to lock them in the past and return=-
-=to prevent the outbreak.=-
What's that?
Dad!
Lee Ahn, you need to find me
and prevent the outbreak of Haba.
-=During this time, Guard was damaged and Thunder stopped working.=-
-=To go back to the future, I need the Divine Sword.=-
-=10 years later, the Divine Sword appeared.=-
You're so beautiful.
But have we met before?
This cunning girl is shooting thunder!
-=People all came for the Sword.=-
-=A strange monk.=-
-=Two immortals from the Samgak Mountain.=-
-=And alien prisoners.=-
Besides...
-=I finally got the Sword.=-
Right King and Left King, go after her!
That inside your body...
What's inside me?
The girl that shoots thunder disappeared with the Sword.
What should we do now?
Find the Divine Sword of course.
We'll go after that girl.
-=Now, I'm on my way to find the ship and Thunder.=-
-=I'll go back to the future=-
-=and prevent the outbreak of Haba.=-
-=Alienoid S02=-
One soup rice for here
and one dried fish to go.
Okay.
Long time no see.
How far has rumors about me gone?
The thunder-shooting girl is heading to the Byongnan Garden House.
Anyone who kills her or gets the Divine Sword
shall get a large amount of bounty.
How come you wear a beard?
It belongs to a man I know.
Very natural right?
Natural indeed.
It takes four days to walk to Byongnan Garden House.
There is no hotel on the way for rest.
How many days have you gone without sleep?
Just two days.
Sleep doesn't matter.
What about the thing I asked you to find?
I'm definitely the right person for the task!
I searched the whole area along the river
where the fishman found the Divine Sword.
And finally I found someone
who once saw this thing.
You said that it's about this big, right?
Thunder, long time no see.
That means it's alive right?
Alive? You said it's a machine, didn't you?
It's a cute and wonderful being.
Who saw it?
Two woodcutters from the village beside Hwangneung Mountain.
They're brothers.
But the problem is...
Watch out for those two.
Let's go.
Where shall we meet after I find it?
The valley near Byongnan Garden House.
The one full of bird calls.
Okay, full of bird calls.
We are the legendary wizards of Sobaek Mountain.
You...
You're the thunder-shooting girl!
She wears a beard on such a pretty face!
She won't look pretty soon.
Because we'll press her face against the ground and ruin it.
What? What do you wanna do with the axe?
I'm thinking
whether I should chop your months or curb the urge.
But it's human nature to brag and be hypocritical.
I'll just curb the urge.
Our lives are very precious. I think you may as well
go before I cut your necks.
Do you really think that shabby axe can hit us?
Such a little trick!
How dare you!
I'll cut you into pieces!
Ouch!
Don't go after me.
Alright!
Next time you meet me,
watch out for the thunder!
Okay!
These two cats followed me here.
Don't follow me anymore.
That night 10 years ago,
we found him unconscious in the bush and brought him back.
What did the Hyungam say?
There was something terrible inside him.
So I suggested killing him
but you stopped me.
As long as he could resist the force, it's okay.
He gave him the fan with two swords.
Do you remember?
That day in Hyungam's room...
What on earth did he encounter near the river?
There is a terrible being inside his body.
That's why I suggested killing him.
Or he might cause a bigger turmoil after growing up.
Dear, it'll be fine as long as we don't teach him the magic arts.
The kid has the right to choose his own life.
I'll leave this fan to him.
There are two very heavy swords in it.
They'll suppress the force inside him.
What if he pulls the swords out?
These two swords can subdue demons and monsters, can't they?
No one can pull them out expect us.
Even if he pulls them out, we can kill him then.
But he pulled them out and learned magic arts.
So shall we kill him?
Is he really the student of the Hyungam?
No way. He looks just like a thief.
Let me touch him and we'll know.
What's this place?
Don't you remember?
You pulled the sword from the fan and killed the monster.
Ja-jang! Ja-jang!
Ja-jang!
Where is Ja-jang?
Who are you asking?
That old lady is both deaf and dumb.
Excuse me.
Ma'am, I have a question.
Where is Ja-jang from?
Write it down?
10 years ago.
Hwangneung Mountain.
Go and check if he's alive.
Okay.
What's this place?
Here is Milbon.
An isolated place where people learn the Way.
I got lost.
I was locked in time.
Everyone is locked in time.
I don't know what happened to you.
Will you wear this?
This mask is called Ja-jang.
Such an interesting human.
Monster!
My eyes!
From now on...
I'll run this place.
Why does Ja-jang want to find the Divine Sword?
Time.
I'm locked in time.
Where on earth is Designer?
When Designer entered other human's body,
there were four human beings present.
-=Hyungam Cheongwoon Heukseol Gaedong=-
They can control the energy.
So you must find Designer and go back.
Why do you have to dwell in that sick body?
Why not get into other healthy body?
That way, I'll lose my memory.
Designer hid inside a human body.
How could he get out?
Use the Divine Sword to stab the rest 3 people.
Stab using the Divine Sword and Designer appears.
Old lady.
You mean Ja-jang killed the Hyungam
and poisoned us to keep us here?
The Hyungam's student was also on Hwangneung Mountain
but it seemed that Ja-jang didn't know that.
Let's kill the student first.
Where is he?
Let's kill him before the monsters appear.
Let's go after him.
He can't be far from here.
Come and see.
Guess what this is?
Mix the ginseng from September Mountain with calculus bovis and herbs,
and you'll get this magic medicine that makes you live a young life forever.
It's called Cheongmyeong Pill!
Though this guy is blind now,
he couldn't even walk 3 years ago.
He is the legendary Neung-pa.
Let's see his swordsmanship first.
That was a close shave!
-Now everyone, you can... -Wait!
I can't sense
the aura from your sword.
Then how about showing us your swordsmanship.
Since you wanna see,
let me show you the sword with a history of 200 years.
You must have sensed its mightiness.
Since I've pulled it out,
one of us will have to die.
This is the best sword from the palace.
It's made by the two immortals of Samgak Mountain.
We're here to greet you with respect.
Do you still remember us?
Such rough sound. You must have had a tough life.
Sir, please sell this sword to us.
You must have bought it from the immortals of Samgak Mountain.
Even if I sell it to you, it won't make any difference.
My swordsmanship is good today.
Have you sold any pills?
Would people buy pills because of your swordsmanship?
They bought it because I was so eloquent.
How was my performance today?
Excellent, right?
It's getting more and more...
Who are they?
Our new members?
What happened?
What's this?
There is no such thing as a free lunch.
To get the Divine Sword
from the thunder-shooting girl,
we need that sword.
We need to find it faster than Milbon.
Milbon is looking for the Divine Sword?
Ja-jang?
My eyes.
It's said that the Divine Sword
can cure any diseases.
I wonder if it can cure my eyes.
It seems that the thunder-shooting
girl is in danger now.
We can help you.
So some cats were playing here,
climbing up along this pole?
The cats were nothing.
That thunder-shooting girl
made a mess here yesterday
which prevented me from doing business.
It seems that she's a tough lady.
They might follow her this way.
I want a bowl of soup rice
and rice wine.
Okay.
I have to find the Divine Sword
so that I can know what's inside me.
Where is Mureuk?
I think he's around here.
There! He's there.
Look at the way he eats.
There is a monster inside him.
So he eats so much.
Let's go and get him!
Let's make sure there is indeed a
monster inside him and then kill him.
We can tell him that we want him as
our student and try to find the clues.
Then I know what to do.
Let's say he's your student,
not mine.
Two bowls of soup rice, please.
Ah!
Such a coincidence!
We met again.
There is no such thing as coincidence.
It's all about fate.
Let us introduce ourselves.
We are the two immortals from Samgak Mountain.
We live in the mountain,
so we know little about the world.
Let me grab your arm first.
What's your name?
Mureuk.
How do you feel?
Very soft.
No, no. Not soft. Shy.
No, no, no. Not shy!
I'm 150 years old. I don't feel shy.
The fan becomes bigger when I
open it and smaller when I fold it.
But this doesn't matter.
What?
Such an idiot! I have to show it to you, right?
We made this fan.
We put some weapons inside it.
We also put the wind from the north.
What's this? A cat?
I don't remember drawing it.
I drew it.
Don't fan it.
Or the cats will become human beings.
What happened?
Who are you?
They are here. Wait! Wait!
Get inside. Get inside!
They've been after you since yesterday.
Where are you leading me to?
Follow me!
Don't stop there. Hurry and come up.
Who are you guys?
He's Right King and I'm Left King.
We're human beings.
Human?
And we're cats at the same time.
Cats?
Where are the cats?
They are after that girl.
And I'm chasing the cats.
I'm kinda busy. Gotta go.
But
your acupoint is blocked here.
That means there is something inside your body.
So the monster is inside you indeed.
I can't do this.
He's taking my power.
Out of my way! Why can't I control myself?
What's happening?
Everyone hide!
You should stop it! Not let it through!
Someone come and stop me!
That! That! That!
Ahahahahahahah!
Where?
Ouch ouch ouch!
Finally, it stopped.
Mureuk will go nowhere.
Go on.
Mureuk.
Follow me.
Hocus pocus. Hocus pocus.
Hocus pocus.
Let me tell you one thing.
Your teacher abandoned you.
Why?
Because he knows there
was a monster inside you.
Wait for me. Wait for me.
Why are you following me?
Our master told us to.
Master?
Oh my gosh!
Don't you know our master?
Aren't you two married?
What happened to you?
He'll come to us soon.
Wait. Is he coming here soon?
Yeah.
Then tell him. I'll meet him
when the weather is fine.
No, you're his wife.
What wife? That's nonsense.
You got married and spent
the wedding night together. You're his wife!
What wedding night?
Oh my!
Why would I say that?
See? Things didn't work out
on the wedding night.
Then have that night again
when you have a clear mind.
What are you!
Right King? You're not a human but a cat.
You live in the fan of that man, right?
Yeah.
I think you look familiar.
What are you talking about?
What are you up to?
It's my first time meeting you.
That broke our hearts. We're cats.
-Yeah. -Yeah.
Goodbye.
Tell that guy. I appreciate it.
I'll treat our encounter as a good memory.
Bye, kittens.
Don't follow me.
Don't speak like that,
my dear sister-in-law!
I'm not his wife!
This is not good!
We're heading that way too.
Let's hope she won't get angry.
We're just doing what we should do.
But when will he come?
Let's kill him
and see if the monster will come out.
I'm against using violence.
I'm against it too!
Why would you change your mind?
There must be something.
One flagon of wine, please.
Two flagons.
I can't do this when I'm not drunk.
Let's drink first.
Hey, here.
Wait.
Give me the knife.
That knife.
What's this?
Are these dishes for that room?
Yeah.
Give them in the room.
But he said that no one was allowed in.
It's okay. It's getting friendly inside.
What's that?
What?
That?
Ouch! An arrow. Where is it from?
Ouch!
That's too much!
Don't let anyone in.
Okay.
That gun is useless.
What about this one?
That way.
Who are you?
Are you from Milbon?
The sound of arrow is familiar.
Is Ja-jang here too?
Neung-pa?
The guy that was driven out?
He is indeed Neung-pa!
Hush.
The Divine Sword
can cure diseases, right?
Who are you?
Is this part golden?
And this part is supposed to be green,
glittering with clear light.
Aren't you blind?
Who are you?
I saw it before.
A man wearing strange armor
disappeared with it in the light.
You saw that scene?
Who are you?
Why do you have it with you?
It belongs to her! She saw people with it.
Who's that!
I'm her husband!
Thunder-shooting girl!
Where is she?
Look at you.
Are you stealing my magic arts?
It's not stealing. I'm just learning.
Thunder-shooting girl! Come out!
My dear, don't mind me. Just go!
Hurry.
Is she gone?
Really?
Who's gone?
Doesn't thing sheet belong to the two immortals?
I took it in secret.
They disappeared behind the sheet!
Why do you have the sheet that
belongs to the two immortals?
Just in front of me.
Why are you always dropping things?
It's you who pushed me.
Don't mind us. We're just passing by.
Quiet!
Quiet! Quiet!
You're waking the whole village up!
Please go on, sorry.
Did you commit any crimes?
Why would you ask something like that so loudly?
Your eyes are poisonous.
What poisonous?
I need to find the Divine Sword.
I want to open my eyes.
-=The year 2022, Seoul=-
Why is my ancestor staring at me today?
I can't even drink the tea.
Don't worry.
Nothing for you to worry about.
Nothing happens yet.
I'm okay anyway.
The world is in peace.
Even if I wanna use the thing inside the golf bag,
there is nowhere for me to use it.
See you tomorrow, sir.
-=2 days before the outbreak of Haba=-
Hey, get him!
Get him!
Who are you?
Me?
A passer-by who's just finished
exercise and is heading home.
Where are you going, thief?
What the hell?
You hit me first.
How did you catch him?
I was just passing by and
saw you guys working hard.
Which unit do you belong to?
Me?
That one.
That crossroads.
Give me your phone.
Crossroads?
Crossroads? North department?
North department crossroads?
Customs Service crossroads.
Ah.
I'm the inspector in charge of smuggling.
Call me if you need a witness.
Okay.
Is he a smuggler?
You can tell that by the shape?
They make them round to
put them inside the body.
Ah.
So I need your contact information now.
What's your name?
Don't ask me name. You should send
the document to the police station.
Sheriff Kang Chun-seok.
Yeah.
I'll call you. Do pick up the phone please.
Okay.
-=Jisan Hospital=-
What?
What's this place?
It's Jisan Hospital here.
We shall not talk unless
it's for the sake of diagnosis.
Do you feel pain when I press here?
What are you doing?
Is my neck broken?
Tell me the truth, will I become crippled?
It's not broken. You're lucky.
I could stay here longer if it was broken.
When will you send me to the police station?
Goo Sam-sik.
Haven't I told you not to speak?
-=Seo Yeon-ging=-
The could looks beautiful.
-=1 day before the outbreak of Haba=-
The prisoner Ho Seong-cheon has arrived.
What's this?
Damn!
Damn! Go away!
What?
His name is Goo Sam-sik.
He's been in prison for 9 times.
I'll go to the hospital first.
Gotta go.
Hey, Mr Kang Chun-seok.
You don't have to welcome me here.
You can only visit him.
Don't ask any questions.
What?
I know that kid.
Let's go and visit the patient.
Wait. Why's the door open?
-We came through the front door right? -Yeah.
Go to the back door and parking lot. Hurry!
Why isn't Lee Ahn here?
What did you say?
She overheard our conversation.
Track Lee Ahn down.
She filmed what happened here with her phone.
She went to her friend's place.
What's her friend called?
She has only one friend,
born on 17th July 2011.
I'm still searching for the address.
The name is Kim Min-seon.
Kim Min-seon?
My niece?
Oh my god! Did you really film this?
Is this your father?
You filmed this yourself?
Hush!
Aunt?
Yeah.
Lee Ahn's here.
Yeahn aunt. She'll sleep here.
She ran away from home.
Good day.
Yeah, I'm very good.
If you ran away from home, your father...
But your father's car.
Is it really like that
which is made by NASA and can speak?
I heard your father talk to the car.
Ah, but how could a car talk?
Right.
Yeah.
Why would you come to my room?
What?
Yeah, have a rest then.
Cultivate your friendship.
So cute.
What's this?
Sam-sik?
-=The day of the outbreak=-
The red spot is the motorbike that
was stolen from the hospital by Sam-sik.
These motorbikes for takeaway
are equipped with GPG now.
It's only 3 kilometers away.
What's that?
It seems to be some accident.
Good.
These medicines are of high quality.
What's happening?
What's wrong with these cars?
It doesn't seem to be a common accident.
Run!
What's that?
Sam-sik is there.
We still don't know where this
red gas come from and what it's made of.
The contaminated area has stopped expanding now.
The police is forming a cordon.
You're now watching the two
survivors in the contaminated area taken by the drone.
-=It's estimated that hundreds of citizens were dead in the red gas=-
How on earth did these two people
survive in an area where countless people died?
-=It's estimated that hundreds of citizens were dead in the red gas=-
This is still a mystery.
I saw that man in the video
taken by Lee Ahn.
The two survivors has driven the ambulance
-=Flash News 2 survivors are nowhere to be seen=-
and they've headed to somewhere we don't know.
The police haven't found any survivors by now.
-=Flash News 2 survivors are nowhere to be seen=-
Stay here, Min-seon.
The police haven't found any survivors by now.
I'll be back soon.
Now is the moment
my ancestor talked about.
Who are you?
I work for the government too.
Hi there.
Play the video please.
Who's in charge here?
Who are you?
Please watch this video first.
This is Jisan Hospital.
This person is the first survivor
in the contaminated area.
The second survivor.
They were both in Jisan Hospital.
This is not a coincidence.
There is one more person.
Sam-sik was in Jisan Hospital too.
He might be the third survivor.
Who's Sam-sik?
He's the smuggler we're following.
He's in the contaminated area now.
Who are you guys then?
I'm Min Gae-in, inspector of the Customs Service.
What's more important is who took the video.
My niece has a friend named Lee Ahn.
Her father is a little bit strange...
Alright, alright.
Customs Service right?
Do you know how many people is
claiming that they took videos of them?
All of these are fake.
Don't you know how to manage the scene?
Give me a minute please.
Hello?
-=Min-seon's Aunt=-
I'm Lee Ahn's father.
Hi, hello!
-=Min-seon's Aunt=-
Can Lee Ahn stay at your place for several days?
Yeah, Min-seon would be happy about that.
What about me picking her up now?
I've just finished my work.
No need for that, I'll send her now.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
YTN, please move your car out.
Give me the car key.
The key's here.
Who's that?
The father of the kid who took the video.
Lee Ahn's father.
I'll get the weapon out first.
Let's go.
You play golf?
No, I don't play that.
Let's go.
That guy lives here?
The address is here.
Sorry, Min-seon.
Lee Ahn will come to our home later.
She'll stay with us for several days.
You two stay at home. Don't go out.
I'll go back once I finish my work.
That ambulance! Is that the stolen one?
This way.
Come on. Let's set off all the Haba inside.
What's that?
Another car's here.
Park Tae-seok.
Ouch! Ouch!
Min Gae-in!
Lee Ahn's dad?
Hide yourselves! Hide!
Everything in place. Ready to go.
Just go back and prevent everything
from happening before Haba breaks out.
Go to another time.
What's that?
-=8:55 a.m. 25th September 2022=-
So you came here from the future 10 years ago
because of that.
-=8:55 a.m. 25th September 2022=-
So you're chasing after me for this?
Why do you need this?
For money?
Why would I need this?
Let me see where the story begins.
This is not the first time I've saved you.
Your name is Lee Ahn, right?
Who are you?
How come you know my name?
Don't you remember the things
back in your childhood?
You fell into the water and I saved you.
You?
I know it's hard.
But try and imagine me as a child.
What's your name? I'm Mureuk.
Lee Ahn.
You're that little brat?
What brat?
So you're alive!
What's your name?
I remember you have a moody name.
It's Mureuk.
Not moody.
So will you return the favor?
It's lucky I found you.
I've been longing to meet you again.
You're the boy back then.
But
what's Designer?
How come you know that?
Where did you hear this?
When I saved you from the water
and climbed up the hill,
I saw something strange.
He walked towards me and said
that he found a human being.
I found you, human.
It's that monster that
got into my body, right?
From that day on,
I would lose my memory from time to time.
If you stab me with the Sword,
the monster will come out, right?
If it comes out from my body,
just you kill it.
No, don't do that.
Whatever is inside your body,
just let it be.
You just live like this.
Just live like this?
Then what am I?
If there is a monster inside me,
what am I?
So the monster will die only when I'm dead.
So you're meant to kill me.
Maybe I was meant to die when I was born.
Why am I alive?
My dad, Thunder,
all the uncles of the busking group
and you saved me
so that I could save others.
You are who you are,
no matter what's inside of you.
I'm none of those.
Good for you.
That's you.
Don't forget the way you are.
I won't forget you either.
What are you doing? Take my hand.
I'm taking the Divine Sword.
Did you find Gaedong in Hwangneung Mountain?
Yeah, I've been tracking them.
Bring him in.
Then move him to the Byongnan Garden House.
What to do with the woman who fired Thunder?
Just wait.
She'll come for this stuff anyway.
But no matter how I think about it,
how did you just meet the person from your childhood?
Oh, there's such a thing as a coincidence.
These are the red pines in front of the yard.
What's that supposed to mean?
Someone's the yard.
And some are red pine
There's a red pine right in front of the yard.
There are no coincidences.
It's all fate.
And so it is with us.
How could I have known such a profound meaning?
You're doing it again.
So where did the red pine go?
Is that what she's here for?
Something like a crooked stone altar.
The one Gaedong  asked us to find.
It's called Thunder or something.
Isn't it painted on his wall?
In addition to the painting, there's another strange thing.
Did he have to tell her
about that thing in his house?
Giddyup! Giddyup!
It's for an arrest.
Looks like they're after the shooting-thunder girl.
I hear the reward is very high.
We have to catch her before we can get the money.
What to do?
The shooting-thunder girl was said to be particularly handsome.
We have to feel how she is like before we kill her.
I heard she's married to
a guy who looks like an idiot.
I'm drunk.
Let's get her too.
-Let's go. - Ouch.
What are you staring at? You look like an idiot.
Who says I look like a fool?
In the Lotus Sutra there is this sentence
Those who meet will leave. Those who go will return.
It's been quite a night for ideas.
Does it mean people are bound to meet again after they've been apart?
No, it means money.
Left King.
It smells like she is in this way.
Let's go.
This way.
You really know how to smell.
I thought she was dead, but she was asleep.
Should we wake her up?
It's cold to leave it like this.
It's okay. It's us.
All the Taoist priests in the country are looking for you.
How many days have you not slept?
Three days
Why are you here again?
I thought we agreed not to see each other anymore.
Sure we agreed.
But, uh.
Promises are made to be broken.
And we're telling you, that thing you're looking for...
What I'm looking for...
That
Thunder
Do you know where it is?
-=Run, you fool!=-
Where is Thunder?
It's a good drawing.
That's what you said you'd show me, the painting?
No, this one.
Mureuk, get out.
Leave her alone for a while.
Thunder, You've been waiting for me for a long time, haven't you?
Thunder
Thunder, is that alive?
Yep.
It's energy.
There's no energy left, so it can't react.
Where does that put the energy?
It's that guy.
Look there, it's me.
It's those guys, wait.
You're the one I'm looking at.
Those two over there,
Come out. Don't hide.
Run! Run! Run!
Let's go together.
Stop.
Let's find the ship first, Thunder.
We have to go home.
Here you are.
Are you going back to the future now?
Yes.
So we're splitting up again?
You gotta watch out for the cats.
They may come after you again.
No, I have to warn them.
Those guys, they'll probably be after you the whole time.
They need to be taught a lesson.
I'm gonna have to do something about that.
Left King, Right King.
Where'd you go?
It's here. It's here.
How did you know I was here
and be right here?
Do you know each other?
Are they the ones you're looking for?
Do you know us?
I know. Left King and Right King.
Who are Left King and Right King?
The guys I saw ten years ago
appear again.
Really?
Ouch. What did that mean ten years ago?
Come on. Come on.
Who are you?
Don't come over here.
Leave us alone. Did we do something wrong?
We just happened to meet here ten years ago.
Meet here?
We?
Ten years ago?
Gaedong
Right King.
Gaedong, why are you here?
Do you see Left King?
Yes.
Well, I need to talk to you.
Hey, hey, you can't go.
You can't go over there.
I have something to tell you.
Are you Gaedong?
Yes, why?
You have to come with us.
Where?
Byongnan Garden House
Why?
Let it off!
Right King.
Left, Left King.
Right King. My body's weird.
No, no, it's okay.
Mureuk is here.
What's wrong with Left King?
There's a bunch of Taoist guys who are catching Gaedong and let Left King...
Stand up.
Let's go. Let's go.
What's going on?
Why am I vanishing?
Am I going to die?
Let's go back to the fan.
Left King.
Thunder.
Are you alive?
Left King.
Thunder.
Right King, is Left King dead?
Gaedong seems to know something.
Mureuk
Let's go to Byongnan Garden House.
-=Byongnan Garden House=-
We brought Gaedong here.
Go ahead, Ja-jang.
Ten years ago, a young student of Hyungam
was expelled because he was possessed by a monster
which is controlled by a fan.
Did someone take the iron car in the water?
I heard it was taken to the Byongnan Garden House last night. By masked priests.
We're at Byongnan Garden House.
-Let's go. - Yeah.
Mureuk must've been here
if he's chasing after Ja-jang.
Wait.
It's really weird.
Why isn't there anyone?
Anyone?
Aren't they here to arrest someone?
Why did they all die here?
And the masked Taoist priest.
This guy is Neung-pa. What are you doing here?
I'm the god of the mountain, and you're always calling me that 'guy'?
It's because you didn't pay for the Divine Sword.
Why did they all die over there?
I came and found them all dead.
There's a monster here.
Ja-jang?
Looks like you two are also here to catch Ja-jang.
Yeah, where is he?
Probably hiding.
Wait, I heard someone on the second floor.
It's a bait.
For who?
Shh.
Mureuk!
We found them tow!
Ja-jang? Where's Ja-jang?
-Shh. - You be quiet, boy.
Where's our package?
Mureuk
Gaedong
I have a sword wound.
Who did this? Is it Ja-jang?
It's in Hwangneung Mountain.
It's about to bite.
Ten years ago, a young student of Hyungam was expelled
whose name is Mureuk.
Gaedong isn't the one Ja-jang's looking for.
Get out of here. Come on.
The woodsmen said they'd seen you ten years ago.
Did anyone see me ten years ago?
They said you came out of there.
Where?
The one the girl was looking for.
Gaedong. Gaedong.
Okay, finally.
What do we do now, Thunder?
Thunder
The one the girl was looking for.
It's the monster.
Right King, keep it together.
Mureuk
Right King
Shooting-thunder...
What are you two doing here?
No
No! No!
No!
Got it.
You human.
Mureuk?
Mureuk
Why me?
What is in that man's body?
My power is dying out.
Have my energy.
Thunder. Take care of this boy.
What?
That's scary.
What's this?
An iron?
Beings discovered.
Two cats. Two humans.
Start copying.
Be sure to kill me with your own hands.
The Designer escaped from prison.
Lee Ahn.
Ok. Let's go to the future.
Haba will explode. The prisoners will escape.
Warning. The time energy is unstable.
What's that?
-=Sep 25th, 2022, 8:55 a.m.=-
Haba will explode in 47 minutes.
Finally.
Designer is back.
Prisoners here. Wake up.
Go to help Designer.
Investigator. Found a survivor. It's Sam-sik.
The medical team is going in.
I'll try to stop.
Wait. The team is dangerous.
We can't let them in.
-Get the armed SWAT team in. -What happened?
Customs Service?
Get her out here.
Commander Kang Chun-seok of the Eastern Agency
was attacked by that monster and sent to the hospital.
Medical team
-can soon carry out tasks. -Wait!
Evacuate the medical team. The mission is canceled.
What are you doing? Get out!
Arrest her.
Medical team. Secret Service team. Retreat.
Can you confirm the viewing distance?
Stay still. Something is  ahead.
What's that?
The survivor
is in the air.
Report what happened.
Where are we?
In the future?
Is Yi Seong-gye the king?
No?
Where are we? How do we go back?
We have to find a horse.
The Divine Sword is in this era.
Where is the Divine Sword?
North by Northwest. 12.4. Only the Sword can prevent the explosion.
Get it back.
Kill anyone who gets
in your way.
Kill anyone who gets in your way.
Sir. Sir.
Hey. What are you doing?
If you are not a member, go out.
Silence.
We may be in the wrong place.
No. We don't.
There are monsters.
Where?
There.
-=Real-time image  unidentified monster discovered=-
Here.
Step aside.
What's going on?
Monster!
Where is it?
It ran away.
Why can't this stop?
Stop it!
Patrol car. There is a violence in the 7-2 area.
-=Police car=-
Nearby cars. Please answer.
Copy that. We are here.
-=Police car=-
Wait.
Who called the police?
Here. Here.
Help me.
Ok.
Turn off the machine.
Please come down.
Come down.
Drop the gun.
They have this.
Do you know the shooting-thunder girl?
Drop the gun.
-=Police=-
Amazing feeling.
What is this?
-=Police=-
Who are you?
Who am I?
It will take your whole life
to find the answer.
Who are you?
Oh no.
Are you noble?
You seems like have noble blood.
How did you break this?
We are gods.
Someone is approaching.
Who?
Closer.
Where?
There.
Help me.
Cheongwoon.
The thunder.
Where is Lee Ahn?
Run!
Quick! Quick!
Why is he still chasing us?
He's chasing us?
You two? Why?
For the Divine Sword.
Where did you come from?
We ran from the woman called Lee Ahn.
Lee Ahn.
Wait.
Are you talking about her?
What?
They look alike.
I feel weird.
She comes.
Lee Ahn is coming.
Run. Run.
Run.
The train is about to set off.
Start the engine.
Start it.
Where is here?
Min-seon.
Aunt. I just arrived at Lee Ahn's home.
Why do you go there?
She didn't come. So I'm here to pick her up.
But I found something strange.
The uncle who had been on the news is here.
I saw him. I saw him.
Aunt. Wait.
Leave there.
No.
I'll go there. Hide yourself.
Mureuk.
Who are you?
I'm the Program.
Mr. Po? Mr. Po. Are you Mr. Po?
We've known each other for ten years. Don't you know me?
Left King and Right King.
What do you mean?
Woman.
Where is that woman?
What's this?
Let's start the attack system.
Start what?
No. No. No.
Mureuk. Get up.
Good.
Get up. We should go.
Finally.
Don't move.
We will go, too.
It's gone.
The energy is unstable.
Which means,
the energy is here.
Yes.
The energy is here.
Good.
Ok.
Let's go back again with this.
I can see the world.
Ok.
We are ready to take a ride.
Mureuk. It's time to leave.
To where?
Don't you want to save that woman?
Woman.
Didn't she ask me to kill her?
Don't believe her.
Where are we going?
Future.
The year of 2022.
Let's go.
Future.
Can't believe I see it again.
Is this the future that the woman was talking about?
Is it?
Congratulations.
You are in the future.
Taxi.
What is taxi?
When you shout taxi, it can take you to anywhere you want.
Let's go.
Wait.
Why is it always following us?
The energy is unstable.
It connects Byongnan Garden House and here. Really unstable.
But don't worry.
I will send you back when all is over.
Fourteen minutes before the explosion.
Let's go.
-=Korea Daily=-
Are you okay?
I'm Min Gae-in, a policeman. I need to borrow your car.
Delicious.
Let's go.
Run.
Throw a charm.
Charm.
There are only two charms.
We are done.
Wait. The train is heading to my home.
Mureuk. Are you ready?
Of course.
What to prepare?
Your arms.
Right.
We have to give it to her.
Give her? How?
Your hand.
What?
Prisoner 8975.
Mureuk.
What?
Mureuk. What are you doing? Why don't you come up?
Sir. I will.
See you later.
I got it. I got it.
Any more weapon?
They were all left.
-Catch it. -Heukseol.
Run.
Remember?
Use the Divine Sword to save people.
Memory.
Didn't you say
that you are who you are, no matter what's inside of you?
It's okay.
Don't.
What are you doing?
This is not mine.
I keep it just for a while.
Take out the prisoner.
Help the Designer to get out of prison.
No.
Five minutes before the explosion.
Fine.
Receive the energy and prevent the explosion.
Lee Ahn. Get up.
Where is the weapon?
Who is it?
Neung-pa.
Why is Neung-pa here?
Why is his sword in the future?
It stands up.
Min-seon. Aunt is here. Hide yourself.
Who are you?
Min Gae-in, a descendant of Neung-pa, greets you.
Are you two the masters of this weapon?
Tell my great descendants.
The two gods and Mureuk left the weapon and went to the future.
My descendants of 2022
should find them and give them the weapon
when the monsters appear.
What should I do then?
Let's work together to catch the monster.
What are you doing? Taoist Mureuk.
What Taoist?
I'm not an expert in any field.
Get up. My disciple.
I don't have that thing in my body.
I am totally useless now.
The fan.
I remember I left it there.
Prajnaparamita.
Why am I reciting the mantra?
It is already in my mind.
Are you fine? My disciple.
Get up.
He's my disciple.
Mureuk
greets to you all.
Nine percent chance of winning.
Ten.
Sixteen.
Dad.
Why is it elevated?
I'm going to die.
I can see the future.
Lee Ahn will solve all.
With other humans.
Humans cannot solve it.
They don't have that ability.
It's impossible when there's only one human.
But now we are together.
Can you see it?
I can see it in my eyes.
I'll send it to you.
Thunder.
Insert that into the heart of the ship.
Come on.
Go.
Appearance.
You are dead. Come.
Go.
I'll kill you now.
Come on.
Crush. Crush. Crush. Crush.
Here.
It's hurt. It's hurt.
Lee Ahn. It's dangerous.
Lee Ahn. Run!
-=Twenty minutes before the explosion=-
Haba will explode in twenty minutes.
-=Eliminate the disruptor=-
Eliminate the disruptor.
Descendant of Neung-pa.
Drop your sword in here.
Raise me up.
No.
Thunder.
Did it work?
Aunt.
Ahh. What?
Min-seon.
Aunt.
Oh my god.
Don't let it in the body.
Min-seon. Are you okay?
Who are you?
Do you know me?
Yes.
Survive.
It isn't the end
of getting out of the prison.
What should we do? Thunder.
Take it and leave.
It will come out. It can't be destroyed.
It won't be stopped.
What if it comes back again?
We should explode it up there.
Then you will die.
I told you.
I'll take this to the universe.
It's time.
That's what Dad said.
I have Guard's program.
And also all your memory.
Is it right? Mureuk.
No. It should be the master.
Left King.
Right King.
I miss you so much.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
Right King.
You are alive.
Of course.
See? I said I am the right arm of my master.
You are in his front. The right side is me.
Hey. Mureuk.
Don't tell anybody that I saved the world.
I am shy.
We are going back. Master.
Where?
Don't be sad.
It's like red pine in front of the yard.
Thank you for your company.
Thank you, too.
Go back.
That is about to disappear.
It's time to go back to your era.
Yes.
You are the cats.
Goodbye. Lee Ahn.
Goodbye.
See you next time.
He's smiling at me.
No. He's smiling at me.
A candy-colored clown they call the sandman
Tiptoes to my room every night
Just to sprinkle stardust and to whisper
Go to sleep
Everything is all right
I close my eyes
Then I drift away
Into the magic night
I softly say
A silent prayer
Like dreamers do
Then I fall asleep to dream
My dreams of you
In dreams I walk with you
In dreams I talk to you
In dreams you're mine
All of the time we're together
In dreams, In dreams
But just before the dawn
Everything to be done is done.
Yes.
But just before the dawn
You've got a lot of injuries because of me.
I awake and find you gone
No. I'm alright.
I can't help it
if I cry
I remember that you said goodbye
Thank you. My husband.
It's too bad that all these things
Can only happen in my dreams
Only in dreams
In beautiful dreams
-Wow. -Oh my god.
Oh my god.
My body is going to fall apart.
You are on time. You are punctual.
Suddenly I was very proud of myself.
Why?
We saved the world.
-Of course Mureuk has helped. -Right.
Is Neung-pa still here?
Do you see Neung-pa?
-You come back? -Yes. Neung-pa.
We saved the world.
And we met your descendants.
But can you see us?
Get up and tell me everything.
Okay. Okay.
There's so much to talk about.
What?
Wait.
What did Mr. Po said at that time?
I know it.
There is still energy.
Wait.
Why is it always following us?
The energy is unstable.
It connects Byongnan Garden House and here.
Byongnan Garden House.
Unstable connection.
It reopened.
Let's drink wine.
Why is Mureuk still here? What are you doing?
Red pine in front of the yard.
What?
I will go there again.
There's something I didn't tell her.
-=Available=-
Taxi.
-=Director Choi Dong-hoon=-
-=Writer Choi Dong-hoon Lee Ki-chul=-
-=Alienoid S02=-SEGHOJANGAN