[sighs]
Morning.
I don't need a permit.
You with fish and wildlife, or something?
Because otherwise you...
USGS land survey.
You guys still aren't finished with that crap, huh?
It's been three months.
Started as a tiny sinkhole. Now look at this place.
Government's just gonna blame it on global warming call it a day.
Well, you know us liberals.
We just aren't happy unless we're blaming something.
My cousin was in one of those houses.
That whole area is in a flood zone.
That's the answer.
More government, more permits, more zones.
He lived in a flood zone, jackass, not a sink zone.
Okay.
You see over there under the water is limestone
and over there,
all that sand was underground,
pushed up by water to the surface.
Called a sandblow.
And when water pushes sand out of the way
and dissolves the limestone,
it creates holes.
Over time the weight of the houses causes the collapse.
Now your cousin would have known that
if he had read any of the info that was sent to him about this.
He and I know well enough to know
that his house didn't cause that...
- Wait.
- Don't tell me to wait.
- I have every right...
- No, no, quiet!
[rumbling]
- What is that?
- Get off the dock!
- Whoa!
- It's an earthquake!
Come on, come on!
Help me, help me!
Help me!
What the heck was that?
A surface rupture.
Oh my God.
- [laughing]
- It's amazing.
You saved my life.
Can I buy you a beer?
Yeah, sounds good.
I mean, but... It's amazing. Look.
How deep do you think that is?
Now, be careful.
- Don't go too close, sir.
- Gotta be at least...
[rumbling]
[screams]
[honking]
Eric, come on, we're going to be late!
- Come on!
- All right.
You know that being late on your first day
is pretty crappy, right?
Mm-hmm.
What are you doing?
Dude, don't you care that we're going to be late?
Like, all you do is play on your phone
and you literally move like a snail.
Do you care about this job at all?
No, I don't care about this job at all.
What?
Eric, there's nothing wrong with a hard day's work.
It's how you find a passion, like a career.
Whatever you say.
Wow, so you don't have any passions, huh?
I mean, maybe I'd want to be a pilot.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What, like, Air Force? Commercial?
Yeah, I don't know, but...
my dad taught me how to fly a helicopter.
It's so sweet.
I bet.
[alarm sounding]
Please, please turn that off.
The earth doesn't take a break, so I don't either.
Okay.
Wait.
Is that an earthquake?
A what?
[rumbling]
Brenda, stop the car!
[screams]
[shouting]
- [panting]
- We're okay.
- Brenda?
- Okay...
- Brenda!
- All right, all right.
We're okay, we're okay.
We just need to think about getting out of here...
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- ...logically, and not panic.
It's got to be at least 20 feet down.
Deeper than that.
- Don't move, don't move.
- I'm not.
All right.
Mom, don't walk away from me while I'm talking.
What did I say about slamming doors?
Oh, so the door has rights, but I don't.
We just had a major seismic event.
I don't have time for this.
Mom, it's not fair, you said when I turned 18,
I could do what I wanted.
Well, I'm 18 and I want to move to Dad's in Marston.
I don't think he's going to help me fight global warming.
In fact, fracking is the exact opposite.
Look, Mom...
Okay, sorry to interrupt this beautiful mother-daughter moment
happening here, but we just got the official data on the quake.
The US Geological Survey just revised it to a 5.7.
Missouri's agency is registering it as something different,
and I read the tracker wrong.
USGS just said 5.9.
Should we do a cross-check
with the State Emergency Management Agency?
Nope, USGS is better equipped than SEMA.
Did you check our seismographs for a more detailed reading?
No, sorry.
No apologies.
5.9 means there's going to be some damage,
possible fissures around the city.
Epicenter is two miles south of New Madrid.
A couple aftershocks, but nothing major.
3.1 and a 2.9.
Two miles south of the town of New Madrid,
or south of the epicenter of the New Madrid fault line?
South of the town.
Mom, we're not done with this conversation.
Your brother could be in real trouble.
We can talk about this later, Emily.
Ooh. Crazy morning already, huh?
- Thought you could use this.
- Thanks, babe.
Yeah, we're in for a long one if these aftershocks keep up.
Fine with me.
It means we're going to spend more time together.
Your brother isn't picking up.
Of course he isn't.
He just found out about Finn proposing.
It's fine.
Why don't you try to call Brenda?
I'll keep checking Eric.
Mom, please, can we finish this conversation?
Why is he not picking up?
Why would you want to move in with your dad, huh?
He's going to get me a job that pays.
Let's take this inside. I have work to do.
[sighs]
Eric refused to do anything else but work for him,
which is why I allowed it.
It's an opportunity to do something important.
I mean, yeah, it may be working for the wrong side,
but I can make changes there.
And I can help and send some money for the house.
Don't even go there.
Finn and I are doing just fine.
I didn't mean...
I don't want to make you upset again.
I just... I want to help.
Benda didn't the answer, but I went ahead and used her phone
- to pinpoint the location.
- Thank you. Where are they?
[rumbling]
Feel that?
Seismograph shows 6.1 and potentially growing.
Hold tight!
They're getting bigger.
The magnitude topped at 6.4.
That's what I'm seeing, too.
- Everyone okay?
- Yeah.
Let's make sure we didn't lose any connections out there.
Carla, epicenter?
New Madrid. South of Marston.
Everybody okay?
Yeah.
Hope the sensors are all right.
Let's get this cleaned up.
Brenda? Brenda?
Mom! Mom! It's Brenda.
They've been in an accident.
It's Cami. What happened?
Is Eric okay?
Just sit tight, okay? We're leaving now.
Carla, Finn, stay here.
Analyze the latest readings and get them to me ASAP.
What's wrong?
They need help.
Emily and I are going to New Madrid.
- I should go with you.
- No.
I need you to monitor the tectonic AI.
That software needs to be operating at 100%.
The New Madrid fault is the largest on this continent.
If we're seeing this much activity,
it means something way bigger could be on the way.
And we need to know about it.
Like a 7 or an 8?
It's too soon to tell.
Well, there's sinkholes, shifts in the geologic table,
massive sandblows emerging.
None of this is normal.
[phone rings]
It's Alan.
Text him. Tell him to meet us in New Madrid near the ravine.
I'll call him on the road and tell him what's happening.
Let me know as soon as Eric's safe.
- I will.
- I love you.
Love you, too.
- Are they going to be okay?
- We need to hurry.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, listen to me. I'm Alan Weddle.
I own half the fracking sites in this area.
My son's stuck inside. I'm going in there to get him.
Sir, this is an evacuation site.
I need you to get back in your truck and go ahead and leave.
No, no, no. I don't care if I got to call the governor.
- I'm going in.
- Where is he? Where's Eric?
- Hey, we got to go.
- I'm going to get my son.
- Yeah, we're going to get him.
- I'll keep an eye on 'em.
- Eric?
- Eric.
You in here, buddy?
Guys, it's not safe to be in here.
Eric, Brenda, you guys in here. Can you hear me?
Eric!
[rumbling]
- Eric!
Mom!
- Hold on...
- Mom! Dad! Help!
- Hear that?
- We're down here!
- That's him.
- Help!
- Eric! Eric!
- Mom!
- Hey.
- Eric, honey.
Dad! We're in here.
- Hey.
- Try to open the door.
- Hang on, we'll come get you.
- Wait, the truck's slipping!
It's moving.
I can't open it. I can't open it.
- I'll get some rope!
- Okay.
I can't open it!
I got it. I'm out!
Hey. Hang on. Easy. Easy. I'm coming. I'm coming.
Give me the rope, give me the rope! Okay.
Oh! [gasps]
Plates are shifting!
How do you know that?
I'm a geologist. It's why I'm here.
The whole area is a hotspot.
Stay put, don't move!
Come on, hurry up!
Dad!
Eric, sit tight, okay?
We need some slack. A little slack.
Mom, get me out!
All right. Here we go.
Put this around your waist.
Wrap it tight around your waist.
Guys, we've got about two minutes!
- Come on!
- Stay back.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
Careful. Careful.
I got you. I got you. Ready?
- Give me your hand.
- Okay.
I got you.
Pull. Pull. Pull.
- Pull!
- Nice and easy, pull.
Pull. Come on!
- Ah!
- Easy, easy, easy.
You got it. You got it.
Just slide, slide, slide.
Okay, all right. Okay.
- Dad! Dad!
- Good, good, good, good, good.
Dad!
You got her? Eric, hang on.
Here I come, buddy. Here I come.
Coming down.
[shouting, rumbling]
Okay...
- The truck is slipping!
- It's gonna fall.
Dad, get me out of here.
Hang on, buddy, hang on. Here it goes.
Get this around your waist.
Get it around your waist. I need slack.
You got it, give me your hand.
Okay, go, pull! Pull!
- [shouting]
- Easy, easy.
Hold on!
All right, all right, come on.
Okay, take the rope off!
Wait, wait.
We all gotta go. Go, go, go, go!
Get him up!
[shouting]
- You guys okay?
- Yes.
Yes, see, if you look right here,
that's one of the spots.
Stay still.
What are you even doing here?
I mean, what happened to saving the planet, Em?
- You're not trying.
- Stop! This is not the time.
This fault line hasn't seen this much activity in over 100 years.
The Geologic Society reported a mass sediment shift
due to the rising temperatures in the riverbed.
I'm sorry, hold on a second.
Who is this guy and why do you know so much about this?
I'm Dan Eames.
Dan Eames?
You led a study along the San Andreas fault?
So nice to finally meet you.
Wait, are you Dr. Cami Weddle?
Yeah.
The pleasure is all mine. I know all about your work.
They asked me to come check on this because of all the concern.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Carla, these thermal readings on the fault
are at an all-time high.
Well, the fault's locked and loaded.
No, it's not that.
The most recent subterranean scan shows
the strike-slip portion as being a double lock.
If the tension breaks,
it'll create a magnitude eight or greater.
And then that'll transfer all that tension...
We need to call Cami right now.
The sinkholes we're seeing are through
a dense layer of igneous rock.
Igneous?
See, you're saying that some igneous layers
are turned upward?
Yes.
I haven't figured out why.
[phone rings]
Hey, Finn. Eric's fine. So is Brenda.
We're almost there. This couldn't wait.
What is the latest reading showing?
Based on your algorithm, if the fault slips today,
it's guaranteed to produce an 8.0 or higher.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I've double and triple checked it.
We've got to get Governor Barber on board.
Cami, it's not just that.
When the quake hits, it's going to transfer that pressure
to a second strike point.
Are you seeing this?
The satellite imagery is showing buckling
that happened in the past 24 hours.
The entire fault line is radically altering the terrain.
Finn, we're seeing massive swells.
It'll reach the Gulf of Mexico.
When it transfers to the second stage,
it'll only be nine hours until...
Until it produces a 10.0 or larger.
That's right.
Okay. Let's meet up later and we'll figure it out.
Sounds good.
Alan, I don't think I'll be getting
to the survey of your site today.
That's great.
That's all based on a guess, right?
Don't worry about it. I got it.
- I'll do it all myself, okay?
- A guess? Really?
Finn just ran the algorithm.
It indicates if we don't pinpoint
where and how these plates are slipping,
we're looking at a 10.0 or larger in less than nine hours.
Wait a minute, a 10.0?
Are you serious?
That'll break the whole country in half.
I just pulled up the Missouri Seismic Emergency Database
- to compare it to ours.
- Wait, wait.
Scroll down.
Why are the aftershocks bigger than the originating quake?
The 6.8 is most likely a foreshock.
Why would you assume that it's going to get worse?
Because even though we've had multiple large quakes,
the total heat energy hasn't completely dissipated.
We need to let Governor Barber know.
Yeah, I need to call her ASAP.
We need a multi-agency response.
Can you get us in touch?
Your pals, otherwise she wouldn't
have approved of your fracking sites.
What's the end game here, Cami?
A natural emergency declaration?
Are we going to do that again?
Yes, exactly.
Then the military can work with us
on a strategy to mitigate the actual quake.
Otherwise, every city in the Midwest will be leveled.
Millions will die.
I've got to get the governor on the line.
The series of quakes is severe for the area,
but not impossible.
Nothing the National Guard and FEMA can't manage.
Should I write up a preliminary report,
get it ready for release, just in case?
Fine, but no leaks. And for God's sakes, no press.
The last thing we need is another panic situation
on our hands.
[phone vibrates]
That's Dr. Cami Weddle.
You should join me.
Dr. Weddle, Governor Barber. Brett Rothers from SEMA is here.
You're on speaker.
The geothermal activity in New Madrid
has only increased after the quakes.
By not releasing kinetic energy, it's only
storing that much more potential energy.
Don't you think that's a bit premature?
You're suggesting an imminent mega-casualty event.
It's not a suggestion.
It'll be a 10.0 or greater in less than nine hours.
Brett, have you seen the data from the orbital network yet?
Yes, but the images don't have enough detail
or data to make such a prediction.
A man was swallowed up by the Mississippi.
I nearly lost my son and a colleague by a fissure
that wasn't here this morning and this was just the beginning.
We need to prep emergency services and the military
and start citizen evacuations.
Two years ago, you thought the big one was coming.
It did not, causing a mass panic
that took us days to recover from.
I'm assembling a team headed by Mr. Rothers.
I'd like you to join in.
All I'm asking is that you prepare an evac plan
for at least New Madrid County.
The safety of families is very important to us.
You don't know that New Madrid indicates a larger event.
My predictive models don't lie.
It will strike New Madrid in nine hours.
Is Alan there?
What does he have to do with this?
You understand our apprehension.
If we know that Alan is on your side...
Call me when you're ready to listen.
There.
You see how stupid the government is, right?
You think they're right.
I think that you can't do it without their help.
I need you with me.
Your fracking business represents
jobs and re-elections.
They'll listen to you.
Cami, you realize that you're asking me to cry wolf.
For me, not for us this time.
You know my position on this.
Dad, come on.
Mom's literally been working on this her whole life.
Predicting earthquakes and maybe stopping them.
I know, but...
I know, I've heard it before.
You can't stop an earthquake, right, Cami?
But our focus right now is urging the government
to get people to safety.
Finn's here with the mobile lab.
We don't have time to argue.
Are you in or are you out?
Come on, at least come to the lab,
see what she's been working on.
Please?
All right, all right, I'll come check it out, okay?
Dan, if you'd like to come along,
I'd love your input as well.
Sure, whatever I can do.
All right, let's go.
All right, see you guys in a little bit.
[rumbling]
I suggest a compromise that won't interfere
with Dr. Weddle's work.
She might be willing to cooperate.
That fracking field brought in millions
over the past 18 months. Understand?
Yes, of course.
Let me reach out.
No, we can still attempt compromise
while making our position clear.
Go meet her.
We'll fly your equipment in.
Okay.
- You guys got this, right?
- Yeah, we're good.
Connect these to this and you're good.
What?
I don't know.
You ever miss this?
I never stopped doing it.
No, I mean, I mean this.
You mean us working together?
Look, we were doing incredible work together.
We were a good team. We were helping each other.
Yeah, we were.
You gave that up. Not me.
You wanted a different life.
You said so yourself.
Look, I thought I was doing what was right
for the kids, for us.
Yeah, but you gave up what was most important to us.
Protecting people.
Make sure the antenna's straight.
Man, this is quite the setup.
I've heard all about Cami's work,
but you say this is updated.
Yeah, we can predict earthquakes and pinpoint the epicenter.
We call it SEEPS,
our Smart Early Earthquake Prediction System.
Huh.
Three sensors allow us to triangulate the epicenter.
Attach a stake to the bottom,
stick it in the ground, and you are golden.
Or you can always attach it to a tripod
if you don't have any soft ground.
And they all communicate with one another.
Yeah, yeah, the tectonic AI I developed is state of the art.
Actually, I just finished writing the manual last week.
Yeah, we can predict earthquakes, minutes,
sometimes even hours ahead of time.
And with the sensors, we're able to triangulate
the epicenter itself.
Wow, this is amazing.
This will save lives.
That's the plan.
- [phone rings]
- Oh, I gotta take this call.
Yeah.
So this is real data from the field from yesterday.
Mm-hmm.
Take a look at the timestamp on my simulation.
It's 10 minutes ahead of the quake.
10 minutes?
- Cami, that's huge.
- I know.
Oh, man.
[alarm blaring]
That's not good.
Cami!
DAN: I know. We'll meet in Minneapolis, okay?
Just grab what you need from the house.
Did you hear that?
Yeah, the origin of the new quake is near Marston,
about 8 miles to the south.
Yeah.
Isn't that where your new fracking site is?
Yeah, we gotta secure the site.
Oh, so you believe her now that your facility's on the line?
No, I believe her because she's got proof.
And I'm trying to help fix this thing.
Cam, look at this.
It's at 8%.
Get the diameter.
Hang on, hang on...
[rumbling]
[shouting]
Is that a sinkhole?
It's a collapse.
Go, go, go!
Dr. Weddle, I just wanted to say...
Dr. Rothers, Finn Holly, Dr. Weddle is a colleague.
She's confirming data at the moment,
so she asked me to speak to you.
Do you see now?
We can't even meet on solid ground
because it's literally shifting under our feet.
Fine. Get your sensors set up and calibrated with ours.
We'll use your system as a backup.
I'll even give you access to one of our helicopters.
No, Alan's got a helicopter in Marston.
We're using his helipad.
That's where we're headed now.
Cami suggested you meet us there.
To do what? Compare data?
Of course, Governor Barber will want to confer
once we've reached an agreement.
The quakes are centered from the south, near Marston.
Cami, Alan, and I have all confirmed the data.
Marston?
My sensor indicates differently.
Smart Earthquake Detection Unit or SEDU
predicts quakes within minutes.
Pinpoint accuracy at a radius of six miles.
You stole Cami's tech.
The one sensor design could do everything
your three sensors can, but faster.
It placed the fault's leading epicenter in Sikeston, Missouri.
A single sensor?
You need three to triangulate.
Brett, we're supposed to be working together.
Just like you should have done when you and Cami were at SEMA.
We need to do something.
We are doing something.
We have the ordnance payload.
Relieve the stress along the fault
akin to a single GBU-39B.
Small but mighty.
We'll confirm the weak spot or a hole,
clear the civilians within 20 miles, and boom.
A bomb? No!
For that to work, you would need to know the exact epicenter.
It's safer to use
multiple precise timed explosions
all along the fault if we're going to relieve the stress.
One location just isn't feasible.
You're putting millions of lives at risk.
It's not safe.
It is safe and efficient.
- One blast.
- The epicenter is in Marston.
Your sensor is sending you to the wrong spot.
Brett! Hello?
He's not going to help us.
We're on our own.
We need to get as far ahead of Brett time-wise as possible.
Did you get in touch with Colonel Silas?
Still on hold.
Me, too.
I can't get through to any Missouri congressperson.
[phone rings]
Hello, you're through to Senator Paulson's office.
I'm sorry for the hold, but I'm sure you understand
we're inundated from the events of today.
Ma'am, this is Dr. Cami Weddle.
There's been a major seismic event.
We're aware.
All representatives received
state-related briefs from SEMA and USGS.
You don't understand.
Your concerns will be forwarded to Senator Paulson.
Thank you.
[disconnect tone]
Any luck?
They just hung up.
Six hours till the fault snaps.
You should call the governor and have her
issue a national emergency.
Alan's right.
If no one issues it, we've got to stop this.
How are we looking?
Created the triangulation.
We need to get to the exact epicenter.
Memphis, Nashville, and St. Louis.
- I'll head to St. Louis.
- Okay.
Okay, this is very important to get the placement right.
It's got to be five to ten feet above the ground
and find the exact epicenter to relieve stress on the fault.
Yeah, if we get there ahead of their planned detonation.
We've got to get this sensor up and running
or it won't matter what we do next.
Okay, it's do or die.
Now let's get this packed up.
I'll go with Carla.
Okay, Dan and Brenda, you take Nashville.
That leaves Memphis. Alan and I will go.
Finn, you stay and man the base camp at the lab.
There's no one else I would trust to do it.
Sure.
Definitely more at home in front of the computer
than on the front lines anyway.
I know.
Sometimes you've got to do what you need to,
not what you want to.
You're right.
Hey, while you're in the air you can text me your thoughts
on the color palette for the wedding.
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Promise me you'll be safe.
I'll do my best.
All right, get the sensors put up and then check in.
Finn will let you know if it's transferred.
Hey, be careful.
Both of you.
We will.
I love you.
I love you too, mom.
What are we supposed to do about this?
I mean, I don't know what to do about it, do you?
We'll set up down there.
Is the tripod gonna hold?
It's weighted, but make sure it's balanced.
- I'll need the wires.
- Yep.
It's not blinking.
Guys, we've got an earthquake incoming
in T minus five minutes.
Get to the helo. Now.
But it's not set up yet.
I got it, go.
Are you sure?
- It's already leaving.
- I'll be right behind you.
- No.
- You see that warning, Karla?
Yeah. Emily and Eric are heading back up to help.
I'm almost done.
Finn, are you linked?
The links good! Great job, Karla!
[rumbling]
No, it's too soon.
Emily? Eric?
This is unbelievable.
We need to fly faster.
Brett's gonna go through with his bomb
if we don't get those sensors operational ASAP.
Flying as fast as I can, right?
I'm doing 120 knots at ground speed.
You really think that all this is from fracking?
Put me on Bluetooth.
Yeah, I'll click you over.
I'm gonna call the kids again.
They never called me back after that quake in St. Louis.
[phone ringing]
[coughing]
Eric?
Eric!
Eric? Eric?
Eric? Eric, wake up. Are you okay?
Eric?
Eric! Can you move?
Are you okay?
Can you move?
Liz...
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
- What is it?
- It's my leg!
It's my leg, it's caught on something.
- I can't move, I can't move.
- Emily?
- Karla?
- Eric?
Karla, we're over here!
Karla!
Karla, it's Eric!
Are you okay?
Oh my God. We need to lift.
- Okay, ready?
- Yeah, yeah, go.
[grunting]
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
We need some leverage.
Use this pole.
I'm gonna lift. You're gonna pull him out.
Okay, on three. Ready?
One, two, three.
[screaming]
Again. Okay, ready?
One, two, three.
[grunting]
[panting]
Wait, wait, wait. The tablet.
You guys go.
- Get him out of here, go.
- Forget the tablet!
- Karla! Karla!
- Karla!
- Karla, watch out!
[screams]
Karla, no!
Come on.
It's all right, I'm sure they're fine.
You don't know that.
How can you not be worried about your own kids?
I'm worried about my kids, okay?
But ruminating over the worst case scenario
isn't going to help anybody right now.
FINN: Cami?
Finn, hey.
Cami? Alan? You guys hear me?
Yes, we're here.
Please tell me you talked to the kids.
Just heard the first sensor's up.
There was some trouble, though.
Uh...
Are Eric and Emily okay?
Please, Finn, please, you got to talk.
Finn, let us know what's going on.
Yeah, Emily and Eric are fine.
They're in the helicopter now, but uh...
Karla, she, uh...
She didn't make it.
The building collapsed when they were setting up the sensor.
Have you heard from Brenda and Dan?
Yeah, uh...
They were in their helicopter on the way to Nashville
when the quake hit.
They're safe and still en route.
Let me know if you hear anything else.
Over and out.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry about Karla, I know.
She was like family to you.
I never should have let them go out on that helo.
Eric was right, it was too dangerous.
I should have gone instead.
- Carla would...
- Stop, okay?
There's nothing you could have done.
They're adults now. They make their own choices.
Nothing you could have done.
You should have been there for them more.
Now we can never get that time back and...
We could all be dead tomorrow.
Cami, I was trying to make a life for us.
You prioritized work.
You disappeared.
I thought that I was doing the right thing for you
and for Emily and for Eric.
By getting in good with the governor?
How much money did you put into her campaign?
Money that should have been given to your kids.
I thought that I was trying to create a future for us, Cami.
Even if we stop this quake?
If you keep fracking the planet,
none of us are going to have a future left at all.
Okay, all right. You know what? Stop. Stop.
I am done with this already, okay?
I'm not arguing about this anymore.
And you know what?
I don't know what you're complaining about.
You got everything you wanted.
You got the house, you got the kids,
you got the lab, everything, Cami.
- Almost everything.
- Everything!
Almost everything.
I just kept hoping that you would come home.
Or maybe even just call.
I'm sorry, okay?
I just thought that...
I thought a clean break would be the best thing for us.
I'm sorry, okay?
Look out!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hang on.
We're going down, we're going down.
I don't have control.
Hold on, brace yourself, ready?
[crash]
We're at the Capitol, Mom.
Yeah, I know, but we're out of options.
I have to get through to the governor somehow, for Karla.
Yeah, yeah, we'll be safe.
Okay, I love you, bye.
I can assure you, I have a team of experts
in New Madrid surveying the damage
and gathering information that will be all available
to you shortly.
We have been told that these are normal quakes,
nothing to be worried about.
That's not true. No, that's not true.
That's not the truth. She's lying to you.
I'm Dr. Cami Weddle's daughter...
Who we fired last year.
And I've seen all the information that they gathered.
Today, a massive quake is imminent.
They're out there right now trying to set up
the last of three sensors to try to triangulate
where the epicenter of the fault will be.
We need a military response to strike at the quake
and to try and disperse this energy.
- You have to listen to me.
- Nonsense.
Look, the governor is minimizing just how serious this is.
It's just like climate change.
As we speak, they're clearing sites
so that they can drop a bomb into the fault
and destroy the entire area.
But what these idiots don't realize
is they're bombing the wrong spot.
- Wake up!
- She's lying to you!
- It's life or death!
- No!
Come on, this way, this way.
- We have data...
- Don't listen to her!
We have data from legitimate sources at SEMA,
which is our state seismic agency
that the situation is normal.
It is headed by Dr. Brett Rothers,
who is highly respected here in Missouri.
He is not bought and paid for,
if you'll excuse some honesty, by the people in Washington.
He is one of us, and he cares about the people of Missouri.
Not the Weddle's, not some special interest.
That's all for now. Thank you.
[reporters clamoring]
Let go of me!
- It's a lie!
- Emily!
It's all lies!
- Hey, let go of her!
- Get your hands off me!
Hey, did you hear me, let go of her!
She's telling the truth!
Hey, it's the governor who's lying to you.
When are you gonna wake up, huh? Huh?
No! No! Let go of me!
Get off me.
Park it over there for now.
Be ready.
Hey! Park it over there!
This is the spot.
Get your boys, assemble that bore-driller here.
Yes, sir. You heard the man.
Let's get it moving. Sir, yes, sir.
All right, I want it up and running in 30 minutes!
It looks like the sensor in St. Louis is up and running,
but we won't be able to triangulate the epicenter
unless all three are transmitting at the same time.
There. All set.
I'll let Cami know we're ready to go
once we get to the helicopter.
Okay.
All right, sensors in place.
Let's get this thing in the air.
We'll get some good readings.
[rumbling]
No, no, no, the sensor's gonna fall in.
[gasps]
Looks like the sinkhole missed it.
- We should be good.
- No.
Let's get out of here before it gets worse.
If we don't get that sensor before the sinkhole expands,
we'll never find the exact pressure point on the fault.
- I'm gonna go get it.
- No, Brenda.
- Please.
- I gotta go get it.
Come on, grab everything.
[shouting]
[tires squealing]
Help me! Help!
We have to help.
We have to help!
- Brenda, where are you going?
- We need to save him.
Brenda!
Hey!
I'm coming!
Brenda, stop!
Brenda, the ground's not stable!
I just need you to...
Help me!
Okay, come on.
Brenda, we got to go! Leave him!
Just unlock the door! Come on, I got you!
Come on, Brenda!
I almost got him!
Hey, we're gonna get you out of here!
- It's not safe!
- Unlock the door!
- I think my legs are broken!
- Come on!
[rumbling]
Ah!
Dan!
Brenda!
My God, Brenda!
Are you okay?
You okay?
Yeah, I think I just got knocked out for a second.
Jesus. You all right?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I thought you were...
Okay. I'm gonna go check on the sensor.
- Sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna go check on the sensor.
I think we're good.
I'm gonna go check on the main rotor. Okay?
Well, the helicopter looks good. Main rotor looks good.
It's just a hard landing.
I think we're all right.
Let's set it up over there.
All right.
This is it.
Big moment we've always imagined.
I know.
You know, before everything turned upside down in our lives.
Yeah, Cami, I'm...
I'm really glad we're sharing this moment together.
Me, too.
Now we just gotta cross our fingers and hope this works.
Oh, it's gonna work, all right.
Okay. I think I have a link.
All right.
[laughing]
Sorry.
No, it's all good.
Just can't believe this.
Hey, it worked.
- Right. Let's go get Finn.
- Yeah. All right.
[rumbling]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look out, look out, look out.
No, we can't lose the sensor.
We can't lose it.
I don't want you to get hurt. Cami, no.
It's got to be in here somewhere.
Just keep me steady. I'm going in.
Oh, Cami, this is crazy.
There it is. It's going to fall.
- I've got to grab it.
- No, no, no, no.
I got it. I got it.
Stay here, okay? I got... Hey, stay here.
Whoa... whoa!
I got you.
[grunts]
- Be careful.
- Here.
A little higher.
- You got it?
- Got it.
Grab the box.
[rumbling]
Okay.
There you go.
Don't forget the head. The head of the sensor.
I got you.
[rumbling]
Ah!
All right.
[grunting]
I'm not going to let go.
Ah!
Ooh...
[grunting]
- Take my hand.
- All right, fine, help me up.
[grunting]
[panting]
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You sure?
I'm gonna...
I'm going to get in touch with the kids.
Let them know we're on our way.
Yeah, yeah. Let me grab this stuff. Here.
I'll take that heavy stuff.
I got it.
She's got it. She always got it.
Move it, people.
We've got to change this bit fast.
We got it as deep as we could go.
We could keep drilling, but we need to replace the bit.
It's going to take some time.
How far is it now?
We pushed as fast as we could go.
Maybe 1,000 feet, give or take.
It'll have to do.
Prep the drop line, get the bomb attached.
We're running out of time. We have to move on this now.
You don't get it right the first time,
we won't get another chance.
Let's get it right then.
I'm working from the best data that I've got.
We'll give it our best shot
and hope they were close enough to have the desired effect
we need to stop these quakes.
Let's prep the bomb, follow orders.
Are you sure we're far enough underground
that we won't decimate the city?
Yeah, it'll just feel like another earthquake to them.
What do we do with those other warheads?
Put on the helo and be ready to go.
Get everyone packed up and ready to move.
We're out of here as soon as that bomb is in place.
Yes, sir.
You heard the man, let's get packing.
[whistles]
Move it, move it, let's get going, people.
Dan, good news.
All three sensors are up and running.
Just waiting on the last one to sync up now.
What's wrong?
I couldn't get to her.
I couldn't save her.
Brenda...
She's gone.
What?
Why didn't you tell us?
She would have wanted us to make sure we got this right.
She wouldn't have wanted us to waste time
feeling sorry for her.
You know Brenda.
You're right.
Hey, we need to stop this quake.
For Brenda.
And Karla.
[alarm sounding]
Is it working?
The software isn't designed to handle this much
incoming data at once.
It's going to overwhelm the central hub.
Gah!
We've got to get the power back on.
Yeah, I know.
All right, without the calibrated sensor locations
were screwed.
I got nothing. Um...
Okay, stay on radio.
I'm going to go in the hanger and flip the main breaker.
Once the lab powers back on, turn on any of these monitors
and systems that doesn't come on automatically.
- Got it?
- On it.
[alarm blaring]
What's going on?
Yeah, I'm working on it. Okay, just give me a second.
This is...
[grunting]
DAN: It's not working.
Almost there.
- Try again.
- All right, I'm almost there.
[grunts]
[powering on]
It's on.
Great. I'm heading back now.
They said they'd be here by now.
- You don't think that...
- Don't even think it.
They said they're fine and they're coming when they can.
I've got the monitors back on.
Great.
Come on, come on.
Oh, thank God.
It's still here. We have the info.
What does this say?
Wait...
Brett and his team are in the wrong spot.
They need to be in New Madrid, not Sikeston.
That's where the epicenter is according to Cami's sensors.
That red, those are the areas of impact?
Yeah. The quakes are spreading.
Are you sure? Maybe we just need to run them again.
Yes, I have. All right?
Look, all these areas along the Mississippi,
those are flood zones.
With the recent storms, that water level is at a max, okay?
When this thing hits, all that water is going to spill over.
New Madrid, the Midwest, all underwater.
Maybe even the entire country.
You're lucky.
They wanted to throw you on a jail cell
until this all blows over.
Blows over? Are you kidding me?
- It's getting worse.
- We're doing all we can.
It's not enough.
You need to evacuate the state
and declare a state of emergency.
Do you realize the trouble you caused me back there?
I've got the press on my back now.
You're just like your mom
once you sink your teeth into something.
Millions of lives are at stake.
We almost died out there cleaning up your mess.
And when the next one hits, it's going to be even worse.
And the next one and the one after that.
So what are you going to do about it, Governor? Huh?
Your mother caused a massive panic
the last time we had a series of quake events.
The DOJ will have my hide
if we are not 100% positive about this.
I cannot declare a state of emergency on a hunch.
So for the good people of this great state,
I will not have a redo of that episode.
We want the same thing.
We're on the same side, more than you know.
Are you kidding me?
We don't want the same thing.
You got your politics, your contracts, your kickbacks.
We don't have time for this right now.
Why didn't you use my mom's data?
It's way more reliable than Brett's.
Emily, the tech Brett has that he developed for SEMA
is much, much more advanced than your mother's.
But it hasn't been peer reviewed.
It's literally just Brett's work, right?
Which was developed and based off
of my mother's research and development.
Tell me I'm wrong.
We have a difference of opinion.
No, you omitted crucial data, my mother's data.
That's not a difference of opinion.
That's a difference of reality.
It just sounds to me like you're more concerned
with staying relevant than saving lives.
[rumbling]
[distant shouting]
Look, just tell them the truth.
My mom's right. The quakes are getting bigger
every single time they hit.
Just do the right thing.
Or their deaths are going to be on your hands.
[phone buzzes]
Governor Barber.
Alan and Dr. Weddle are here?
Send them to my office.
- Mom!
- Thank God you're okay.
You all right?
Hi. Welcome.
I just spoke with Finn.
He confirmed we've triangulated the data
and linked up with Brett's system.
Yeah, found the epicenter's weak spot.
It's a wide area.
We're still honing in on the exact site,
but it's somewhere south of New Madrid,
near the fracking sites.
Not in Sikeston, like Brett thought.
How sure are you of this?
This earthquake will rip apart the entire continent.
And the flooding will destroy what's left of middle America,
maybe even the entire country.
We have to stop this quake.
And you're sure you can stop it?
Yes.
We have to stop that warhead at Sikeston.
I tried to reach out to Brett, but no luck.
This could blow up in our face.
Are you okay with this?
Am I okay with it? It doesn't matter if I'm okay with it.
The tech's solid.
And there's more.
Aside from the quakes growing in strength,
the data is showing that it's rapidly building.
And it's hitting at specific time intervals.
Meaning?
The big one we told you about?
You can expect it in a few hours.
If you're wrong about this, I will lock you up myself.
This is not a charity for people's pet theories.
Pet theories?
We have a state to protect, a society that has to keep going.
Do you understand that?
Sure.
All right, I see what this is about.
See, for me, it's about human lives.
And that means sticking out your neck.
[rumbling]
Wait...
Get under the table now! Go! Go!
- Go, go, go, go!
- Take cover!
- Hurry!
- Get under the table!
Get under the table!
Mom, make it stop! Make it stop!
It's okay, it's okay.
I think it's over.
Mom, was that the big one?
No, no. That must have been a 7.4.
The big one is predicted to be at least 10.0.
That was a short 7.4.
That was short?
All right, come on, you guys.
I got you.
You all right?
Wow, that was heavy.
Oh, my God.
It's over.
This is all my fault.
Oh, my God.
If that's a 7.4, what's a 9.7?
Now you see why we need all the people
in the immediate vicinity evacuated.
Multi-leveled buildings cleared.
We need a traffic lockdown to keep the cars
off of the highways and the bridges.
Okay.
Get Brett on the phone. We've got to stop this.
We're the point team now. Understood?
Understood.
Have Brett meet us in New Madrid.
I'll relay that information ASAP.
Thanks.
Dr. Weddle... Cami...
just please get down there and stop this anyway you can.
I'll do the best I can.
Alan, get Brett on the line.
Eric and Emily, get the climbing gear
from my car to the helicopter. We're going to need it.
Okay.
I'm gonna update Finn. Be back in five.
Hey, we're back. How's it going?
Glad you're okay.
You, too.
How was New Madrid?
- Hey, Dan?
- Yeah.
Can you give us a sec?
Sure.
Thanks.
Senator Paulson can't take your call.
Straight to voicemail.
Going to voicemail. I'll try the land line.
I think the tower's out or something.
What's up?
[sighs] I can't do this right now.
It's been almost a year since you and Alan separated.
We have a catastrophe on our hands.
You want to do this?
I think we rushed into things.
I think a lot of things are happening way too fast.
Finn, it's...
Look...
This type of environment, it's not for me.
The system overloaded and the entire lab shut down.
You know, millions of people could have died
because I didn't account for one little thing.
And I heard the two of you on the radio.
You guys are built for this kind of pressure.
Not me.
And I can't ask you to give that up.
This is your life's work.
It's complicated.
Then I'll make it simple.
I will stay here and hold down base camp for you guys.
I'm here until the end.
This is my home, too,
and I will do whatever I can to protect it.
But once this is all over...
I'm going back to Jefferson City.
Maybe finally get that job in government.
It seems like they could use a computer scientist
who actually knows what they're doing.
Maybe slow down for a bit.
I'm going to miss you around here.
Yeah.
I'm going to miss you, too.
Come on, keep it going. Hurry it up.
[phone rings]
Go for Brett.
Hey, hey, Brett, what's going on?
Hey, it's Alan Weddle right now.
I need you to talk to Cami about something. Cami?
Cami, I got him on the phone. Come on out.
Governor Barber ordered you to stop.
We're getting ready to drop the payload into borehole.
The epicenter will be at New Madrid, not Sikeston.
You we're wrong last time.
How can you be sure you're not wrong now?
If you detonate that bomb, it'll set off a chain reaction
of quakes we can't come back from.
That last quake convinced me we have to make a decision.
Sometimes it comes down to a best guess.
You're playing with people's lives.
We are sticking with the original plan
before the activity worsens.
You said it yourself, we have to do this now or it won't work.
If you blow up the wrong place, it won't work at all.
My information is reliable and it's the best we've got.
Over and out.
Ugh!
He's going to get us all killed.
We have to do something.
We've got this, we're going to do something, okay?
What if I'm wrong? What if I'm wrong again?
Hey, stop that.
Okay, you're not wrong, okay?
Trust yourself. Believe in yourself.
You got this.
Fine but I can't have any mistakes right now.
Come on.
Get those ropes into the helicopter.
Pull up Brett's tech specs and ours into a side-by-side.
Just like last time, right?
- Boost the signal.
- Yeah, I did.
Same results.
But now that the sensors are up,
we should have a couple minutes heads up
before the next quake hits.
Wait.
It is at the fracking site in Marston, not Sikeston.
The quake's coming in 56 minutes.
Regardless, we should cross-check the data with Brett.
You should call him.
Wait a minute, you guys are seeing
the predictive data right here?
When Brett detonates that bomb,
it's going to trigger an 8.6 quake
that's going to cause a kickback
that'll basically reset the plates
but at a higher intensity.
What will that trigger?
A 10.6.
It's in the same time frame but 100 times the intensity.
It'll split the entire continent in half.
We've got to get to Marston and stop Brett.
I don't think the mobile lab can take it.
Everybody outside.
I'll back up the data.
[phone rings]
That's enough! That's enough!
Stop!
Get back to Jefferson city.
Yes, sir.
Let's get her in the air.
You got it!
Aaron, let me know when everyone's clear.
We need to move now.
Get everyone out now, Aaron.
Copy that.
Yes, we've pulled them back 50 miles.
I'm beginning detonation process.
Three, two, one.
[beeps]
[explosion]
What's going on?
Sir, it didn't reset the plates.
It triggered a magnitude 8.6!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No! Dammit!
It's splitting apart the Mississippi River!
Massive flooding is inbound from here to St. Louis.
[rumbling]
Under the table, now!
We have an 8.6 occurring now.
Was that Brett?
We've just received word that a magnitude 8.6 earthquake
has occurred in eastern Missouri.
The last quake, a 7.4, left the capital
Jefferson City heavily damaged.
Reports of massive flooding along
the Mississippi have been reported,
which may send tsunami-like waves
as far north as St. Louis.
The death toll is estimated to be
in the thousands and rising.
Mission is a failure, sir.
The blast didn't reset the fault.
It just increased the intensity.
The next quake will be a 10.0 or higher.
No word yet from Governor Barber
if this 8.6 with part of the state's earthquake mediation.
Brett.
What happened out there?
Governor Barber, we need to start evacs now.
Right now.
I need casualties. Collateral damage.
Everything's gone.
It's all gone.
Shoulda listened to Weddle.
We need to evacuate the state.
- Now.
- It's too late, Brett.
This is a complete institutional failure.
We have a magnitude of 10 or greater imminent.
Find Cami! And do whatever you can to fix this.
Sir, what do we do now?
We have floodwaters approaching our location.
Sir? Sir! Ah!
Okay... okay.
Okay.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
[screaming]
You okay?
- Fire up the helo.
- All right, I got it. I got it.
We gotta go. Follow your dad. Now.
No, no!
Go.
Go, go, go.
Mom, Mom, no, no, no.
- You have to come.
- No.
Mom!
Oh, wow.
Let's go, guys. We gotta go. We gotta go.
[engine powering up]
Mom!
Hey, come on. We gotta go.
Tell her we gotta go.
Mom!
Come on. You have to go! Mom, come on.
Guys, we gotta go now. Now, come on.
Backed up the data.
Whoa!
- Go, go, go, go, go, go.
- Go, go, go, go.
- You gotta go now.
- Go, now!
Dad, Dad, Dad, go, go, go, go.
Ready?
[grunting]
Hang on!
[panting]
Oh, God.
We made it.
Put your headsets on.
Get Brett on the radio.
That idiot detonated. He didn't listen.
No, we need to get Governor Barber on the phone.
We need to get evac to higher ground.
There is no higher ground.
The Mississippi started flooding.
The United States is going to completely split east to west.
There is nothing we can do.
[panting]
No!
Alan, Cami, this is Brett. Come in, over.
Brett, your alive.
Hey, we're headed your way.
Negative, negative. Everything's been destroyed.
All systems are down. It's gone. All gone.
Mission's a failure.
Where are you?
Should have listened to Alan.
Last check was 32 minutes
until the fault splits apart completely.
We failed.
We still have time.
Do we have anything, any weapons to use as an ordinance?
We brought another warhead as a backup but
with the granite encasement around the fault,
we've got nothing.
ALAN: Where is it?
On board.
It won't do us any good though, Doctor.
There's no way we're boring a hole that deep.
How much time do we have?
About 28 minutes.
Where's the weakest point?
The weakest point is about a mile north of Marston.
See, right there.
Right there?
That's my decommissioned fracking site.
Well, how deep does it go?
It's about 5,000 feet.
The heart of the fault.
I hate to say this, but Dad's fracking site
may actually be a good thing this time.
Wait, won't the site be underwater?
No, Marston's on a plateau, 300 feet above sea level.
It should be dry.
Brett, meet us at the airport in Marston.
I'll send you the coordinates.
Maybe, just, maybe we can stop this thing.
All right, drive it right here.
All right, everybody. There's no room for mistakes.
So, mini tactical nuclear weapon wired with a remote detonator.
Push these seven in sequential order to arm it.
Push this eighth detonator button when you're ready.
But be careful.
You need a clear signal.
No obstructions between you and the bomb.
And once you trigger it, you have 30 seconds
to get out of there.
Got it.
You're not coming with us. Go with Brett and his pilot.
- What?
- No, I'm going with you.
Please, after Karla, I can't let that happen again.
Mom, I'm coming, too.
Somebody's got to fly that helo.
That's not a good idea.
Cami, you don't have any time to argue.
Look, Mom, none of us are going to sit this one out.
All right? Not for this.
And none of us want to get hurt either, but it's our choice.
Okay? Not yours.
We can handle this.
Okay.
Are we certain it's my mine in Marston?
Location confirmed.
Dan, thank you for everything.
You stepped up when you didn't have to.
No, no, I had to.
All right, let's get this done, guys.
Give you a hand.
Be careful.
All right, you see that field up there?
Yep.
I think that's a good spot to set her down.
- Copy that.
- That's where we're going.
Okay?
See that? That tower moving?
That's not the wind.
A foreshock.
We've only got eight minutes. We need to hurry.
All right, okay, nice deep approach.
All right, I lower collective right paddle.
Watch your airspeed. Watch your airspeed.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
All right.
Your VSI. I'm just saying...
Dad, please. Thank you.
- I'm just saying.
- I got it.
I know you're saying but I got it.
Easy. Okay, good.
Nose through it, nice.
All right, let's set it down.
Eyes out front. Eyes out front.
Let's skid down and right.
Nice job.
- You did it, kid.
- We don't have much time.
We got to hurry.
Eric, you sure you got this?
Got it, Mom.
You got this?
- I got it.
- You sure?
Because I can do this.
-Dad, I got it
-Alan...
- I got it.
- He's good. All right.
You got it, kids.
Come on, let's hurry.
All right.
- Ready?
- Ready.
- Got it?
- Ready?
Okay, give me slack. Eric, give me slack. Thank you.
That's it.
- Go up.
- Take it up, take it up, go, go.
Nice and steady, full power.
Eyes out front, eyes out front.
Correct for that yaw right there.
There you go.
Give me a little left pedal on that.
- The tower!
- Watch out! The tower!
[grunting]
Eric, I need you to straighten it out.
Straight... no, no, no, no.
Don't go over there.
- Eric!
- I'm trying, I'm trying.
I thought you knew how to fly.
Steady, steady.
Full power, Eric.
Eric!
Come on, get control of it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, Eric, Eric! No, no, no, no.
Full power, full power.
Don't let it do that to you.
Get out of my ear. I'm doing it.
Whoa!
Eric, the bomb, you need to steady.
Pull up, full power, give me some left pedal.
Point it into the wind.
Okay, got it.
There you go, you got it?
It's really windy, Dad.
There you go, there you go.
Okay, stay in the wind. Grab it in the wind.
You're good, you're good right there.
All right, we need to set the well.
- Let's go.
- All right, I'm heading over.
At the well, over the tower this way.
How deep does this thing go?
About 1,000 feet.
Yeah, right through here, watch the tower.
- Straighten up.
- Straight up over the top.
Keep it steady.
I'm keeping it as steady as I can.
Bring it toward me, little more toward me.
There you go.
Easy, right there.
It's good, looking good.
Lower the collective just a little bit.
- Good job.
- Very nice, okay.
That kid.
I wonder where he gets this from.
Two more lefts.
There you go, looking really good. Nice and steady.
Keep it right there, keep it right there.
Nice.
Five more feet, that's good.
Keep coming, coming, right here.
That's it, right there. Last five feet, we got it.
As soon as I start this, we've got about 30 seconds
until it hits the bottom and we've got to clear out.
It's going to be 30 seconds you guys,
then we're out, then we're up and out of here.
All right, let me know when.
Everybody ready?
Okay, I'm going to arm it.
Three...
Two...
One!
Drop it.
Go.
Okay, now go, go, go.
- Nice, we got it, we got it.
- All right, pulling out.
Go, go, go, go, go!
- Let's go, let's go.
- Lower the ladder!
Okay, let me know when, let me know when.
Bring the ladder over here, in here, right in the zone.
All right, heading over.
Yeah, meet us here, meet us here.
Come back to the LZ, LZ right here.
Okay, lower it down, lower it.
Okay, lowering.
Eric, it's broken.
What do you mean it's broken?
It's broken, it's only going part way,
you need to get lower.
- Lower!
- Wherever you got, lower it.
I'm as low as possible, I can't go any lower.
Okay, hold it steady.
Okay, grab the ladder.
Go, go, go, go, run, jump, jump.
Steady.
Hang on.
Okay, yeah, yeah, they got it.
They got it? Yeah, yeah.
Let's go, get out of here, buddy.
Whoo!
FINN: Five, four,
three, two, one.
[explosion]
Whoa... whoa.
Are they alive?
- Are they good?
- They're on the ladder.
Whoo!
All right, heading out.
[laughing]
- We did it.
We did it!
Oh, yeah!
You were awesome out there.
You are too.
Hey Mom and Dad, we're reeling you in.
FINN: Cami, pressure has been relieved all along the fault
and the water is receding.
CAMI: It worked! 10.0 averted.
Good job everyone.
The damage done was catastrophic,
nothing can change that.
But at least we can rebuild.
A quake like that shouldn't happen again.
How about that flying, Pops? Whoo!
Yeah, Eric, man, I'm so proud of you.
Flew the crap out of this bird.
Nicely done, brother.
Woo-hoo! Yeah.
Oh man, now you see why I got out of this racket.
Even though I do still miss it sometimes.
Yeah? You ever think about coming back?
Yeah, I think about coming back.
But...
You and Finn?
We talked.
He's a really good person and I'll always care about him.
But... 1705
01:24: