Sir, we will be arriving soon.
Would you like some more of the same wine?
No,
it's okay
}And I
I'm Korean.
That's right,
I'm sorry
Have a comfortable flight
Our representative...
Well, your main
business is real estate...
There is quite a lot of land in Korea.
Are you doing investment business here and there in the U.S. ?
Well,
there are people like that.
People born
rich
Just a rich person with no bottom or end
How can I trust them?
You should have considered my opinion
These
are completely different situations
I don't understand
just do whatever you
want
I'm calmed down now because of the medication
Doesn't stop crying since birth
I tried all the famous medical staff, but...
Well, medically
There is no problem...
We have heard it all
Sorry, but
can it be just us?
yes?
Cheonjoneon Sinjungguryeong Habulsoji
Ilwal Cheonsaeng Iwal Muyeong
Samwal Hyeonju Sawal Jeongjung
Ohwalhyeoldan Yukwalnoenoe Chilwaldanwon
Palwaltaeyeon Guwalyeongdong
Sojijeuk-gil, Shinjung Samjeong, Habulhoji,
Ilwal Taegwang, Iwal Sangryeong, Samwal Yujeong
Hojijeokgyeong, heartache, six
veins, four limbs, spirits, Baekjeol advanced level
It's Uisong Cha-gyeong.
There must be more people like you at home .
With my father...
grandfather
You are talking about Jiyong and your father, right?
Those faces...
yes
- That expression changes from suspicion to surprise
- I think so.
Always live in a bright place
People who only look at bright places
The world must have bright light
We can see it
And the people
I only believe in things I can see and touch
A world with bright light
And behind it
From long ago, people
I knew those dark beings
Called by various names
Ghosts, devils, goblins, monsters
And they always
yearn for bright places and are jealous
Very Occasionally
Sometimes it comes down to foul play
And then
people come to me
Yin and Yang
Science and Superstition
The person right in between
I am Lee Hwa-rim, a shaman
I received a call from my wife.
This is Park Jiyong
My brother...
He ended up committing suicide in a mental hospital.
From then on, to me...
also...
It also started with my newborn son.
When I close my eyes,
someone screams
I'm strangling you
Eldest grandchildren...
Blood circulation...
Usually , a genetic disease is suspected at first.
Later on, they even move because the house site is a problem.
shadow
I saw a shadow in this house from the beginning.
The shadows pressing on the veins here
maybe
It must be my grandfather's shadow.
My grandfather?
To put it simply, it's a cold wind.
It is also commonly called oxygen masking.
In other words,
someone among my ancestors
You're complaining about how uncomfortable it is.
Are you sure?
yes
one hundred percent
then...
What should I do?
We need to spend money and people.
I can't do it alone
I need to call the experts...
Ai, tsk...
Why are creepy faces passing by?
It's a mess!
Oh,
are you looking at me when I wake you up?
Oh, sorry.
low price
Come on, quickly.
One, two, three!
Whew
Um... the water wasn't full.
Oh, sorry for waking you up.
Well, it's clean.
Yes, it is fragrant.
Hey,
why did you put so much in it?
uh?
Ah, this...
Hey, really
Don't put any metal or anything in it.
Inconvenient, huh?
Chairman Kim
Here
is a place for my mother and the elders of the family to lie down.
I took care of everything, right?
yes, that's right
So, everyone
is healthy, their business is prospering, right?
Yes, thanks
Even if I dig here again...
This prestigious place is
This is the best of my 40-year career , huh?
Ah, look at this,
the five elements are perfect, right?
Right, yes?
You really made me cum.
Oh my, really...
Ah, yes...
So don't worry
I think it's right to bury it again.
If Mr. Kim
says so, then so be it.
Ah, but
Ah, why do you keep appearing in my children’s dreams?
These days, my wife also
says she can see her mother...
Go undertaker!
Are you done yet?
Hey, I'm hungry.
I’m hungry too,
this person is hungry too
No, someone
made the claim without checking, huh?
- Is that the number?
- yes
it's okay
Who has this grandma?
Who has grandma's dentures?
Have you ever...
Does grandma have dentures?
Sanghyun, you
That thing in the closet
Do you have dentures, grandma?
No, that's you...
I burned all of my grandmother's things...
I don't have grandma anymore...
dad...
I must have something...
baby
What should I give to my grandmother when she is hungry ?
Then I...
What do you remember about your grandmother?
There's nothing...
Did you say it was Sanghyeon?
Sanghyeonah
Grandma is
always by your side
It's blood
You can never escape even if you die
- Sister...
- With the same genes
A group of shared bodies and minds
When the human body
ends its activities, it becomes dust and becomes the ground
And we
will drink the dust and tread on the ground
Living, dying, and being born again
Keeps turning and turning
Well, in a word
This soil and land connect and circulate everything
Fuck all the ‘superstitions and frauds’ .
For the top 1% in Korea,
Feng Shui is both a religion and a science
I am Ji Gwan
Searching and digging for land for the living and the dead
This is Hoan Kim Sang-deok, a geomancy master
Many domestic companies are considering
the current economic situation
Survey results show that it is perceived as a long-term recession
According to the survey, Korea's...
Oh, eat it when it’s done!
No, just
wait until it ripens.
All you have to do is ‘get it’ once.
Honestly, there today.
there...
Is it a famous place?
Uh-huh, this person...
What are you talking about?
I'm still a regular...
No, I saw that grave earlier.
Well, Hyeonmu is also a bit ambiguous.
Well, it looks like a tiger...
I'm not sure...
Okay, this anti-feng shui is done.
No,
if you think you know that well
Hey, do it alone now
No, so I
thought about it.
Are you saying that an average of 250,000 people die in Korea every year ?
Of these, 30%
have stores.
Then, since the Joseon Dynasty,
this narrow land
They wouldn't have buried so many people in every good place.
But the fact that the famous place
is still popular...
- I like this...
- Just...
It's 65 points, that's it
Yeah, yeah,
not 100 points.
Now the seeds have dried up and
are no longer there
Look at
these idiots like you, huh?
They are all sold to mutual aid companies.
huh?
All these idiots who live off the ground like us.
- They're all snooping around construction sites
- Ugh...
This is the end, huh?
last standing
- One wreck
- Baby, stay still.
You arrived quickly?
Oh my, you came early?
- Oh my, it's been a long time
- Oh my.
- Hello
- Oh, yes.
- Hey, wow
- Yes.
oh my
- Oh my
- the smell of bunches reaches all the way to Seoul.
- You have to be able to hold it in
- Songi ate it all.
What are you talking about, haha
- How have you been?
- Hey, welcome back.
I should have contacted you more often.
Oh well,
there's nothing you can do if you're busy.
however
Bonggil has become prettier
Uh, really?
Hey, don't even say anything.
They say the sisters
take each other with them...
- Be spoiled
- yay
How long has it been like this, huh?
- Has it been three years?
- yes
Time flies so fast
Write, how...
How is business these days?
Well, it's just like that.
- Well, it's the off-season, so...
- Ah, so I...
- Again, our elders...
- Just stay still.
This is something... sniff
Sniff, I think it smells?
Can't you smell something?
What smell?
What is that smell?
- Oh, I think it smells like this?
- ha ha ha
Ic... Tsk.
I hid it so I could hide it...
It caught me right away
- Hey, solve it, what is it?
- It's stuck, it's stuck.
- Hey, be quick to notice.
- There will be a mark, then.
Introduction to a close doctor
I went to America with a strange family?
Park Ji-yong...
Even my father
is Korean
The client
is of American nationality
There is no bottom or end
, it's just...
He's rich, very rich.
Good start, huh?
My eldest grandchildren suffered from ghost disease.
Even a newborn baby
Oh my...
It lasted quite a long time
Isn't it possession?
It's not that far yet
...
Just looked at it...
It's a cold wind...
first of all
I can't trust those people.
If you do it wrong, things will get worse.
The baby will be fine soon.
we pray together
Treat again
we just
All you have to do is live quietly from afar .
Oh my,
how about showing some belly at the wedding?
Ah, what better
coma than that?
Oh, that's still true.
What is a grandchild? A grandchild?
Plus,
with this yellow hair...
Oh, aren't these headlights blue?
It's really tacky...
Oh, so Yeonhee
will continue to live in Germany once she gets married?
What does this person mean?
Of course I should live in Korea, tsk.
Hey, by the way
I was a little worried about money because Yeonhee is getting married.
- But you still got one big thing?
- That's right.
Hey, our Lord
Well, when the time comes,
they even provide severance pay like this.
amen!
No, but how rich is this guy , huh?
Are you giving me 500 million won for the relocation ?
Would you have given that to me?
I guess they gave me more
uh? more?
Hwarim , what kind of a bitch is she?
You couldn't have eaten any more, right?
Yeah, uh
The bright blue thing is just
annoying
uh
First of all, please honor my grandfather and
tell me about his hometown first.
I originally...
I am a person who researches the reputations of the people in this family and
even their jobs.
Since you said it was urgent
, well...
than the person receiving the money
Doesn’t the giver
need more trust?
ah...
trust?
Well, let's do it, okay?
If you don't feel like it,
just pretend it never happened.
Could you please keep two things in mind?
Please keep everything
a secret today.
And please apply makeup right away.
With a government office
With government bonds?
So what, don’t even open the opening?
Well, does it matter?
Either move it somewhere else anyway
Well, I heard you were doing makeup
?
This is it
This usually
has to be reported to the district office first...
After the opening,
the undertaker collects the remains,
Then
you have to move to another location or apply makeup.
yes?
Tsk, well, first of all...
Let’s look at the place first.
So do my parents
My relatives are quite against it.
- So, as quickly as possible...
- Let's take a look at the grave site first.
It's in the north of Gangwon-do...
Ha... why am I anxious?
Ah, but I'm
telling you not to open the coffin.
That's a little strange
Oh, shouldn't we check the remains ?
So
you're saying you don't even salt it?
What 's in the coffin ?
Have you ever seen a tomb at the top of a mountain?
It's rare
Do you know this mountain here?
It's my first time here.
A person who knows all eight provinces and mountains
Are there places you don’t know about?
I only look for famous places
and...
The dragon is spread out
good night
Can you see North Korea over there?
uh? I can also see North Korea
uh...
The tomb is very simple compared to the location.
huh?
What do you have?
You don't have a name?
Can you tell me who recognized this tomb ?
A famous monk at the time
My grandfather
made great contributions to the country.
My father said he found the best spot for me...
Are you a monk?
yes
I heard that there is a monk whose Buddhist name is ‘Gisune’.
Are you a jockey?
The name of the law is very unique.
For something like that,
the tomb is a bit simple, right?
At that time, there was a lot of robbery...
So I heard that they served quietly and simply.
How are you feeling?
Well, I'll catch you right away, okay?
why? What's strange?
president
I don't think I can do this job
I got a pout again, Mr...
older brother!
- It's arbitrary, tsk
- What is it?
Don’t you like it very much?
Is there any way?
Why aren't you talking?
no...
The pickling here is fine and
fine, but why? why?
Oh, how much does this cost? I really...
no, sir
Why are you doing that, yes?
You know everything here
What happens if you touch a grave by mistake?
I lived off the land for 40 years
This is an unheard of secret place.
This place is really evil
A den like this...
It's definitely not a place for people to lie down.
If you touch something wrong like that,
Everyone , from the branch office to the workers,
are lined up for a portrait. I, these people.
Talk about what you know
Hwarim, did you see it?
foxes
A fox and a cat are polar opposites.
This doesn't make sense.
It is the worst of evils.
That was the last time I saw my son's smiling face .
actually...
There were two more children in front.
For unknown reasons, they all miscarried.
I am a son who was acquired through hard work at a late age.
Does Mr. Kim
have any children?
Yes, there is
I have a daughter who will be getting married soon.
Congratulations
What is a celebration, hehe
Oh, then does your daughter
do something similar?
My daughter
majored in aerospace engineering at KAIST.
I'm currently working for an airline company in Germany.
There's so much fuss about getting married now , oh my...
It's fun
My father is a feng shui practitioner.
My daughter is in aerospace engineering...
This is it
If you just leave those two like this and
look at them,
It's a field with a lot of similarities
, right?
These five elements
Originally based on earth
, water, fire, iron and wood
Studying the essential requirements that make up nature
And this is space engineering, huh?
then...
Please save my son
Park Ji-yong , are you hiding something from us ?
- What do you mean...
- Three eight three four one seven.
One, two, eight, three, nineteen
latitude and longitude
The numbers engraved on the back of the tombstone
That monk called Gisune.
I don't know who that guy is
It's eerily accurate.
I can see a clear intention.
no...
I do not know
And I
'm not hiding anything from you two.
Haha...
I'll say it again
Moving to a place in such an unidentified evil place ?
This is really dangerous
It's the same thing as digging landmines with your bare hands.
Let’s do a Daesalgut.
I knew that
You do it with gut and village head at the same time.
Why are you like this?
I know the answer
I don't believe in anything I haven't done
Although it is my first time doing this when moving ,
It's not theoretically impossible.
No, wait a minute.
why we now
Are you getting permission from Mr. Kim?
There is not just one Ji-gwan in Korea .
This is why it's hard to work with old guys
hey
No, the kid is sick.
yes?
This hotel has a good location.
- Okay
- let's go!
It is a kind of trick exorcism , also called ‘Akdorigi’
First , connect the five pig-year workers and the five animals
Let those five people dig the grave
Send the negative energy coming from the land to Daejeon
The principle is that I blow it up for you
Your aunt is here.
It looks like you finally helped her.
‘Im-in, a campaign car’
‘October Sinhaesak’
‘Go Yeong-geun, who studied abroad’
'Reduction gou'
‘Student Miryang Gable’
'Singibo'
‘Bimuhugan’
'Upwards'
Thirty-three thousand in the palace under heaven
Twenty-eight figures in the underground palace
Thirty-three thousand Jebuljecheon
Geumwoo stance Namseon Buju
Let's create a Joseon state
After ascending to the Asia Pacific Dynasty
Clear the ground on the back
The house built by Zuo Zhaoxiang
Guide to Mt. Gwanak
Inwangsan Mountain becomes a blue dragon.
Dong-gu Jeman-ri White Tiger!
let's go!
Hey!
good night!
Well done!
hey!
let's go!
- good night!
- OMG!
- let's go! good night!
- Sangsan!
Sangsan!
Destroy my grave!
A prize!
A palace!
Sangsan!
hey!
- Ugh!
- came out
Overview!
Thank you for your hard work
- Oh...
- Oh my...
The chill is incredible.
It's been so long
I can't recognize it.
Hey... what is this...
hey...
There is a juniper coffin?
This
used to be used only in the royal family.
Is there something like this here?
uh?
Adjutant!
Uh, okay
Okay, okay,
cheer up little by little
Now, lower your preference!
- Slowly, slowly
- Lower it.
Hey,
I'm just going to put the coffin on the hearse.
We 'll go straight to the crematorium
Bury me with that tombstone and
give me a good ending.
Now let's change the straps, uh
And don't eat meat today
- Yeah
- Oh, my chai.
I'm using it well.
yes
There's a dead man
lying inside.
Let’s serve each other respectfully.
Oh my, that's right
I am Go Young-geun, who wants to be president .
Now that it's over, just
relax, okay?
hmm
see...
There's nothing
let's go
Hey, what is it?
Seed...
No, what's going on?
Ha, my...
- I'll talk to you
. - Then I'll call the warden.
president
It suddenly rained without any forecast
I think I'll have to postpone my makeup for a bit.
Why is that so?
It's not like you're putting on makeup outside, right?
If you put on makeup on a rainy day like this ...
The dead
can never go to a good place.
Well, you might think it's a superstition ...
I'm talking about professional ethics.
This happens
sometimes, yeah
In times like this
The remains were placed in the morgue of a nearby hospital.
You can just apply makeup again on days when you don't have hands.
If you go to the hospital , don't you have to file a funeral report ?
형님!
Brother, I'm on the phone. It's okay.
Oh, you can go right away!
don't worry about that
Because we know everything
No,
what does it mean to say that the coffin has been relocated and then brought back with the coffin?
Hey,
I guess the owner of the store is preventing it from opening.
- Hey, W
- Hey, that's enough, that's enough, uh
what the
Oh, what's wrong?
- Ah, here, ah, quickly
- Hey, it's me...
The last team left today so it was quiet.
Oh, great.
Oh my,
it's raining on makeup day...
It's hard to leave even once
Do I have to set the date again?
yes
But can you really trust those people ?
I gave as much as I could
and said only what I had to say.
No need to worry
Now that I have time
Let’s think about a way to quietly enshrine it at Yeoju Seonsan.
I'm still against wearing makeup
He is my father,
so I can decide.
Get some rest first.
I...
I can't give an overview.
Let’s just leave the coffin open.
I just have to set the humidity
Ah, thank you anyway
Hey... the coffin...
It looks like you held a government position?
- no?
- Wow, it’s been a while.
Ah, yeah, hehe
Sangju and the bereaved family
all went up to Seoul.
But Hwarim
is coming this way?
I hope you will be happy this day too.
I'm having a bowl of hot soup
I'll go somewhere and come back
is it so
This is my first time meeting you.
How...
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I was passing by and
saw a sign on the road.
Oh, I see.
It's no different
There is a feng shui sign on the sign of Boguksa Temple.
I came here because I was a little curious.
Are you a Ji-gwan?
Haha, yeah
I studied under teacher Choi Eui-jung in that building.
Right now,
I am a person who is barely able to survive alone.
Although this place
looks a little shabby
It is a place that has been in existence for over 100 years .
The head monk who first built Boguksa Temple here
He was very good at feng shui and
made quite a name for himself.
Ah... yes
I think you can tell just by looking at this place.
So, by the way...
Here is the name of the head monk
Are you Gisu by any chance?
Are you a jockey?
No,
it's Monk Wonbong.
But, why
are you asking?
ah...
Ah...
on top of that mountain over there
There was a grave with no name.
Just in case you know...
Huh, sure
Well,
I don't know if it still exists.
I heard a lot of rumors a long time ago
What... rumours?
Don't be alone in the dark
Go across and
have a bowl of beef stew.
Yeah, okay,
don't worry.
- Okay, go
- Good job, okay, go in.
Ha, why do you decide the menu , Mr.
There was a rumor that there was treasure buried in that tomb.
Treasure?
There was also talk that it was the tomb of the richest man in Joseon.
There was also talk that it was a royal tomb that no one knew about.
So, in the past, there were quite a few grave robbers .
Grave robbers?
Suddenly,
everyone is captured and...
I heard there were people who crossed over to the North or something.
So you ended up
not being able to rob?
I didn't even try, I guess
Perhaps because it is the tomb of a high-ranking person,
security is very tight.
It was difficult to even approach.
this...
This is the equipment they left behind at that time .
however
Why do you ask about that grave?
me today
I dug that grave
how
Was there any gold or silver treasure?
hey?
- eww!
- What are you doing?
hey!
teacher
teacher!
hey!
teacher
Teacher, are you okay?
what?
Oh, what does that mean?
The coffin was opened?
Hey, I'm shaking my hands...
If you've given enough,
you shouldn't do that, Mr.
For some reason, his eyes were dull
uh
What happened?
Something
passed by the teacher
Well, what's going on?
What came out there?
It's so fucking rough
father...
My father...
종순아
My baby
Please open the door
father...
Please come in
Uh... father...
Our small and intelligent
puppy...
This
place flows with milk and honey...
Your father is cold and hungry...
sorry...
Your soul
is probably running around like crazy right now
Sangju will be dangerous
Teacher, please
go to Seoul first
In the meantime, we
'll bring the soul back here
No, you're calling me here right now ?
I screamed like that under him for 100 years.
No one took it out
Only hatred remains in my soul
I'm going to find all my blood ties.
Oh my, you're killing the mood, Mr...
It's raining outside,
the coffin lid opens, and a ghost comes out.
I really
don't want to do this, man...
What's going on with me
? This is so...
Do you think it would be okay to do the exorcism and this as well as
two soups a day?
it's okay
Elder Ko, you
need to get your timing right.
You have to hold on to it as soon as you come in.
Sabah World Namseon Buju
Haedong Shipbuilding Republic of Korea
Gangwon Dora Twenty-six Building
I captured the county and called it Goseong-gun.
Grab the noodles and make them Jukwangmyeon.
Park family, Kwon clan, Yongjeong
When we pick up the dead today
Cho Dangogwi Lee Dancheongeun
Come back to the three-tiered room.
Come back to the reflection room.
Come back to the anti-government room.
Hehe,
come, come, come
Chunsu chooses everything.
Is it impossible to come in because the water is deep?
Saying hello to the sick
Am I sick and can’t come?
On horseback...
If you can't come because you don't have any clothes,
please bring back your resident uniform.
If you can't come because you don't have a bar,
please come back with a listing bar.
If you can't come because you don't have shoes,
please come back wearing Sangju straw shoes.
- If you can't come because you're thirsty
- hehe
Come back for three drinks
If you can't come because you don't have a home,
come back to Shintae's house.
If you can't come because you're in a bad state,
you can get lost in Chobaekri.
- If you can't come because you don't know what to say
- Okay, everyone is here.
- I'm begging for help
- Hey!
Please come back at least for a moment
- Thinking about ancient times
- Hey!
Gong Do-ran has gray hair, and
what he cannot avoid is death.
Load it!
Yes, he's coming, he's coming
Yes, it's loaded! It was published
Bonggil!
Take it!
Grandfather
Who is there?
yes?
Bonggil, don’t let go!
oh my...
What were you so upset about?
Try speaking
- yes?
- Seed...
Unpack everything here today and leave.
Don't go anywhere else
My babies...
Take me with you
That won't work
I missed it
What do we do?
Yes, hello?
Ah, this is Kim Sang-deok,
boss
Is everything okay?
yes
What's going on?
Oh, that's a relief
No, that's because
something happened to me...
I'm
heading there in a bit of a hurry right now
It's a little late, but
can I talk to you for a moment?
yes
What's going on?
Park Ji-yong,
you are staying at the same hotel you were at before, right?
Yes, I'm almost there?
I'll be up soon
wait a minute
who are you?
Yes, I
am Sangdeok Kim
어?
Hello?
What is it? What is it?
Mr. Kim,
are you outside right now?
Hey, boss
Ah, no,
no! No, no
That's not me
That's because my grandfather's coffin is open now
Hey, Jiyong Park
I have urgent business
to attend to, please open the door!
- Um, um, my grandfather's coffin?
- Ah, yes...
I'm sorry, but
things turned out that way
What's going on inside?
So
Never! Don't open that door and stay still
- I'm almost there now
- Jiyong Park!
From now
Just listen to what I say and
act calmly
Jiyong Park, listen carefully
Stay away from the door now and
avoid towards the window
First,
open the door
First of all, the situation is urgent so
I need to explain it quickly, boss!
Don't even answer
- Don't even listen
- Oh, open the door quickly
First go to the window and
open it
Grandpa will protect you
You have to take care of your grandfather
Hey, boss!
Trust me, quickly
Open the door!
Jiyong Park
are you okay?
Good luck
to the youth of the peninsula!
Can you hear the sound of hundreds of planes and cannons?
Go forward,
sons of the empire!
Raise your silver gun and sword in the shining sunlight of the rising sun !
For the new unification of Greater East Asia
your whole body
Offer it to the great empire!
ambulance...
Call an ambulance
Please call an ambulance
yes?
Call an ambulance!
Well,
I saw it clearly with my own two eyes.
If you leave this alone,
it's all a disaster.
I'm going to that crematorium.
Okay, let's go
Oh, and my brother gets permission to wear makeup.
I 'll be waiting there
now...
- Grandfather's coffin was opened
- The fox cut off the tiger's waist.
yes?
The fox cut off the tiger's waist.
The fox
cut off the tiger's waist
mother in law
Ah...
are you uncomfortable, where are you?
I guess you're tired after visiting the countryside.
I need to get some rest...
The kid looks good today
I can't contact you at home, so
I'm going to visit for a moment.
Okay,
I'll be by your side.
Ah, you man!
I'm not doing this because I'm in a hurry.
When
did I ask for this?
No, bro,
not now
Oh,
I'll be there soon, so hurry up, okay?
Oh, and
it's raining like this, what kind of makeup do you need?
What does Sangju say?
What
came out of the coffin, man!
You know what I mean?
You need to put on makeup right away.
Please call America quickly.
yes?
What are you saying?
You saw it now
Next time, the child is in danger?
I don't answer calls home in the US.
Ha, then...
What is this?
You said you moved, but
you didn't even prepare it?
Are you going to burn this whole coffin?
Oh my,
there will be an uproar if the district office finds out about this.
Your father’s coffin?
Yeah, I
don't understand either.
Anyway, I need to put on makeup quickly .
What does that mean?
Yes, aunt
You have to hurry.
To an American child...
Father is leaving now
- Burn it.
- No, wait.
The store manager
hasn't answered yet, wait a minute.
I can't contact you in the US either
So, you need to allow your aunt
to be cremated
Is that really the only way?
All right
Put on makeup
yes
태워라
Oh my, let’s sell it...
I can't go to any good places.
Re-search after leaving the path
Brother, Changmin knows, right?
After moving then
You say it hurts a lot?
Brother, let’s visit when you have time , okay?
Turn left in a moment
Even the hospital doesn’t know
Ugh... just do the inspection and spend money
Ha, dreams are difficult too...
I see things in vain...
older brother...
I think I've woken up...
Not that other thing, that...
I saw something while I was working after work that day ...
It looks strange...
The snake...
What, snake?
Hmm... I should just leave it alone...
older brother
I just want to ask you one favor.
Please find that half-cut snake and
give me some healing.
I really didn't want to go that day...
I really hated it...
형님
It was strange from the beginning
, right?
Why is there a tomb there?
It's a booklet
Yes... I'm busy right now
I'm currently studying the Bible with people from church.
Here is 50,000 won
Uh, here it is.
Tung
yes?
A booklet?
Yeah,
it's right below that.
But Elder Go
Have you ever seen a coffin standing upright ?
yes
Are you Teacher Hwarim?
Now, V-Up
Now, two beats
When the ground is distorted,
the coffin sometimes stands vertically...
Hey...
Is this too big?
what's this?
What is that again...
this...
I think they made it impossible to open it from the outside
...
- Or...
- Or, what?
It would be the opposite.
No, just
take it out and take a look.
take out something
It's right to let the store manager know first.
We
still have money to talk about.
we...
Don't touch this
Let's get it out first
Ha, it must be someone from the family.
I can't just leave this guy here like this.
This...
this, uh...
Hey, let's just pull this out.
Go get the rope.
the sun is falling
Now, when you say one, two, three
, pull hard.
one! two! three!
Is that a human coffin?
Where are you going...
Is there a problem?
As I said on the phone
I suddenly moved to a new place
I'll take care of you today
They say Sangju
is coming here.
Is there somewhere I can put the coffin ?
why...
What is this...
what is this?
Hey, Bodhisattva.
Excuse me, but do you have some glutinous rice
?
Bong Gil-ah
Go to the car and
get some horse blood.
You know it's not good.
A lieutenant?
What on earth is that?
Please tell me everything you know
I do not know
I really don't know
Why is something like that buried there ?
And why was my father's grave in such a bad place?
It was written in the famous tablet.
My name is Marquis Park Geun-hyeon, Vice Chairman of the Central Committee .
Your father
was a very famous person.
sold the country
So the monk
punished my father...
I know
So I don't know any more
That monk called Gisune
Not Korean...
He was Japanese
- yes?
- Are you Japanese?
The name...
My name was Junji Murayama.
I heard that he is a person who knows all eight provinces of Joseon.
But why did their father, who was loyal to them,
I don't understand why they buried it in such a bad place.
I was informed that the American child was okay
I will prepare the case that Jiyong promised
That coffin...
Just take care of it.
Yeoshimun lump sum payment Seolguhosinmyeong
Jane's disease, Do-Aek-gyeong, Ho-Gwe joint funeral
General Gapjin's Bua release amount
is 7,000 dollars.
Wihoinshin famous amulet
General Gapin Wia released
Guardian of the Seven Thousand Buddhas of Hell and Hell
Reiki shredding self-
harm 60-year-old Jongbulhasaeng
It's called Wiadoje Hokip Cheonmun
Let's burn it right away.
okay
Let’s burn it as soon as dawn breaks tomorrow.
Yes, that's right.
Ah, I think that would be a relief.
excuse me...
I've boiled some noodles inside, so
please warm them up a bit.
Oh,
yes, thank you.
- Oh, now
- Come on, come to work.
Oh my, that grave
had a bad feeling from the beginning.
- Just stretch the mountain straight and
- Ah... Now that I think about it,
I didn't even get to eat a single meal today
, sir...
ruler
Have a drink of this at least
- Oh, thank you, oh, thank you.
- Oh, oh, yes.
Well, ayu, ayu,
thank you, I'll enjoy it, yeah
Well, take care of your health.
This scent is, well...
Oh, this is precious, this
- Oh my, a cup of Bodhisattva...
- Oh my, it's hot.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Let's get a drink.
Is there
any acorn jelly...
Hey, I just
said this once for a laugh...
Yes, Junji Murayama
Don’t you remember?
The teacher
sometimes said this before
In Japan, that...
Yes, fox onmyoji
yes, that's right
Onmyoji Murayama
I heard I met a teacher
once a long time ago...
The Lord is so strong
that he is a human being
It's obviously a fox cub, why
Are you here?
Where are you now?
Uh, no
okay
Thank you, Gwangsim unnie.
I'll call you again
Grandma...
I feel strange...
oh my...
They took my liver...
My liver...
They took my liver,
my liver
Some guy
took my liver
Some guy took my liver
They took my liver
Because they took my liver
where are my clothes
Where are my clothes?
my clothes, my clothes, my clothes
- Ha... fuck...
- Where are my clothes?
Some guy
took my liver
My clothes... my liver...
They took my liver...
madam...
Hwarim-ah
Madam, really, sir...
Oh,
fuck Nurinnae...
The seal pierced my stomach.
This now...
What is this, you bastard?
speak up
This now...
I think it's in the barn down there.
Wake up people quickly
yes
Do... do, run away
Bong Gil-ah
Bong...Bong Gil-ah
Cough...
Bonggil...
Bong Gil-ah
Bonggil! Bonggil!
Wake!
Chungju High School regular butler 350,000 won...
- Bong-gil...
- Kim Young-ja from Sunshine Cafe 700,000 won...
- Bong-gil, Bong-gil, come to your senses
- broadcaster 170,000 won
- What should I do...
- I have to pay back 2 million won to Cheonil Sangjo...
- Mirae Essen subtracted 5 million won...
- Teacher, please help me!
Ask for help!
Help!
Help me...
Bong-gil, come to your senses.
Come to your senses,
Bong-gil...
This morning
in Goseong, Gangwon-do
Human casualties due to wild bear attacks...
Neither of you have fever, so
I'll give you some fever reducer.
At the damaged village barn
Dozens of pigs
were found with their abdomens torn
Two additional bodies from the same attack were found
The victim
was a monk from a nearby temple
It turned out to be a migrant worker who worked at the livestock farm
County officials are
currently working with local governments and military units
Chasing wild bears,
etc...
sorry...
I
asked to bring it out for no reason...
Same thing with Bonggil...
Bodhisattva too...
Bong-gil got sick while playing baseball
and quit...
When I came to my teacher after being abandoned by my family
I told you not to be a shaman ...
It's okay if you're with me...
I said there was nothing to be afraid of
...
I stayed quiet because I was scared.
There were footprints
And the shadows...
In shamanism
There is an orthodoxy
The soul is imperfect and
the ears have no body.
So in the end, a person's
intact mind and body
I mean, you can never win.
But that...
It's completely different.
not a spirit
It's a spirit
- Spirit?
- The soul of a person or animal
We evolved together by attaching ourselves to things.
This should never happen in our country ...
I didn't feel anything
What is it?
where did you come from
Why was it at the Park family tomb?
There is a lot of damage to the abdominal viscera.
I shed a lot of blood
But the problem is that
I have some damage to my spine...
Let’s send him to a big hospital quickly.
Because the damage is caused by wild animals...
The fox
cut off the tiger's waist
At that time, there was a lot of robbery.
I heard that the tomb was kept in a simple manner in a place that no one knows about.
The robbers' luggage
is still in the warehouse.
‘Our land, my comrades’
Iron Blood Order?
Organ damage has been prevented in a hurry ...
I need to check further
First, I have to regain consciousness
...
It's strange.
Oh, what is this?
Fortunately, I passed the crisis.
He said his spine was slightly injured.
I heard you can walk?
They say you have to overcome it
But I'm still healthy
What on earth are you doing these days
?
What?
sister
huh?
It smells like you're enjoying it?
I know
, that's why I called you
Let's play goblin for the first time in a while
Park Jahye, what are you doing?
lock the door
Badge per...
Lee Chung-gu...
Park Gil-ho
Shin Pal-gyun
Kim Jeongbok
Song Jong-ik...
min...
radical
Jeon Tae-hwan, Lim Chung-shin
yes...
It's so tragic
For grave robbers
Creation of low hell terrain
Yongjangbongjeon Jajiijin
Booby Speedy Pyeonyeok Yeongcheon
Wow, ladies,
it’s been a long time.
Everyone came?
i just came
The harvest is over and
the weather is getting chilly.
How come everyone is like a dog?
Oh my,
everyone gathered like this.
Hurry up , you have to bring some ups and downs .
don't worry
I already
made some rice cake and some boiled pork.
Where did I hear that a delicious smell
wafts from the air?
I brought it because I had plenty of it, right?
I brought my hearing loss
Even if you eat it, there will be no residue!
Then I live beyond the horizon
Do you think we should invite Jang and Jecheon’s house too ?
What are you calling a busy person for?
If we just
stay quietly and deliciously...
Okay...
let's eat together.
Did you catch some sweetfish?
What?
Where do you think Seobu Yoon
came from?
Ah, what are you talking about?
Have you not heard of Seobu Yoon’s Yag?
Well done
Ah, there is no way Seobu Yoon could have come.
What is everyone saying?
Don't you talk quickly?
Don't even talk to me
Where on earth did you say you met something terribly dangerous
?
Why did I encounter something so difficult?
Does that
mean he was lying down sick?
You don’t know?
I met a guest during the night.
What the fuck are you talking about...
Oh my, Seobang Yoon?
What are you doing?
Are you lying down scared?
woah
Does this guy look fine?
Who are you?
The customer who said he met a dick?
Just tell me at once
master
master?
What kind of master?
Speak quickly, you son of a bitch.
My master
is the one who killed 10,000 people and became a god.
That Lord
Where are you now...
three eight three four one seven one two eight three one eight nine
It's Sakura...
The general who guards that place
What the fuck...
Master!
Please look at me!
Here I am,
I want to be your body
I'll take out that meat for you.
Jahye
Come to work
Please save me, Jahye...
Oh, motherfuckers
you all die
Hwarim, don’t do this.
It's a Japanese ghost
I know
Even if it has nothing to do with it,
they just kill it.
They say they kill everyone who comes near them.
Haven’t I seen you in Japan before
?
Don't even come near it
No matter how much your grandmother
is next to you,
This doesn't work
Let's go, Jahye.
Then what is the length of the bong?
I'll call you
let's go
You mean it's underneath there?
They say it's back to normal
...
Ah, but
why did you go there again?
uh?
Jiyong Park
said that before that gentleman died.
‘The fox cut off the tiger’s waist’
Oh, what does that mean?
In our Feng Shui
The shape of the land of Joseon
is a tiger.
A tiger holding a continent
however?
The numbers engraved on the back of the tombstone
latitude and longitude
Where would it be?
That's right, there
exactly the waist of a tiger
That fox onmyoji that Hwarim talked about
That fox cub...
Plus, wow!
It means that an iron needle the size of a bamboo stick
was stuck in it.
Then what is the American Park family grave above ?
Those
serious-looking people over there
Because I keep looking for things like that and pulling them out.
At that time, the tomb of a high-ranking official
was just covered over.
So
they can't even approach it at all
then
Why are there ghosts there?
uh?
You are the general who protects the castle.
three eight three four one seven one two eight three one eight nine
maybe...
I think that's what's protecting the iron needle.
Lee Hwa-rim
we...
It's a business relationship
- Let me ask you a favor that doesn't cost money.
- Hey, what...
If you're thinking about something useless
, don't say anything.
Well, is it the national spirit?
Well, they cut the country in half with iron stakes .
Do you still believe that?
All the iron needles in that temple are for land surveying.
You know
Previous academic conferences also
said that 99% are fake.
So what about 1%?
Elder Go
why?
This
is different from just an ordinary strange thing
There's something meticulously
calculated.
Not long ago, you saw people dying because of that grave.
Do you want to get stabbed again?
older brother
No matter what the iron needle was stuck in
, just
We've lived well
without any problems so far.
But
why are you doing that now?
okay
You or me
We
sold the land to rich people
I ate well and lived well during that time.
It's because of me
Elder
Go This is land, land!
This is the land that my future grandchildren
will have to step on and live on.
And you and me
and all of us!
And then
someone
Hwarim, they say it’s a spirit.
If , as you say, it
is a ghost attached to metal, then
Can't we just take the needle out
?
Then, if the iron needle disappears,
the length of the pole can become better.
Hey, what...
Well,
I heard he's a general or something that's holding on like this.
But how do you pull it out
You saw it at that temple.
Oh, I really...
Calling me like an animal...
speak with spirit
Brother, do you really
think this is possible?
There is something we
can do
- There's something I can't do
- I'm sorry, but that ghost...
It's not something that can be eliminated.
Even if there is no resentment
It kills everyone even if they come near it.
It's a Japanese ghost
however...
I can't get rid of it...
I can come out for a moment
I can take the time
Bong Gil-ah
Please
give me some more betadine
I'll clean it with saline solution one more time
and put a gauze on it
네
Wait
Did you avoid this bastard’s tattoo?
What kind of tattoo is this?
That's a blessing
Oh, I'm sorry.
There is damage from that wild animal nearby.
- Oh, I... uh...
- Hehe...
where...
Are you on your way...
Ah... there...
We
came to that mountain to cut down the grass.
Ah, yes, that...
A few days ago,
a military unit was searching the mountain over there.
- Ah...
- Ah, we...
Well, it went up quickly and then
I'll be back soon after working on it.
Ah, yes
Open it for you
Withdraw, withdraw
, return, return
Because I gave you what you wanted
It will probably move around 10:00 o'clock
If you just lure the yew tree...
I'll take as long as I can
We'll pick it up soon
Okay,
just wait for 30 minutes.
and two minutes
If you take out the iron needle
I will wash it away with the blood of this horse.
Mr. Kim
That iron needle...
It really exists, right?
one hundred percent
sister
Please look after Bonggil today.
If things go wrong,
Bonggil is in danger.
stop looking
They say it came out at a celebration.
Elder Go
Anyway, thank you for coming with me.
‘ It only takes one person to defeat’
‘Can two people fight against each other?’
‘A three-ply cord is not easily broken .’
Ecclesiastes 4:12
amen
sister
I hope they don't kill him
I will die instead of you.
And why are you saying that when you’re having a good time staying in Kyochon?
Have you eaten your fill?
It's this way
Is anyone there?
My mountain is noisy
Is this mountain the old man’s mountain?
Yes,
this is my mountain.
You damn tree old man.
But why
can't I hear the sound of guns and swords?
That's not it
The war has already ended a long time ago
No
Our war is not over yet
Why are you
here?
That fox enshrined me in Daitoku
I brought you here, not the shrine in Namsan.
It must have been Katahito’s children who ordered it.
Or maybe it was Makoto's doing...
Now this is a land of silence
This is no longer your place
No
no
We must continue to aim for blessings
Go forward with your guns and swords
To the north
A brave centipede never steps back
what?
Nothing comes out
AC...
As the owner of this place, I will bite again.
Since when have you been here?
Be polite to me
I am fear
This is my land
I ask again,
what on earth are you!
Hey, there isn't any.
No, Mr...
No!
Oh, it's 100%!
Mr. Lee...
madam...
Remember
The enemies cut off my head in Sekigahara, but
I have already defeated the body.
I am the god of war!
The eternal and incorruptible master
is a flaming sword.
three eight three four one seven one two eight three one eight nine
That fox is casting a spell on me
and I have to protect this place.
Are you dominating someone right now?
Please free the humans you are holding on to.
Quickly!
Please!
He is human
Forward
Damn old woman
The sun
spits out the fire of samadhi
- Subdue the light of Mun-eup to Cheonbong Station
- Make the Geumgang subdue the monster
- I change the dirty traces that cause illness...
- into good and auspicious things...
- Huh, did you find it?
- doesn't exist
- Nothing
. - Oh, what does that mean?
Oh, there's nothing!
Quickly withdraw...
her...
Ah, brother
This can't be happening...
This can't be happening
Three eight three four one seven one two eight one eight nine
My daimyo,
please return!
three eight three four one seven one two eight three one eight nine
Sangdeok Kim!
older brother!
Come out quickly!
Then why is that ghost there ?
They said he was the general guarding that place.
It means it's back to where it was before .
Have you ever seen a vertical pipe ?
It's fire
the fire goes into the ground
come out!
Will you become my subordinate?
Otherwise
Would you give up your liver?
Have you memorized everything written on your body?
It's been over 500 years
iron stuck in the ground
the fire that protects it
Season...
Please eat
That fresh liver
damn!
Horse blood! Horse blood here!
Blood of the White Horse
It's hot
Go in and
You must never hear it again.
It's a spirit
The soul of a person or animal
We evolved together by attaching ourselves to things.
okay...
It's iron
You are the burning iron
older brother!
- Brother
- Come to your senses!
Come on, we have to get out quickly.
God,
I too, God is coming
hear hear hear hear
It's dirt...
And it's a tree
On the spirit of discussion, Tuesday
, Wednesday, Thursday, gold and silver
make up the four seasons
Fire and water are opposites
Gold and wood are also polar opposites.
done
Burning iron...
Its opposite is...
It's a tree wet with water.
Water overcomes fire...
OMG!
wet wood
tougher than iron
Sister, wait a minute.
The blood is black
ruler...
last
Bong-gil, aren’t you a dog?
Brother... this...
- What should I do with this
... - Teacher...
What should I do... Huh?
this...
Die...
- Fortunately, it doesn't hurt that much
- Hey, Kim Sang-deok!
Hey, Kim Sang-deok!
Come to your senses!
Always lived close to death
okay
- This time it's just my turn
- 200 lines.
Death
is returning to dust
comfortably...
Oh, wait a minute.
daughter's wedding
Please give me the courage to get through the surgery ...
Please embrace me with the blood of the Lord ...
How many people die in a few days?
Several people were seriously injured
CCTV was secured following a tip from a village resident ...
After a long search, the soldiers
They succeeded in capturing a wild bear alive.
Public opinion is boiling over whether to kill or save the innocent bear.
Public opinion for and against
is boiling
It was originally planned to be killed for the safety of residents ...
oh my
I opened my eyes
older brother
Can you come to your senses?
huh?
Fortunately, Mr. Kim
He recovered quickly for his age...
And Bonggil...
what...
Oh,
it's a ghost, it's a ghost
Wow, really...
This
is our food now
- Oh, so you eat without me?
- Come on, eat.
- Please give me one.
- Uh.
Ha, I will eat well.
Is this a good restaurant?
Do you always come here and eat?
Do you know that I eat something because I want to
?
I force myself to eat it.
Because it’s delicious
delicious
I'm fasting, so
what should I do?
- Ah...
- We have to make a living too.
At this point, my brother, lose some weight.
After winter passes
Everyone returned to normal life
casually
let's go!
I told you to align with the sun , right?
Are you saying that not everything facing south
is good?
So what should I do?
Lady... tsk
uh...
Yes, next
There will be a meeting between the bride and groom.
bride and groom greetings
Yes, next is the bride and
groom's relatives and family.
- There will be a photo shoot
- Hey.
- Please come forward
- Elder Goh
Hey, come to work
Ah, why are we filming those relatives
? Why are we...
Ah!
- Just take one picture and go
- Mr.
Just take one picture and go
- A child is no different from a family member.
- Ah, what kind of family photo are you taking...
Yes, the tall one in the middle.
Please go back one space.
Yes, the person with glasses on the left
Please stick inside a little bit.
yes
- Ah, so they don't overlap
- How can I get my father's belly and my daughter's belly?
What is this, this is
a child, my true...
Okay, let's take a picture.
father of the bride
I'll look at it from the front.
Yes, thank you for your hard work
Now, everyone
smile once
One, two, three
Digging