♪ And I looked at a mountain
♪ And the mountain
started shakin'' ♪
♪ I looked at a boulder and
the boulder started breakin'' ♪
♪ I looked at the ground
♪ And the ground
started shakin'' ♪
♪ When I looked at you
my knees started shakin'' ♪
♪ Knees shakin''
Heart achin' ♪
♪ Bones a breakin'
♪ I'm in love with you
Joe, you hear that?
No. Hear what?
I thought Big Red
wasn't scared of anything.
You getting the heebie-jeebies, friend?
I am the heebie-jeebies.
Remind me why Junior G-man's
coming along for a ride?
I'm just here to make sure that
whatever's in that box
and one pretty lady
make another 600 miles to
Fairfield without any trouble.
So what's in the box?
Should I tell him?
A funnel-web spider.
Probably the most
deadly arachnid in the world.
Only this one seems
to house a plausibly
demonic entity.
You're yanking my chain, right?
That's not the half of it.
There's all manner of bizarre
phenomena associated with this creature.
Temporal, gravitational
I mean things
you wouldn't believe.
I barely believe it
and I've cataloged
the photographic evidence
in detail.
It's been kept sedated
in a state of sensory
deprivation
until we can analyze it
in a more controlled setting.
Dammit, you're not hearing that?
Hellboy, are you okay?
What's happening?
Oh my god!
Ahh! Ahh!
♪ Heart achin'
bones a breakin' ♪
Ahh! Ahh!
♪ I'm in love with you
Ahh!
- You alright?
- Yeah, yeah.
Hey, lay dead a sec.
Ah! Oh fuck!
Oh shit.
Hellboy, Hellboy, look.
I like them better small.
Don't let him get away.
It's...
Oh crap.
Who builds a tunnel to hell
in the middle of the woods?
Some kind of ventilation shaft.
Coal mining country.
Appalachia.
Well that's just swell,
we lost the cargo.
After you.
Come on...
He, he, he.
Joe?
I'm okay.
Field work, huh?
It's not much like
research, is it?
I just don't get it.
Spider what made it
go crazy like that?
Something in these hills.
Trees,
and the dirt.
Something haunted.
Evil.
This place has the stink.
I smell pine needles?
Underneath that, Joe.
Madness.
Death,
called out to Daddy Longlegs.
Woke him up.
How do you know that?
Dark things call to dark things.
I heard it too.
We are so screwed.
Screwed, chewed, and tattooed.
We need, we need to find a
phone. We need to call this in.
Yeah.
Ma?
Around these parts I'm not sure
which one of us stands out more.
It's the devil come up the road.
No it ain't.
Get!
It's that red fella
from the United Nations.
I've seen him once on
the cover of Life magazine.
United Nations?
Look at you...
little oriental doll.
Ain't you a purdy thing.
Um
I'm Special Agent Song, ma'am.
We've been in an accident;
do you happen to have a phone?
Sure we do.
It's in back next to the color
television
and the chicken that
shits out silver dollars...
- and the Mercedes Benz.
- Alright.
May as well come inside.
Ma'am, get these on some modern rags,
doll, they're all cut up and bloody.
Oh no, that's not necessary.
What happened to him?
He ain't moved a muscle
since I found him.
Anyone thought of
taking him to the doctor?
You guys have doctors, right?
- Or you like him as a rug?
- Truck's out.
Anyhow ain't no doctor
gonna do him no good.
- Why's that?
- Cause he witched, that's why.
Witched?
Child didn't have no sense.
Kept teasing that Cora Fisher.
Throwing rocks at her window,
leaving dead things for her to find.
Told him he better stay away from her.
Everyone knows Cora Fisher be a witch.
You said Cora Fisher?
Tom Ferrell. I will be damned.
I ain't dead yet.
Never thought we'd see
you around these parts again.
How many years it been, Tom?
A spell, I reckon.
I found this in the doorstep.
Hmm.
Let's see it.
Ahh.
Yeah.
Witch ball.
Yeah, I've I heard of these.
That's what made
that mark there, ma'am.
You said Cora Fisher did this?
Why, you know her?
Used to.
She wasn't a witch back then.
Take off that boy's clothes and
boil them, calling it out Cora Fisher's name.
If she's one that witched him,
that'll bust the spell.
You going up there, ain't ya?
Yeah, reckon I will.
First I'm going to
stop by and see my mama.
Sorry, Tom.
Figured you knew.
She's, uh...
she's dead?
Long time now.
Her brother come up to fetch
her. Took her back East.
Oh, ain't that, uh...
what about my daddy, then?
Never did see much of him.
Not once since you left.
Guess he finally drunk himself
to death.
He weren't ever much good.
Well, friends,
ma'am, I'll be on my way.
Just a second, Mr. Ferrell.
Um, was it?
It's Tom.
Tom,
this witch, Cora
you might say, eh
this sort of thing falls
under our
sphere of expertise.
- Do you mind if we come along?
- Excuse us. Tom.
Hey. What are you doing?
- Field work.
- Field work?
You're lucky to be alive.
I'm taking you back
to headquarters,
where you belong,
in the library,
spilling coffee
on your weird old books.
There's something going on here.
You said it yourself.
'This place has the stink.'
Yeah, it does.
It's exactly why you shouldn't
be here.
Look, I... I need to
understand it.
Okay? And not from some weird
old book, but for real.
Like you do.
Besides, are you really in such a hurry
to tell Broom we lost the cargo?
If y'all are coming along
you best come along.
♪ May not believe
it but it has to be told ♪
♪ A poor soul
doing the Dead Man's Stroll ♪
Ohh.
Who's that there?
Oh,
look at you
all pie-eyed.
What you come see
Grammy Oakum for?
Huh?
What's that?
Oh,
they want to know
how to make a witch ball.
Well, I'll tell you.
It's easy peasy,
you dance around,
buck naked
calling out: blood of weasel,
tail a rat,
guts and bladder of a black cat,
buzzard eggs and baby's nails,
foot of toad frog,
brain of bat.
And you put a pot to boil
and it all goes in.
Cut some hairs from your head
and your nethers,
and wrap 'em
round a gob of stuff from
the pot.
Make 'em round
and a good size for throwing
and that's that.
You people
wanna trade your souls
for some balls of poison.
Grammy Oakum says: 'Go
right at it.'
And she'll see you
in hell.
Magazine said they found you in
a church in England.
So they tell me.
That's all right.
Everybody knows the devil
can't set foot in no church.
You know I'm not actually, uh
The devil?
Yeah.
Oh,
no, I met that son of a bitch.
He don't look nothing like you.
Here's Cora's place.
Cora!
It's Tom!
Tom Ferrell!
Cora?
You knew this girl pretty
well, huh?
Well
we, uh, we weren't much more
than kids.
We were sweethearts.
Figured we'd
always be together.
It's a long time ago, I guess.
Oh, girl
what you do?
Great. Fucking witch balls.
There's more.
Eh, guys?
What do you make of this?
She must be out roaming around.
Just gotta wait for her to
get back.
That'll be her demon familiar,
I suspect.
I hate those.
They feed on
the witch they're attached to.
They feed off each other.
The witch, the animal.
According to the lore, they
function as symbiotic parasites.
The lore.
Lord, have mercy.
My mother was a witch.
I bet they left that little detail out
of your magazine, huh, Tom?
Hmm?
I never met my mother.
Never wanted to.
In fact...
everything I ever knew
about witches
I wish I didn't.
On the way up here
you mentioned you saw the devil.
Some 15 years ago,
about a mile from this
very spot,
come upon a stream, and
there she was.
No, not the devil.
Close enough.
Her name was Effie Kolb.
I knew right off
she was trouble.
I'm ashamed to say
I forgot all about
poor old Cora Fisher after that.
You see, Effie,
she was a witch,
and she got me all twisted up,
thinking maybe I ought
to be a witch, too.
And all that talk about
having power over other folks,
made it sound real good.
Yeah.
So, I went out
and I got me a dead black cat.
While my Ma was out,
I boiled it on the stovetop
till it went all to pieces.
Took that mess down
to the creek,
to clean off the bones.
Now Effie told me whatever bone
I was holding when the devil showed up
that was gonna be my lucky bone.
So arbitrary.
I knew him right off.
I heard tales about him all
my life.
Mister Onselm,
some of the old folks
called him.
Most just called him the
Crooked Man.
Crooked Man. Uhh.
As story goes, Mr. Onselm
was one of the first white men
who came here from Europe
hundreds of years ago.
He played both sides
in the war between the states.
He came to be a very rich man.
Sounds like a real clever
little fella.
How did that work out for him?
They say heaven don't have much
room for rich folks.
They got plenty down there.
They sent him back up,
to claim souls instead of
legal tender.
They say he takes a
a copper penny
for every soul he claims for
the devil.
He gets enough of them,
one day he'll be rich again.
One look at old Mr. Onselm scared all them
witchy thoughts right out of me.
Got lit off for home, swearing
the whole way to be good again.
I even took that lucky bone,
threw it as far as I could.
Somehow I never could be
rid of it.
I was so scared when I got home,
I just kept right on running.
Guess that's how I wound up in
the army.
I come through it,
without a scratch.
It ain't because I was
born lucky,
smart,
tough...
quite the opposite.
It's got power in it.
Just like that old witch said:
It's got the power to hurt
people.
But I never used it.
Not once.
Like I said, I never wished harm
on anybody my entire life.
But not even them boys over there trying
their damndest to put holes in me.
You think that means
I ain't really a witch?
You hear something?
Ahh!
No.
Ahh! Ma!
Cora.
I'm sorry, Cora.
You can't see me like this, Tom.
Shh, shh.
You just can't.
Hey, it's alright.
Hey, Cora, it's alright.
Shh, Shh.
Enjoying that field work, Joe?
How do you get used to this?
I'm gonna get you by the fire.
Why you done it, Cora? Huh?
I know I was
a shit for brains kid back then,
but you was the smart one.
After you left, I didn't know
what to do.
I had to go up with
Nate Southby.
We married, but he died.
Our babies died.
I was all alone, Tom.
It's alright.
You just gotta rest now, okay?
- You just gotta rest.
- They're coming for me.
They're out there, Tom. They want my soul,
and they gonna have it.
Not while I'm here. Not while
I'm here.
Hey, Shh, shh, shh, shh.
She out there!
She out...
Shh, shh.
Looks like Deadsville to me.
Ohh.
Hey, you're alright.
Who's this now?
This ain't who I come to see.
Well, don't I just like the
look of you.
She never did have much
use for going to church clothes.
There's my Tommy.
She don't look a day older
than the last time I saw her.
The only way to tell how old a
witch is,
you gotta cut her leg
off and count the rings.
You come back to see me, Tommy?
Hell no, I ain't.
You know who I came to see.
Not that pitiful thing
Cora Fisher I hope.
Why, she ain't even much worth tormenting,
but I do it all the same.
How's a girl expected to pass
the time?
I don't know what you ever saw
in that tragic little creature, Tommy.
Why she barely got any soul
to steal.
You keep her name out of your
mouth, you wicked old whore!
I'm just playing.
You 'member how I like to
play, Tom?
Don't you?
I know why you're here.
And he knows it, too.
He got,
let's just call it
un-finished business with you.
I know.
I aim to finish it.
Ahh!
- Jesus
- Hey!
Still a wild hare with
more spunk than sense, ain't ya?
Hey that's enough of that.
You tell your master if he wants
to get to these poor folks,
he's gonna have to go
through me.
You? Ha. Mister
he ain't a tiny bit afraid
of you.
And Tommy,
I near forgot.
He asked me to give you a
present.
No!
'fraid he don't look like much.
I've been riding him pretty hard
every night since you left.
Guess he pretty near wore out.
Curse you, Effie Kolb!
Curse you!
This can't be real.
Radioactive, man.
Oh,
Oh, no.
No.
What'd they do to you,
Daddy? What?
Daddy. Shh, shh, shh. Hey.
Tommy.
That's you, boy?
You, you come home.
You.
Come...
I'm sorry, Daddy. I...
Cora?
Is Reverend Watts still in that little church
up on the side of the mountain?
He is, but you can't go up
there, Tom.
You heard Effie Kolb,
Crooked Man's waiting on ya.
Maybe he is...
Maybe that's why I came back.
Thought I'd have it out
with that old devil.
Not before I get this
sinner buried in church ground.
Oh, my God, Cora!
Oh!
Oh.
- You didn't want me to squash?
- No,
squashing's good.
Totally approve of that.
♪ Did you ever really
love me? ♪
♪ Did you ever really care?
♪ Did you ever really
miss me? ♪
♪ Kiss me,
♪ I wonder if your heart
was ever there ♪
What?
Nothing. Shh...
Hey, try to get some Z's, okay?
Yeah right.
♪ Or did you really
tell a lie ♪
♪ Did you ever really
♪ ever really care?
♪ ever really love me?
You want me to take him
for a while?
Oh, it's my sins that done it.
He's my burden to carry.
Think of it a little different,
I think sins are
just a part of who we are.
We're born with them
and we'll die with them.
You mean like a Adam and Eve
kind of sin?
I mean sins you can't shake.
Saw 'em off,
and they just grow back.
I'm speaking metaphorically,
of course.
Friendly folks around here.
Salt of the damn earth.
Maybe you can
help me with something, Cora.
I'll try.
I've been studying spells.
What makes them tick?
It's more than
just the words, right? I mean,
an incantation on its own does
nothing.
Well, in my case, I sold
my mortal soul off to the Devil.
So that probably helps
grease the wheels some.
Right.
Besides that?
Needs to touch your heart.
When I do a hex,
I think of the saddest
thing I can.
That seems to make
the magic come on stronger.
Ain't none of my business,
ma'am,
have you been trying to do
witch magic?
It's just research.
You want to be real careful
with that.
Coal mining country.
Yeah,
whole territory's snake full of
tunnels.
If these woods are alive,
tunnels are like
veins underneath the skin.
Ohh.
What is it?
Nothing.
Cora? Cora?
Cora?
Cora!?
- Cora?
Cora!
That's interesting.
Ahh!
Arg!
Fuck.
Am I dead?
Maybe.
Well,
that's all right.
Everybody knows the devil can't
set foot in no church.
What the hell is this place?
I think you know.
It's your mama, ain't it?
That's news to me.
I've never seen her face.
Yeah, I guess that's her.
She tried to get out
of paying for all them sins.
Now she'll have no rest from
tormenting.
She ain't slept a wink for more
days than I know how to count.
Sins?
They couldn't have been
that bad,
right?
They were many. Consorted
with demons,
flew upon the black goat and
gave herself for the Sabbat,
changed her shape into that of
varmints,
and things unnameable.
He's here.
Wow.
That's a big fucking bird.
Beast takes many forms,
this be but one.
Sweet
Sarah.
What the fuck?
Please.
Mercy.
If you will forgive me,
let me go up to God.
To God?
No. This is where you belong.
My Lord.
My master.
What more can I give thee?
So much more.
Can you not feel
the new life growing inside you?
It can't be possible?
A dark thing.
Malignant.
It can't be for I am dead.
You sang out to the deep
of night,
and the night things answered.
Now you will give the
world a gift.
A gift.
A son.
A beautiful son.
Ow.
Woah, easy there, easy.
I'm fine.
Oh shit, my head feels
like Minnie Minoso took a swing at it.
Ahh.
He brought you back.
Cora. Cora!
Cora!
Cora.
I used it.
I used the lucky bone.
If I wasn't a witch before...
I surely am now.
There you go, Daddy.
It's consecrated ground.
Let's get you inside, you
old sinner.
Reverend.
That you? Tom Ferrell?
How'd you know, Reverend?
She told me.
She?
There's a girl here.
Come in a couple of minutes
before you fellas. Bold as brass.
You don't see her?
Well,
maybe she a ghost.
Is it Cora Fisher?
Cora Fisher?
Yep.
Remember her when she was just a
little tadpole.
Devil might have got a body,
but he didn't get her soul.
It's y'daddy, ain't it?
Figured he ought to be
buried in proper church ground.
So he shall.
All right, Daddy.
But I think you got another purpose
for being up here on the Hurricane, don't you?
Yes, sir.
We, uh,
we aim to go up that hill.
You're going to his house?
Now, why would any damn fool
want to do a thing like that for?
My daddy's dead.
Cora
You're dead.
I'm sorry, girl.
Maybe all that's left to do is
surrender myself to him.
Tell him, take my body,
take my soul,
take your goddamn penny.
Just so long as there's no
more killing on my conscience.
After all, a deal's a deal,
ain't it?
That's ridiculous.
You were just a kid.
A deal with a demonic entity?
How can that possibly
be binding?
- Oh, it be binding.
- Hellboy.
Yeah, it's kind of binding.
Look, there may be some
wiggle room.
It's what I'm here for.
To renegotiate.
Negotiate, my ass.
Well, he do seem like a pretty persuasive fella,
Reverend, don't he?
Men's pride and folly, all
that is.
Well, if you're gonna go, best do it
when the sun's up in the sky.
His power's strongest when
it's dark.
Y'all stay here tonight.
We got to boogie-woogie, preach.
Looks like we still
have some daylight left.
You sure about that?
That, that's, no,
wait, that's not possible.
no, the Earth, the Earth doesn't spin.
It, it, that's not how it works.
We on his time up in the
Hurricane.
We've got company.
A lot of witches around
these parts.
Always have been.
Used to be plenty of regular
folks, too.
Nowadays, mostly just witches.
Haha! Hallelujah.
And I will lead the blind
by a way they know not.
And I will make
the darkness light for them.
And the crooked things straight.
Oneiros und Nótt
SchlieBßen Sie ihre Augen
Needs to touch your heart.
When I do a hex.
I think of the saddest
thing I can.
Let not your hearts be troubled.
Them witches. Can't set
foot on this holy ground.
And that black magic.
Ain't no good here.
I guess we'll find out
soon enough.
You doubt the power of
prayers, son?
I just like to have some
excessively high-caliber ammo on hand.
Just in case.
Oh! Sheee. Ha!
Tommy...
Shhh!
I know you can hear me in there.
Ain't you had enough trouble
for one day?
It ain't even really begun.
All your friends in that church
with you,
they all gonna die.
All on your account.
That's why you gotta
come out and face him.
Elvis's ass don't shake
this hard.
Reverend, the coal mines,
do they run under this church?
Oh, they run everywhere.
A coal mine collapsed about 30 years ago.
Last time the ground shook like this.
100 men killed.
Buried alive.
Great place to build a church,
huh, Joe?
Where's Tom?
I don't see what's so
godforsaken funny.
Little Tom Ferrell, come back
to see me.
Bring me my lucky bone.
I come to collect it,
Tom Ferrell.
Yeah and I'm gonna give it
to you.
You gotta make me one promise.
No harm comes
to those good folks in there.
But it was you who put them in
harms way,
not I.
All right, then.
All right.
I don't think so.
See, I don't like this deal.
You want it too bad,
and that makes me not want you
to have it.
Go on inside, Tom.
Go.
Well, ain't you
a pug-ugly son of a bitch?
Pot calling the kettle black
here, but
Jesus H.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
The nympho-broad in the tree
mentioned you weren't afraid of me.
Well guess what?
I'm not afraid of you either.
So why don't you turn around,
take your crooked ass out of here,
and take those dizzy bitches with you.
You had a different aspect
when you watched
your mother burn.
What the hell you say, Gumby?
Be gone from this church,
Mr. Onselm. You be gone now.
You saw how she is.
This sorrowful thing.
She suffers so.
But I have it in
my power to mollify her pain.
Let her feathered soul
take wing.
Really?
You would do that?
Yeah.
Something small in return is
all I ask.
That you twist off the head of
that little Tom Ferrell.
and bring it hither.
We're just
renegotiating.
I'm sure we can see eye to eye.
Why?
You got witch blood in
you, friend.
You're more like me
than you are like them.
Come on, snake, let's rattle.
Ohh!
Help him.
Oh, come on!
Oh! He's kilt. He's kilt
for sure.
Arg! I ain't kilt.
You can't hide in there
forever, Tommy.
Crooked Man gonna wear you
out, boy.
Oh, you shut your cursed mouth.
He gonna heap sorrows on you a hundred times
worse than what you drunken
daddy ever got.
You get out of my skull, you witch!
Witch! Get out of my skull!
Ahh!
Joe,
I need you.
Reverend.
Now we both know,
Reverend, a deal's a deal.
Here's what I'll do.
I'll buy that lucky bone
from you.
Ain't nothing in here
for sale to you, Mr. Onselm.
Do it.
Okay.
Urmm! Ahh!
Come on, Joe, you gotta
pull harder.
- Come on!
- Ahh!
Uhh, I know you got no use for
legal tender, old man.
But what about time?
What do you give for
ten years of it?
What are you doing to me, Satan?
How about
twenty?
Fix up those
eyes of yours while we're at it.
Come on!
No, sir! I come fairly
by my years and my afflictions,
and I don't want nothing else.
Abby Riley done poisoned two husbands.
How'd she get planted in a church yard?
So many sinners
in this consecrated ground.
Flesh rots, but the sin goes on.
Oh shit.
Okay, are you sure you're okay?
Because...
You want to stick your
finger in?
No I do not.
You can't keep bleeding
like this
I'll be fine.
- No, no, you will not be fine
- Bobbie Jo.
Part of the job.
Okay? I can't wait to get my
hands on that Howdy Doody fuck.
Where the hits just keep
on coming.
He looks a little different,
doesn't he?
Mm-hmm.
You always did like them pretty
girls, didn't you, Reverend?
I could feel your eyes on
me giving them Sunday sermons.
You go lay back down, Abigail.
This ain't your world no more.
Kiss me, Father.
Kiss me like you always
wanted to.
Kiss this.
What are you doing?
Callie Hicks, fornicator.
Fornicator!
Abel Jacobs.
Gambler.
Josie Ward.
Philanderer.
Manly Langrishe.
Lying drunk.
Lying drunk!
Nathan Green.
Murderer.
Like ducks at the county fair.
Flora Sue Baker.
Cheatin' whore.
Ada Calder.
Child killer.
They were dead, and buried.
Sins were forgiven.
Forgiven don't mean forgotten.
Wyatt Ferrell.
Drunken old fool.
Ha ha ha.
Agsk
Ugh!
What is this?
No, wait, wait.
Fuck.
Sorry Daddy.
Lord, I can't look on this
no more.
Take my eyes away.
And I don't want no gifts from
the devil.
Thank you, Lord.
Tom Ferrell!
Give me that old cat bone!
I was never gonna use it,
Reverend.
You watch now. I ain't no
perfect man.
None of us is.
I got a shadow in
my heart like anyone else.
But you gonna see that light,
Tom Ferrell.
You gonna let it
blaze bright inside of you.
Just like that light be
blazing in me.
I'm all fired up.
I'm gonna bust that evil
wide open.
I'm gonna squeeze it.
I'm gonna squeeze the
Holy Spirit
into this vile unlucky bone!
I can feel it.
Look at it blaze, Tom Ferrell.
Look at it!
Every grave in this yards
been dug with this shovel.
If it ain't full of God
then nothing is.
Thy rod and thy staff!
They comfort me.
That'll work.
Yep.
He's going home.
Ah-ah. Hellboy, no.
We call this in and come back
with the whole team from the bureau.
Better to finish this.
He's hurt.
He's weak.
Joe, you're done.
Staying back here
with the Reverend.
- No.
- We don't come back,
you keep going down that mountain
and you don't stop until you find a telephone.
Don't ever come back here.
What?
Keep the shovel.
It's been called
that since I can remember.
A long time back a hurricane blew down
a mess of trees on this mountain.
They never grew back.
No one still alive remembers it.
Might have been a thousand years
ago for all I know.
And hell, maybe
it wasn't no hurricane at all.
How's that?
Well,
the Indians say it's always
been bad.
They say there's ghosts and
critters up here older than the flood.
Scarce animals.
Shonokins. Mountain spirits.
Here me out,
I might be just talking
out of my ass here, but
might be looking at a
dimensional rifting.
Lovecraft type scenario.
The old gods forcing their way
into our world type thing.
I don't know nothing about
that, but
it's a queer, bad feeling place,
that's for sure.
Gonna need a new shovel.
Something in these hills.
Something haunted.
Evil.
In the trees.
In the dirt.
Tom said these hills
were like a living thing.
Come again?
He said the old mines were like
its circulatory system.
Its veins running underground.
The Crooked Man, I think,
I think he draws power from it.
You got something
on your mind, girl?
Something I don't like.
Maybe if we disrupt the power
source, we can hurt him.
What?
I'm talking about sabotage.
If this were a war and those tunnels were
supply lines, we'd plant dynamite.
You gonna dynamite that mine?
No.
Maybe something better.
A spell.
Girl,
You outta your mother
fucking mind.
I didn't know if it was real,
or if it was just a story they
tell little chaps to scare them.
You ready?
They told me them stories too.
Could use a woman's touch.
They go down into them mines.
Make me understand
why they built a church
on top of a very
convenient access
to a collapsed coal mine?
Explain it to me
like I'm a little...
a little slow.
Wha-
S'ppose they thought
it was some kind of doorway
'tween this world and the other.
They reckon they'd drop a
church on top.
Consecrate the soil.
Block the doorway.
Maybe not such a swell idea.
Worked all right up until today.
It's dark down there.
Dark as the devil's asshole.
If we're going...
I'm bringing this along.
Maybe it got a bit of holy
left in it.
We?
- No, Reverend, I...
- Down there,
I ain't much more blind than you
is, girl.
I always figured rich folks had
them some real fine soirees.
Mm-hmm.
Real fine.
All right.
Tom!
Bet you wishing your friend
was here.
Yeah, he's not afraid of
anything.
Oh, I know somethin' afraid of:
he afraid to tell you how
he really feels about you.
Tom?
Tom.
Ahh!
Something's coming.
Run, girl!
Hurry up! This way, this way!
And he shall eat the flesh of
your sons,
and the flesh of your daughters
shall he eat.
Destroy them in wrath.
Destroy them
that they may be no more.
Magic ain't like a bullet, girl.
You just can't pull the trigger.
Some things you
can't understand by thinking.
It comes from the spirits, not
the meat!
Ahh!
Oh, crap.
When's the last time you felt
the touch of a woman, Tommy?
Have all these years been so
lonesome?
Did you sit up and dream
about me?
I know it, I bet you never stopped thinking
about the way I touched you.
You got something hard for
me, Tommy?
Yeah, I do.
Ahh!
I know well thou are my son.
Thine eyes,
thine eyes attest to it.
Let's not pretend this
is some beautiful moment.
I don't care about you.
You never gave a damn about me.
Thou should look upon
me and say these things?
I should let you burn!
I gotta get you out of here.
No, my sweet child.
I can't be saved.
This burning be my fate.
For them many sins I done,
all us witches end up the same.
There's only one way to end
this pain.
Destroy me, my son.
No.
No, I can't do that.
You can't ask me to do that.
For thy scorn.
For thy wrath.
Thou were right to hate me.
I hated myself!
Myself!
This goddam monster you made!
Oneiros und Nótt, beruührt die
Gedanken meiner Feinde.
SchlieBßen Sie ihre Augen
und fangen sie bis zum naächsten
Sonnenaufgang in Traäaumen ein.
Oneiros und Nótt, beruührt die Gedanken
chlieBßen Sie ihre Augen
und fangen sie bis zum naächsten
Oneiros und Nótt,
beruührt die Gedanken
Sie ihre Augen...
Let me be as a dream.
Forgotten,
Dust without meaning.
Oneiros und Nótt, beruührt die
Gedanken meiner Feinde.
SchlieBßen Sie ihre Augen
und fangen sie bis zum naächsten
- There's gotta be another way.
- There is none.
Oneiros und Nótt, beruührt die
Gedanken meiner Feinde.
SchlieBßen Sie ihre Augen
und fangen sie bis zum naächsten
Sonnenaufgang in Traäaumen ein.
This agony, I can't bare it
any longer.
- Please!
- No!
Ahh!!
You alright, big fella?
Some kind of booby trap.
A spell.
I almost...
something broke it.
It smells like death,
and bird shit.
Wait here.
Oh crap.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
Please, please, fuck!
Ahhh!
Gah! Ahh!
Ugh.
Egh! Guh!
Oh! Ahh!
Uah!
Better you'd given me that boy's
head when you had the offer.
That's twice you might have
saved your fork-tongued mother.
Well, but you'll be
by her side soon enough,
suckling that black teat
in hell.
You must die in this house
to feed the earth beneath,
to feed these hills,
these ancient stones that
do live.
Hey there, devil,
I got something for you.
That's for Cora Fisher.
You go on and choke on it,
son of a bitch.
Look at this devil,
fools himself into thinking
he's a man.
Your road ends in the dark
like mine.
And this,
witch,
No I ain't.
You'll burn, both of ya.
Like Cora Fisher burns.
Like your witch mother burns.
That's all for you.
It's all souls, ain't it?
Look at it.
You think that one's mine?
I don't know.
Guess you'll find out someday.
Like all of us.
You know what I think, Tom?
I think that
so-called lucky bone of yours,
I think it's just a cat bone.
All this time you
thought it held the power, but
I think the power was in you.
He was afraid of you.
He was right to be.
♪ Oh sinner
you better get ready ♪
♪ The time's a comin'
when the sinner must die ♪
♪ Oh God gave Noah...
Ha, I've woke up to worse.
All of a sudden I'm old.
Tommy...
I don't know how to be old.
I knew I held on to
this old bridle for a reason.
♪ singing Halleluya,
sinner you bet get ready ♪
♪ The time's a comin'
when the sinner must die ♪
All us witches end up the same.
Joe.
Joe!
Arrgh!
Bobbie Jo,
Hey, wake up. Joe, wake up!
Come on. Come on.
Get up.
You went inside the tunnels.
Unbelievable.
You're supposed to be the
smart one.
Yeah, you're telling me.
Oh, look...
I got the cargo back.
Nice field work, right?
Besides, I wasn't down there
by myself.
I was with the Reverend the
whole time.
Never would have
gotten out of there without him.
I can't wait for the 60s.
60s, yeah?
This ain't my decade, Bobbie Jo.
I feel good times are coming.
I think so, too.
I ain't gonna miss this
place much.
Me neither.
Can't wait to get
home and just document all this.
That Tom Ferrell's not a
bad egg.
Lucky you came along when
you did.
He just needed a little push,
that's all.
Hey!
Not afraid of anything, are
you, big guy?
Yeah, well, there's an upside to
looking like this, Joe.
You see this face in the mirror long enough
the monsters don't look too bad.
Yeah, yeah.
I know something you're afraid
of, though.
There you are.
♪ Trouble in mind,
♪ I'm blue, yeah ♪
♪ I won't be blue always,
Bob will ♪
♪ Cause that sun
is gonna shine ♪
♪ in my back door someday ♪
♪ Hope soon and aha boy
♪ Trouble in mind is blue ♪
♪ I just see me blockade June ♪
♪ When you see me laughin'
♪ I'm laughin' just to keep
from cryin' ♪
♪ Gotta let me ♪
♪ Trouble in mind, I'm blue
♪ And I won't be blue
all way, why? ♪
♪ Because sun's gonna shine
in my back door some day ♪
♪ Going down to the river
♪ And I'm going to take
my rockin' chair ♪
♪ What you gonna do?
♪ And if the blues take me
I'm gonna rock away from here ♪