Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Homage to the Incomparably Blessed One,
the Worthy Undefiled One,
the Perfectly Self-Awakened One.
Homage to the Incomparably Blessed One,
the Worthy Undefiled One,
the Perfectly Self-Awakened One.
Homage to the Incomparably Blessed One,
the Worthy Undefiled One,
the Perfectly Self-Awakened One.
Mom, who are you praying to?
Do you know the person in there?
I'm praying to sacred beings.
I want to stay
in a single burial plot like this.
I doubt they'd grant your wish.
It's a million per plot.
Mom!
Are you ready to go?
Their real family is here.
Yes, just a second.
Come on, Mom.
You can stay in a shared plot like this.
Close to your mom and dad.
It's cozy and inexpensive.
Mom, don't listen to her.
I'll buy it for you.
It's easy to get a million now.
Get away from me.
Your breath smells like cigarettes.
Try returning the money I lent you first.
How many hundred thousand
do you already owe me, Soei?
I don't know. I don't remember.
I only remember good things.
What selective memory.
Hey! How dare you cross over it? And you!
How many decades
have you been coming here?
The duck and chicken butts
are all facing my parent's faces.
How about this then?
M.
Come and help.
I already helped put the mat down, Mom.
Come on.
How dare you!
The ceremony hasn't started yet.
We're here for the Tomb Sweeping Day,
but all I've seen you do
is play your games.
Come on, Grandma.
At least I came.
Look at Uncle Kiang's family.
I see. Yes.
- See, I told you. Everyone came.
- All right.
Is it hot?
It's not hot.
Haven't you gotten ready?
Then I'll light an incense stick
for you, okay?
Mom. Here she is.
- That's it--
- Just once a year,
we come to pay respects.
Your wife and daughter
have never shown up.
Hold on.
Go scatter them up there.
Look at your face.
GRANDPARENTS
ZHENG YAFANG, ZHOU QINXING
Gosh. Look at the job you've done.
Can't you do it nicely?
- It doesn't change anything.
- See?
My great-grandparents
have risen to the clouds.
You really are a qi chou.
What?
- "A good-for-nothing."
- Yes.
Mom, come down. You'll fall over.
The wind will scatter them when it blows.
You're stubborn, you know?
Come on down.
She's looking for trouble.
Mom!
Mom, come down now.
- Hey, Mom!
- Mom!
The patient's family,
please fill out the form.
Sure.
See you, Mom.
Sew, go in and fill out the forms.
Hey, guys.
I've got to go and pick up Rainbow.
Who can stay?
I'll leave some money with you.
My motorbike is at your house, Kiang.
I'll have to go and get my ride first
then come back to stay with Mom.
Are you crazy?
Kiang's house is out in the sticks.
Don't bother running around.
I can look after her.
- Really?
- Yes.
Take this.
M.
Uncle Kiang,
are you going to pass the MRT?
Yes.
Can I get a ride with you?
Okay. Here.
- Let's go.
- See you.
I'll leave it to you then.
This place is filled
with talismans, everyone.
Hold up, a ghost!
There's a ghost, guys.
Take that!
- Wait, where did it go?
- Are there only four viewers?
Mom, your voice is picked up
by the microphone.
Mom, come sit and rest first.
You've been standing all day.
Have you read my text yet?
You want a new computer for your games
and you want my card details.
Why don't you use your own card?
They're going to cut off my card.
So let it get suspended.
If your internet gets cut off again,
I won't pay for it.
I don't understand.
When you dropped out to be a game caster,
what did you tell me again?
You'd make truckloads of money.
You'd rent your own apartment.
You'd also give me an allowance.
I want to retire when I'm 60.
I know.
Don't rub salt into the wound.
Geez.
When Grandma fell over
on Tomb Sweeping Day,
she told the doctor she had stomachaches
and found blood in her stool.
So they did an exam of her intestines.
The results came out this morning.
Grandma has cancer.
It's in the final stage.
- The doctor said she has a year left.
- Dead!
Man, I told them to pray first.
Damn it.
Anyway, find time to go visit her.
But don't tell her about the cancer.
I don't want her to stress out about it.
Would you hire me to go then?
My time is money.
Goodness.
MUIII: THE TELEVISION IS ACTING UP AGAIN
WHEN YOU HAVE TIME,
CAN YOU COME TAKE A LOOK FOR GRANDPA?
You have to keep updating the application
or it will keep on freezing up.
What?
He said you've lost a lot of weight.
You need to eat more.
He only made random sounds
and you know what he said?
Actually, I made it up.
He's probably telling you
not to block the TV.
Hey.
Grandpa!
You're still kicking it.
Your diaper is heavy.
I'll change it for you.
I'm lowering the bed.
You're like every grandparent's dream,
to have a grandchild
who studied to be a nurse.
Is that true, Grandpa?
Who do you love the most?
Come on, Grandpa!
You're hurting my feelings.
You're going to be sleeping alone tonight.
Don't you ever think
about doing something else?
When do you have time for yourself?
Grandpa once told me
to go find some easy,
high-paying work to do.
So why don't you?
That's what I'm doing right now.
Here's a pure silver belt.
You can get over 10,000 for it.
Thank you.
Your dad is not around anymore.
So Grandpa left it to you instead.
Thank you so much.
I'll take care of it for you.
You might go off and sell it.
Mom.
Grandpa was one smart cookie.
He had already divided the inheritance.
He was just waiting for his death
to reveal everything.
Leaving a headache
for those left behind like me.
Did Grandpa leave anything else to me?
There isn't anything left.
He left his house to Mui.
All your dad's siblings
got only a bit of money.
Attention. The train
approaching Talat Phlu station
departed from Mahachai station…
Grandma.
HOW TO MAKE MILLIONS
BEFORE GRANDMA DIES
It's so damn ancient.
VINTAGE STYLE SHOP HOUSE
IN TALAT PHLU AREA
NEAR GREAT FOOD,
CONVENIENT TO TRAVEL TO,
AND NEAR MRT STATION
CONTACT: M. THANAPAT
Who's that out in front?
Grandma.
It's me, M.
I'm kind of free, so I dropped by.
I miss you.
Kiang and Soei also came
to visit just the other day.
Really?
What's with all the visits from you all?
I'm here to see how your leg is.
Aren't you happy
your grandson came to visit?
Sure.
What are you doing?
Have you eaten yet?
Here. I've bought some noodles for you.
Let's have them together.
It's not time for my meal yet.
What kind of noodles did you get?
From that famous beef noodles place.
I remember
that you like to eat offal, right?
There are tendons,
liver, flat iron steak, and tripe.
See? It's really tender.
Let's eat together.
I pray to the goddess Guanyin.
I don't eat beef!
Then what are you going to eat?
Is this some kind
of Michelin-star fried fish?
Do you want fried fish?
It's freshly fried.
Fried fish?
- It's freshly fried and quite large.
- One, two, three, four, five, six…
Fried fish?
Fried fish? Which one would you like?
My goodness, the fried fish
from the guy's shop looks tasty.
Why are you back so fast?
Was the queue for his shop short?
He used two woks, Grandma.
It's a busy day for him.
I've been buying from him for 40 years.
Do you think you can trick me?
The fish from other shops
absorb a lot of oil.
I'm not eating it.
If you're already eating fried foods,
you don't have to worry about your health.
That guy's fried fish is here.
It's piping hot.
Gosh.
I'm already full.
What did you eat?
I had the fish you bought me.
Are you boiling water for yourself?
I'm making tea to offer the gods.
Let me take care of it for you.
Did the water finish boiling already?
Of course.
Why didn't I hear the kettle whistle?
I microwaved the water.
Reckless boy!
- Gosh!
- What?
Take it down right now!
- Why? Can't you use it? It's--
- Because you can't!
- It's faster and saves gas as well.
- Take it down.
You can't use it.
Yes, you can.
It's tea all the same, Grandma.
The gods won't say anything
about the water being boiled or not.
If you do things just to get them done,
don't do them at all.
I'll come tomorrow
to boil the water for you, okay?
Just leave.
Two kettles tomorrow.
You don't have to come at all.
You usually never come anyway.
Watch where you walk.
Okay, here.
I'm not sure if Ms. Mui meant to leave it.
It'd be a waste to throw it away.
Why are you so stubborn?
I told you that I meant
to throw away those things.
Yet you still brought them to me.
If you're here to ask for money
like the other relatives,
I don't have any.
No, it's not like that.
I…
I think you took great care of Grandpa.
The person who took care of him
should get the inheritance.
Here, I'll carry it for you.
I'm here to talk to you
about that easy
and high-paying work
that you did.
I want to save the money
from selling Grandpa's house.
So I'm renting a monthly hotel room.
There's breakfast
and housekeeping.
If I get bored, I can just move out.
Are you working as a nurse now?
At which hospital?
That's what I wear
for my OnlyFans account.
Those costumes can fetch a higher fee.
Do you want to subscribe?
It's fine.
What are you embarrassed about?
We've even kissed before.
When we were kids,
when both our parents
used to play cards at Grandpa's,
we used to play house, remember?
I was the mom and you were the dad.
We hugged under the blanket.
Yes,
I remember now, all right?
Why do you want to look
after your grandma?
I want to be able to live on my own.
I don't have
the same head start as others.
Some people are born rich.
They have a family business to continue.
So do you think of Grandma as an asset?
That hurts.
Is what we're doing…
wrong?
You know,
I really hate Grandpa's kids.
BOONYANUCH GARDEN
They dropped by for a visit
once a week for just 15 minutes.
Why bother to come at all?
M.
Yes?
We don't intend to make them sad.
We're giving them happiness.
How did you get to be Grandpa's number one
despite being a granddaughter?
Do you know
what old people really want,
but will never receive
from their offspring?
It's time, M.
But I was already with her all day.
When you visited Grandma,
did you smell something strange?
Well, old people smell.
That means you haven't been
with her long enough.
You have to stay with her
until you don't notice it.
I was even unfazed by Grandpa's piss.
Gosh!
I'll bring you back when I get the money.
What has gotten into you?
Why are you staying at Grandma's?
Didn't you want me to go there anyway?
How did you get in?
Mom gave me the keys.
What's with all the stuff?
Some of it is mine and some I bought.
This is for you, Grandma.
I got the money
from selling things online.
What's the real reason
you all keep coming here?
If I'm fine,
you guys don't need to come!
That day Mom took you to the doctor's,
he found…
that you have cancer.
But Mom and the uncles
don't want you to know.
Is it severe?
Stage four.
The doctor said you have a year.
But you don't need
to listen to him, you know?
Those doctors like to pretend
they know everything.
Do you remember Auntie Yen
from down the block?
Her doctor said she had half a year.
It's been 10 years already.
She's still running around
her five-story house.
When I was a kid and lived here,
you took care of me for many years.
It's now my turn to take care of you.
From now on,
I want to spend my time with you, Grandma.
This money is for the utilities then.
I'll help you sell congee tomorrow.
What time do you leave?
Five in the morning.
- What?
- Five in the morning!
Why so early?
Do you expect to sell congee
late in the day?
People eat congee at night too.
Congee can be eaten all day.
Haven't you ever heard?
The early bird gets the worm.
And haven't you ever heard?
The worm that wakes up early
will be gobbled up first.
The worm that woke up late survives.
Throwing scowls, are you?
Why didn't you wake me up?
Well, I'm not an alarm clock.
You do the next bag.
Fine.
- Do you know what you're doing?
- Just wait.
You can give me the cash
to deposit in the ATM,
so you don't have to walk to the bank.
Stop meddling.
I always take this walk every month.
Isn't it good
if you don't have to go this month?
Ngek.
Who?
My friend.
Here.
Ngek, how are you?
Did they let you come back already?
- Just yesterday.
- I see.
The doctor said I was taking up the bed.
I've been hit as well.
Where?
Intestines.
What stage?
Four.
Same.
Well,
you have my support.
But at least you have your grandson
to take care of you.
I'm jealous.
See?
Everyone is envious of you.
SIAM SAVINGS BANK
Stay out here!
You'll use my bank details behind my back.
I'm your grandson, not some thief.
- Have you watched too much news?
- Whatever. Stay right there.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Do you think I'm some kind of scammer?
Thank you.
- Are you making your usual deposit today?
- Yes.
Mom, this is bad.
The fridge smells like a garbage can.
You should throw away
all the expired stuff.
It's not expired. I can still eat it.
You eat this every day.
That's why you got stomachaches.
Even if you throw it away,
I'll dig it back up.
You girls are bickering
so early in the morning.
Why are you sleeping downstairs,
not upstairs?
Grandma locks her room.
She won't let me sleep with her.
Why are you dressed up so fancy, Grandma?
Fancy?
Yes.
Why didn't you button the last one?
Are you going for sexy?
Stop it. No need.
It's too tight. I don't like it!
Of course it's tight.
Why are you bothering me?
Did you steal Rainbow's shoes?
Aren't they too tight?
They fit well.
- A perfect fit?
- Yes.
- Is this a perfect fit?
- Why?
Why are you bothering me?
You understand
what "perfect fit" means, right?
They're my feet.
If I can wear them, then that's fine.
What about your shoes?
Perfect as well.
So why are you dressed up so nicely?
Well, today is Sunday.
Everyone comes.
You're the only one
who has never come over.
This chicken is
from the famous Montien Hotel, Mother.
The one where all the VIPs eat.
You know, Rainbow,
we used to raise a pet chicken downstairs.
- Do you like them?
- I like baby chicks.
- Small chicks are cute.
- Right?
Your aunt, your dad, and I
used to play with the chicken all day.
Until one Chinese New Year,
Grandma chopped the chicken.
She chopped it
and steamed it for us to eat.
Who could eat it, right?
So we had to give it to the dogs.
You've got quite a memory.
- Right, Sew?
- Do you remember Kiang would cry
until he blew a snot bubble?
- Right?
- Hey!
Can you guys stop
telling stupid stories to my girl?
Come on, Kiang. It's nothing.
They call it passing down knowledge.
Hey.
When we're done eating,
let's play some cards.
We're all here.
Well, you're planning to take money
from your kids, right?
Go open up the safe.
I'm going to win all your money.
I'd like to see you try.
Bring it on!
Mom, my family can't stay though.
I have to drop Rainbow off
at her English class.
Hey, come on.
She won't be late
if you play a game or two.
- Right, Kiang.
- There's no time.
There's traffic as well.
Soei, you too.
You shouldn't be playing cards with Mom.
- Why not?
- You should let her rest.
- Mom, do you still have stomachaches?
- Right.
Does it hurt anywhere?
I already know about the cancer.
What?
M told me.
Well, it's Grandma's body.
I think she has the right to know.
I'll go see the doctor on my own.
I won't bother you guys.
It's not like that.
At first, I wanted you to get treated.
But they didn't agree.
What?
Why are you making yourself look good?
You didn't even come
and you didn't pay for anything.
Right, you're bringing up money again.
I don't have any. If I did, I would pay.
It's because you don't work.
I do. I've got jobs here and there.
- Business is slow.
- You don't have to yell.
- I work.
- You aren't any better, Kiang.
- I come when I can.
- You're not free.
Don't I work as well?
Are you saying Soei and I don't work?
Yes.
When I grow up,
I'll study to be a doctor
so I can heal you.
It's fine, Mom.
My friend knows a doctor
who treats a lot of hotshots.
I'll pay for the treatments myself.
You will get better.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
I'll take you to the hospital myself.
There's no need to…
It's my duty, Mom.
Mom.
Mom, I just took a dump
and noticed the floor was really slippery.
I'll install a handrail
for you to hold onto. Okay?
Thank you, all of you.
Come on. No need to be dramatic.
You'll be fine.
Don't you have a shift
at the supermarket today?
No.
I already changed to the night shift.
So I can take Grandma
to chemotherapy treatments during the day.
I can't take five to six days off.
Are you expecting anything?
Expecting what?
My mom is sick.
Don't you think I should look after her?
Otherwise, people might say
I'm an ungrateful child.
I'm coming here only this one time.
I'm not coming back again.
Don't you remember what the doctor said?
He told you to exercise often.
I can walk on my own.
See? You had to take a day off from work.
They'll fire you.
Don't worry, Grandma.
Mom changed to the night shift already.
So she can take you to the doctor.
I see.
Have you already changed your shift?
What time do you get off work?
What time?
In the morning, Grandma.
She works at night.
I see!
Does that mean you haven't slept yet?
I'm getting out.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Why would you get out now?
Can't you let me do
something nice for you?
Every time you want to do
something nice for me,
it always causes me trouble.
When you quit school
to help me sell congee…
What did I do wrong?
I didn't want to lie around useless
like Kiang and Soei
and let you break your back
- selling congee every day.
- How did that turn out?
Look at you breaking your back
working harder than me now.
If it were Kiang bringing you here,
you'd be fine with it?
Sure! I'll tell him for you.
But who knows if he'll be free to do so.
Grandma is crying in the restroom.
That's impossible.
She never shed a tear for me.
True.
You're always the one who sheds tears.
The more you fight,
the more she gets stressed out.
Let me take Grandma to her chemotherapy.
Just think of me as your representative.
- Have you turned off the lights already?
- Yes, I have.
- Both downstairs and upstairs?
- Yes.
Mui.
Grandma, this is Mui.
My cousin.
Grandma, have you eaten yet?
I have.
Where are you going, Grandma?
I'm going to see the doctor.
I'm going to drive you there.
Thank you.
Do you speak Teochew?
Hey!
You owe me one, okay?
Yes.
M, leave your shoes to reserve a spot.
They'll be taking patients at eight.
We even woke up at four.
Let's find a place to sit, Grandma.
Wait for me here.
I'll go get a wheelchair for you.
Next time, go in and sit with her.
This is when you can rake up your score.
It's burning hot inside, like I'm on fire.
Go put the money away.
- In the cabinet.
- Sure.
Wait, Grandma. I'll help you up.
No. No way.
When you were a kid,
you asked me to hold your hand.
But your eyes were glued
to the television.
I fell down the stairs because of you.
I don't remember it.
- I'd rather climb the stairs on my own.
- Come on.
Stretch out both of your arms.
Mui said when I help you up the stairs,
I should stand above you
so you won't fall over.
Are you sure?
Yes. Come on.
- Give me your hands.
- If I fall down again…
Be careful. Slowly.
Get some rest.
Is this Uncle Soei?
Yes.
Hilarious.
Grandma.
You and Grandpa were quite the cool kids
back in the day.
When you were a kid,
you were afraid of ghosts.
You'd sleep between me
and Grandpa every night.
Me? Afraid of ghosts?
I had to sing a lullaby
to get you to sleep.
Nonsense.
It's good you're not afraid anymore.
Because Grandpa likes to walk around
downstairs every night.
If you see him,
don't say anything.
Shit!
I thought you said you weren't afraid.
What are you doing in the dark?
I'm praying.
I dreamt of my parents.
They came to take me to stay with them.
M…
I'm about to die, aren't I?
Come on, Grandma.
You've prayed to the goddess.
You haven't eaten beef for decades.
How many cows were saved because of you?
You're not going to die that easily.
Trust me.
Well, I'm going back to bed then.
- Hey, no need.
- You sleep…
You sleep here.
There's no need to tire yourself.
Let's go inside the mosquito net together.
Do you mind sharing the space?
Scoot over, will you?
I "zoi sia" you.
Are you cursing me?
I said, "Thank you."
How are you Chinese?
You can't understand a single word.
I'm a Thai-speaking Chinese.
A Chinese-Thai.
- Whatever, I'm going to sleep now.
- All right.
Goodnight.
Grandma, lullaby, please.
Keep doing this whenever you're free.
- Sure thing. You'll be out of a job.
- You're not doing it tight enough.
If it's too tight,
the vinegar will suffocate.
The counter is open.
Grandma, come on. Let's go.
Grandma, are you ready?
Just a second.
Grandma.
What's wrong?
- Gosh.
- Hold on, stop.
Wait.
My goodness.
Let's not go sell congee today.
Let's go upstairs. I'll give you a bath.
I can go sell it.
Come on, let me give you a sponge bath.
Be careful. Take it slow.
I'll help you.
One, two, three.
Come.
All right. Arms.
Wipe underneath as well.
Wait! Hold up! What are you doing?
Wipe my body as well. I'm all sticky.
I'm old, you know. I'm not embarrassed.
Give me one second. I've never done this.
Let me prepare myself first.
My goodness.
What are you sighing about?
Shit!
What's wrong with you?
Was that bump your nipple?
Are you crazy?
It's my mole!
Whose boobs would sag
all the way down there?
How would I know?
My boobs aren't that saggy.
What's with the camera?
To watch things.
Watch what?
To watch you, Grandma.
If you faint, I can help you in time.
If you turn into Sleeping Beauty,
it'll be hard
to find a prince to kiss you.
Are you cursing me?
I'm not.
Here, check it out.
Hey!
How could you move the goddess?
- Why?
- You can't!
Move her back right now.
Do it now.
How could you, M?
- Done.
- No! Do it again.
Do it nicely.
Use both of your hands.
Move her carefully.
Done. Right back in the same spot.
It's as if she was never moved.
GUANYIN
All right, done.
It's easy. Sit and walk easily.
Done?
Mom, move away.
You hate the smell of cigarettes.
Why are you hanging around here?
Mom.
The pomegranate is looking nice.
Let me have it.
Leave it alone.
I want it. I don't care.
It's not yours!
What? Gosh.
Soei!
- Why are you so protective of them?
- Because they aren't yours.
- What?
- You're keeping it for your favorite son,
Mr. Kiang, right?
What's there to eat?
Go take a look.
Hey, M.
Did you know?
Grandma used to call Kiang's wife a dud.
A dud? What do you mean?
You…
Didn't you go to school?
What did you learn there?
A dud is what you call
something that's blemished.
No one wants it.
- Really?
- Yes.
When Pinn was able to latch on to Kiang,
Kiang changed into
a totally different person, you know?
He became posher.
Stretching his neck.
Sending his kid
to an international school.
- Did you know?
- Soei.
- He took out a loan--
- When you drink,
- you have no filter.
- What?
What? I haven't finished gossiping yet.
She's protective of her son.
All right, I won't say another word.
You know, my motto is
"live within your means."
Unlike him. No matter how much
he has, it's not enough.
- That's enough.
- He should give to those in need instead.
Don't you agree?
Anyway, do you have a thousand on you now?
No!
- Where is it?
- I don't have it.
- If I find it, I'll take it.
- No.
- Just one thousand.
- One thousand.
- I don't have any!
- I'm going to keep on kissing you.
- Gosh!
When it comes to Soei,
it's best if he doesn't come.
Why?
If he doesn't come,
it means he's doing fine.
That's how it is, M.
They're her kids, we're the grandkids.
They've been loved
long before you came along.
So can you rank yourself?
Who does Grandma love the most right now?
Number one goes to
either Uncle Kiang or Uncle Soei.
One plays the stock market,
while the other plays around.
As for me,
I've probably moved up over my mom.
Being number three
doesn't get you anything.
Back then, how did you know
you were already number one?
- Did Grandpa tell you?
- Old people won't tell you directly.
You can feel it.
Feel it?
I can't feel anything at all.
I can only feel words cutting at me.
Every single day.
It was probably when Grandpa
told the other relatives about me.
How I took good care of him.
I guess.
We're almost there, Mom.
It's a bit far, but the air is better.
I'm sorry for never bringing you here.
Welcome home, Grandma.
Hello, Mother.
Show Grandma the picture you drew, honey.
Come on.
Grandma, do you like it?
I do.
It's pretty.
Mom, have you seen the bed?
Rainbow chose the pillows
and blanket herself.
The television is connected
to the internet.
You can watch Chinese operas all day.
But I have to take care of my place.
Come on, Mom.
That house is really old.
Living here is much more convenient.
There are restaurants,
a hair and nail salon.
There's also a senior citizen club.
They do tai chi every day.
But Grandma has to do
her chemotherapy, Uncle Kiang.
It's not wise to travel around.
Well, I trade stocks at home,
so I can look after her around the clock.
But how will she sell her congee?
The customers are already complaining
that she has been taking Sundays off.
Actually, I want her
to stop selling congee already.
I have money.
Come stay here.
I'll take her to chemotherapy myself.
But this place is so far away.
Wouldn't she have to wake up
at two in the morning then?
M.
Yes?
I really appreciate you.
Here.
For the time you spent these past months
taking care of Grandma.
It's fine, Uncle Kiang.
I'm not doing it for the money.
Mom.
I've only heard that children
should look after their mom.
How can I let my nephew do it?
Mom.
I want to be your full-time son.
- Have you locked up?
- I have.
Rainbow.
Go ask Grandma if she's enjoying herself.
I want to know if she's having fun.
- Could you?
- Sure.
- Grandma, are you enjoying yourself?
- Of course I am.
- How about you, Rainbow?
- I'm having fun too.
My beautiful granddaughter.
This temple accepts donations
for coffins, Mother.
It's very sacred.
My friend just paid a visit recently
and her condition improved in no time.
Mom, taking the train is good, right?
Just like when we were kids.
It brings back memories of
when you and Dad took us on train trips.
- You were really small then.
- Me?
You.
Did Soei keep running around?
Of course. All three of you did.
May you all be blessed
- for coming out here for a visit…
- Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Mom, are you good to climb up?
- Eleven.
- Uncle, you can go first.
I'll take care of her.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Have you figured out
whether you're going to live
at your place or Uncle's?
Be quiet, will you?
I'm counting the steps.
You're making me forget it all.
Why are you counting?
For the lottery.
Gosh.
Does it hurt?
Come on.
Back in the day,
when Kiang was just a kid,
we came here to pray.
When we were done, his shoes got stolen.
I had to give him my shoes,
so he could walk back home.
That day, the sun was just
as bright as today.
The ground was just as hot as today too.
So was it Uncle Kiang
who bought you these shoes?
See?
All right.
- Come.
- So?
"May I, Mrs. Mengju Saejiew…"
Mom, I'll go paste the labels
and wait for you outside.
- And?
- "Recover from illness."
- All right.
- That's not all.
Where are you off in a rush to?
What's with the wishes?
"May my oldest son,
daughter,
and youngest son…
be healthy and strong,
be wealthy in money and gold."
Gosh. With all these wishes,
we'll need another label.
Then write smaller.
"And I ask for my grandson…
to have a good job."
Okay.
- I'll go paste it for you.
- All right.
Grandma, look. One.
KIANG: MAY MY WIFE AND DAUGHTER BE HAPPY
Two.
RAINBOW: MAY I STAY
AT THE SAME SCHOOL WITH MY FRIENDS
Three.
PINN: MAY I HAVE WEALTH
No one asked for a wish for you.
I think Uncle Kiang
doesn't really want you to live with him.
He's just sowing the seeds,
hoping to reap them later.
Well, he has a family.
He has to think of his family first.
Are you not his family, Grandma?
MAY I RECOVER FROM ILLNESS
MAY MY OLDEST SON,
DAUGHTER, AND YOUNGEST SON
BE HEALTHY AND STRONG, AND WEALTHY
AND I ASK FOR MY GRANDSON
TO HAVE THE BEST JOB IN THE WORLD
M: MAY GRANDMA WIN THE LOTTERY
Mom.
Get your things ready
for next Sunday, okay?
I'll arrange the car to pick you up.
M.
My feet hurt.
I want to change my shoes.
Try these on first.
How are they?
A bit too loose.
- Loose?
- Yes.
That's good.
This time you'll get the right size.
M.
Yes?
You're also sowing seeds
in hopes of reaping them, aren't you?
I'm
just like Uncle Kiang.
I want to be your full-time grandson.
You're just so full of it.
"You're just so full of it."
If you don't believe me, that's fine.
Which ones do you want to try on next?
Let's try one side each
to see which one you like more.
What are you doing?
Look, aren't you pretty?
You're back
to being your beautiful self, see?
Gosh. You're obsessed
about your looks too, right?
After your treatment ends,
you'll look kind of like this.
What?
Nonsense.
What? Don't you think you look cool?
You do look cool.
You don't have to wake up early
to curl your hair anymore.
Do you like it?
Yes.
All right, get some rest.
Rest up.
Close your eyes.
I want some pork. Give me more pork.
- Do you only want pork?
- The pork belly
and some vegetables too.
- You said you wanted only pork.
- I meant give me a lot of pork!
Fine. A lot of pork.
Watch and learn. Keep stirring.
Later on,
you can sell congee in my place.
I can't wake up at four
in the morning every day, Grandma.
Can I sell late at night?
Don't you forget,
every kind of work
leads to the birth of a winner,
zhuangyuan.
All you need to do is be good at it.
Then you can live comfortably.
Just like those zhuangyuans.
But don't they have to be castrated?
That's eunuchs!
You're messing things up.
I'm going to defeat you.
Try me.
All right.
Bring it on.
Well.
In this round,
will Madam Ju from Talat Phlu
be able to bluff a win with this hand?
Just be quiet, will you?
You're jinxing my cards.
- Let me see.
- No.
Uncle Soei must inherit
his gambler's blood from you.
Well, on the Chinese New Year
and the Ghost Festival,
we didn't know what else to do
after the rituals.
So we'd gather around and play cards.
Are you lonely?
You've lived by yourself for many years.
Lonely? I don't know about that.
This is just how life is.
But I don't like the day
after the Chinese New Year.
The fridge would be bursting
with leftovers.
And I've…
Well…
I've got to eat it all by myself.
Let's play cards.
- Here, my cards
- Okay.
Seven with double deng.
Show yours.
I've got eight with double deng.
What? It's six, not eight.
It's doubled
because I got a pair of eights.
Are you sure you're not being cheated on
when you sell congee?
And I have this extra one.
What?
Just give in. I won.
- Give me.
- What?
Cough up 20 baht from that basket.
What is this?
You can rob even your grandma.
What?
I never complain when you take mine.
All right, another round?
It's good to have you around.
It's fun.
Come on. Let's continue playing.
Sure.
- This time, it's a real game.
- Sure.
Uncle Kiang isn't answering.
He's probably upset you didn't move in.
Uncle Soei turned off his phone.
As for Mom, she said the supermarket
is short-staffed today.
No one is probably coming today, Grandma.
Then put the food away in the cabinet.
Or else the bugs will get to it.
The lid is loose.
Hey! What happened to all my money?
It's all gone.
- M!
- What?
How did it go missing?
It wasn't me.
I didn't take it.
I didn't, seriously.
See?
Not only did he nab the pork floss,
but also the money.
No wonder he went missing.
How much did he take?
Shit!
Damn you!
Have you ever helped Grandma sell congee?
She only earns about 10 to 20 baht a bag.
Just how many bags
does she have to sell to get 200,000?
Do you even have a conscience?
Even Grandma
has never told me off like this.
How much do you owe?
A million?
Or…
Should I just ask Grandma to help out?
Uncle Soei.
What is it?
It's pure silver.
- You should get a good price for it.
- Gosh.
Awesome. Come here.
You're a lifesaver.
Disappear for a longer while this time.
I'm sorry for all this, M.
Take care of Grandma on my behalf.
Uncle Soei
isn't at his apartment, Grandma.
I didn't see his motorbike either.
His neighbors said
he went out of town for work.
Is anyone home?
Who's there?
Is the owner home?
Must be Soei's creditors.
Go hide.
I'll go talk with him.
Ma'am, hello.
You won't find Soei here.
He's ordained as a monk and won't be back.
I'm just the housekeeper here.
I'm not looking for anyone
called Soei, ma'am.
I saw a post listing this house for sale.
When I texted him, no one replied.
I'm not sure what to do.
Thank you, ma'am.
This house isn't for sale.
Here, ma'am.
The name is M. Thanapat.
Is he a broker for someone?
No. I don't know him.
Grandma.
Did he leave yet?
What did you tell the creditor?
That I'm just the housekeeper.
You can pull it off.
Your outfit and all.
Your face too.
Housekeeper, get to work.
Stop sitting around.
I bought a shirt for you.
What for?
For you to wear to work.
Gosh.
The shirt is a bit dated.
After my third treatment,
I'll be cured.
You won't have to take care of me anymore.
Are you kicking me out?
When you were in the first grade,
you used to be at the top of your class.
You can do whatever you want
if you do it yourself.
Okay?
Go find proper work.
I'm a good-for-nothing, Grandma.
I can't compete with the others.
This pomegranate tree
was planted when you were born.
It's just as old as you.
They say if you grow a pomegranate tree,
the child will be healthy.
You once ordered me
not to give them to anyone
if the tree was ever to bear fruit.
I was to keep them only for you.
Here, eat it.
I don't remember.
I apologize for always saying
you're a qi chou.
Just let me leech off of you
for the time being.
I'll leave when you're all better.
Then
can you go somewhere with me tomorrow?
Is this really your older brother's house?
Why wasn't I born into this family?
His house is like a hotel.
Goodness.
- Revive me when I'm in need
- Guide me when I'm lost
- Always be my source of energy
- Warming my heart
- Your heart
- Is like my heart
- Sealing our hearts among the stars
- Pure and bright
The reason why my grandson
and I are here today
is because I've got cancer.
I want to buy a burial plot,
hoping to extend my lifespan.
So I'd like you to help me out.
Perhaps a million, if possible?
When Dad and Mom
gave you the house at Talat Noi,
you got several million when you sold it.
I've never asked you for a single dime.
Well, Dad and Mom gave it to me, right?
Don't you remember?
You were there as well.
But I was the one who wiped their butts.
Why have I never received anything?
Ever since I was a kid,
whatever Dad and Mom got,
they'd always give it to only you.
What about the one
who cared for them like me?
Why didn't I get anything?
What they did was right.
If they gave it to you,
it'd all go to your lousy husband.
But that lousy husband of mine
was arranged by Dad and Mom for me.
If you really want money,
go ask your own offspring then.
Understand?
As for me,
I wouldn't even give you a penny.
M, let's go home.
Leave and don't ever come back.
You and I don't share
the same family name anymore.
- Approaching Tha Phra station.
- Grandma. Let's go.
Please be careful when…
Why do you want
a big burial plot so badly?
I want a good plot of land
so my offspring will be prosperous.
People will see it and think
you guys have filial piety.
What nonsense, Grandma.
That's damn stupid.
Your parents are in small, shoddy plots,
but your brother still got rich.
When people die, they just die.
The brain stops working.
Then the body will either
become part of earth or water.
Who knows where it will be?
You wouldn't even know
what everyone would be up to.
Rich or poor, you wouldn't know.
But if I die
and you scatter the flowers carelessly,
I'll come back to haunt you.
Sure.
Just come.
I hope you come.
On Tomb Sweeping Day,
you won't even know who shows up or not.
Uncle Kiang might hire someone
to do the ritual.
I might go on Google Street View
and pay respect through the screen.
But if I have a beautiful burial plot…
who knows, you all might want to meet up.
Have a seat.
Hello.
After going over the results
of the treatment,
the patient hasn't shown any improvement.
The doctor said you're better.
No need to continue with the chemotherapy.
At first, you said the chemotherapy
will get rid of it.
Have you taken a good look?
From now on, we'll treat you
according to your symptoms.
Don't I need to complete the treatment?
Just like what I said.
You should give the patient
a lot of your time.
- This is the most important thing.
- Calm down.
- It'll be okay.
- The family must stay strong.
You know,
Ngek has gone already,
about a few days ago.
She also didn't complete her chemotherapy.
It's my body.
I have the right to know, don't I?
What did Grandma say?
What does it mean, Mom?
"Rice grains have turned
into cooked rice."
What's done can't be undone.
Dad. Mom.
Come and take me with you.
I'm in so much pain.
Grandpa, Grandma. Where are you?
I want to die.
Sew.
How is Mom feeling?
The doctor will run some more tests.
If there's nothing,
she can go home tomorrow.
Get up.
Sew, come outside and talk with me.
Where's the deed to Mom's place?
Mom isn't even dead yet.
Why the hell are you asking
about it right now?
Someone has to take care of it
in the end, right?
It will be much easier doing it now
than doing it later.
Your wife put you up to this, didn't she?
See?
That's why I don't want
to be a part of this family.
Why do you guys treat Pinn
as if she's not a member of our family?
So where's the deed?
It's in the closet at Mom's place.
Mom.
If Uncle Kiang asks Grandma
to sign anything, don't let her sign it.
Mom.
Are you listening to me?
PATIENT ROOM
Quickly transfer ownership.
Thank you so much, Sew.
Grandma gave Uncle Soei the house.
SPECIAL ROOM
Hold on.
I'll go settle the bill.
Take her over to the taxi queue
and wait there.
M.
PATIENT PICK-UP AND DROP-OFF
Haven't you learned your lesson,
giving money to Uncle Soei?
Well, he can't look out for himself.
You're always like this.
That's why he's a loser.
I thought you said
the caregiver would be rewarded.
I don't have anything else to give.
You don't have to look after me anymore.
Didn't I take good care of you?
You took good care of me.
Very good, actually.
Why won't you ever let me
come first place?
Where's my spot?
Where the hell do you put me?
Give me an answer!
Answer me, Grandma!
You're a fool…
for loving the wrong person.
Die!
Your mom is dead!
Done.
Have you even slept yet?
Mom! The microphone
is picking up your voice.
Hey.
Do you even have viewers
this early in the morning?
Haven't you ever heard?
The early bird gets the worm.
But it has to be a foreign worm.
The person who bought Grandma's house
is going to come in to renovate it.
Go there and help pack things away.
Everything there can be thrown away.
What is it?
You sound exactly like Kiang.
He even said
he's not going to show up
at her funeral if Grandma dies.
Actually, it's good
that you and I didn't get the house.
Being the giver feels much better
than being the receiver.
Are you trying
to cheer yourself up or what?
Didn't you want the house as well?
When did I want it?
If not, why'd you change your shifts
to visit Grandma so often?
Because I miss her.
When you weren't home,
the house was really quiet.
Were you lonely?
I finally understood
how Grandma probably felt
when everyone moved out.
Hi. You can park inside.
I've prepared a room for you, Mui.
- Thank you.
- It's nothing.
Last time, my aunt blacked out.
It turns out that she has a heart disease.
So she wants me to take care of her.
Her only son passed away
several years ago.
Her daughter-in-law and grandkids
moved abroad permanently.
Come help out, M.
I'll take care of her at home.
You can help take her to the hospital.
When it comes to an end,
I'll give you a part of my share.
I thought you'd have gotten it.
Grandma told me
you took good care of her.
Have you ever dreamt of Grandpa?
The day Grandpa passed away…
he choked on his food and then went still.
I knew how to help him.
But I didn't.
He kept telling me…
it's time to let him go.
I guess he has gone to a good place.
That's why he's never come to visit me.
I pay respect
to the benevolent goddess Guanyin.
The respected Guanyin, savior from peril
and beacon of divine inspiration.
I pay respect
to the benevolent goddess Guanyin…
NURSING HOME
Mom, did you know?
Uncle Soei didn't take Grandma
to live with him.
He put her in a nursing home.
I'm going to visit her.
Hello, Grandma.
Hello.
Good morning.
- Visiting family? Welcome.
- Hello. Visiting family?
Hello.
- Hi.
- Visiting family?
Yes.
Mr. Chaiyapon, your nephew is here.
- Yes.
- You can go in.
Grandma just fell asleep.
I've paid off all my debts.
There's some money left over.
You should take it.
Keep it.
Hey, it's okay.
Because from now on,
no one is going to help you out.
Who is it?
It's your qi chou, Grandma.
Have you eaten yet?
Perfect, I wanted to show off my sexiness.
Grandma, come home with me.
I'll make you congee.
Let's go home.
Mom!
Why are you keeping this?
What? You do it too.
What are you doing here?
Go back and lie down.
You shouldn't eat expired stuff like me.
Cancer is genetic.
I know.
Sons inherit the assets.
Daughters inherit cancer.
What are you talking about?
Memory in the making, right?
Go on as you were.
M…
is always badgering me,
asking me
who I love the most.
I don't know either.
But all I know is
that I want to stay with you the most.
- Hello, Auntie Pinn.
- Hello.
Happy Chinese New Year.
You can just say it in Teochew, Rainbow.
Let's go see Grandma.
I'm not sure if you know, Uncle Kiang.
Grandma once told me that
beef was her favorite food.
But when you were a kid,
you were often sick.
So she asked the goddess Guanyin
to look after you
and for you to be strong and healthy.
In return, she'd stop eating beef forever.
Kiang.
Come on out.
You haven't been able to sleep lately.
Grandma.
Your son came to visit you.
Smile.
Grandma.
Uncle Kiang is holding your hand.
Mom, you're very lucky
to have a grandson
taking good care of you.
DAOCHAI FAMILY
Tendons, tripe, and flat iron steak,
braised until they're tender, Grandma.
Did you see the silver belt
that Grandpa gave?
I don't know where I put it.
I can't find it.
Is this some kind of scam?
My Grandma has passed away. I'm sorry.
SIAM SAVINGS BANK
MRS. MENGJU SAEJIEW
FOR MR. THANAPAT THAWARAKUL
When was this account opened?
Why don't I remember it?
All you do is play games.
You walk so slowly.
The bank is going to close.
Grandma, you walk slowly too.
I'm going to open an account.
See?
I'm going to make a deposit for you.
You were able to become the top
of your class.
I'm going to keep putting in a deposit
throughout the year.
Can you keep putting in a deposit
until you die?
I want to have millions.
Gosh. Are you cursing me?
What are you going to do with a million?
I'm going to buy you a new house, Grandma.
Your house is old.
It's crawling over with roaches.
Just talking about it
gives me goosebumps. See?
My goodness, you got the goosebumps?
You're just so full of it.
I'd like to withdraw everything
and close the account.
M.
Knock on the coffin
and tell Grandma the directions.
Grandma.
We're about to leave.
We're passing the congee shop.
Grandma.
We're crossing the bridge.
We've arrived at the house
I bought for you.
Grandma.
You're my first place.
Rainbow.
What are you doing?
Here.
Go scatter the flowers for Grandma.
Soei, why don't you help lay out the food?
- I'm trying to win a 12-million lotto.
- Gosh.
There you go.
Spread them out nicely for Grandma.
Kiang, how old was Mom? She was 78, right?
- Rainbow.
- It's 79 in Chinese count.
Let me help.
Here, do it like this.
I'll show you.
- Watch.
- Nine hundred ninety-seven…
It doesn't matter what number.
You'll never win.
Do you have one ending with 22?
Why would you want that number?
It's going to be 79!
Take a picture!
Okay, do you want to stay here? Fine.
Subtitle translation by: Karina Suvapataya