In the future, humans will have
developed a star gate system,
allowing spacecraft to traverse
vast distances instantaneously
by creating artificial
wormholes and distorting space,
reaching distant extraterrestrial
destinations spanning tens of light-years.
Report to Star Gate Dispatch Station,
orbital data has been
sent, requesting approach.
Airline 0722.
Mrs. Star Seeker.
Mrs. Star Seeker can get closer.
With the frequent use of star gates,
people have started encountering
a highly unlikely occurrence.
If a spacecraft miscalculates
during the journey through a star gate,
it will be trapped in the
distorted space behind the gate,
and this is referred to as the
[Star Abyss]
These spacecraft can be trapped
for several years or even decades,
with no possibility of rescue
and no survivors.
Upon the discovery of the
existence of the Star Abyss,
in order to prevent accidents,
many spacecraft are
equipped with hibernation pods.
[Mrs. Star Seeker]
In case a spacecraft gets trapped,
the crew can enter a hibernation state
until the spacecraft is freed.
But not all spacecraft
allocate expensive hibernation
chambers for each crew member.
Some people may choose to take
chances in an attempt to save money,
thinking they can
overcome the odds and fate.
The Mrs. Star Seeker was
originally just a cargo spacecraft,
but the greedy captain illegally
carried far more passengers
than the approved capacity.
Now, we are trapped in the Star Abyss
with only 4 hibernation pods.
What's even worse is that
we are not the only ones
on the spacecraft.
The monster is catching up again!
Keep running!
Duo, run!
This is an airlock module.
Outside is a vacuum
with no way out.
I'll manually initiate the
depressurization process shortly.
Once that happens, the door
can only be opened from the inside,
and you'll be safe.
What about you then?
Wait until it's quiet outside
before you come out.
Remember, go find Ji Ya.
If you get injured,
it can save your life.
But you're already injured.
Take it. Don't lose it.
This is from your parents.
They will surely protect you.
Go!
You must survive.
Duo,
there's something I need to tell you.
I'm the one who caused the death
of 80,000 people in Sailor Valley,
including your parents.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
[24 hours ago]
[Mrs. Star Seeker, a cargo spacecraft]
[Ji Ya, the navigator of Mrs.
Star Seeker, a cargo spacecraft]
Mrs. Star Seeker.
This is the Star Gate Dispatch Station.
Why hasn't your cargo
manifest been declared?
If you don't report it soon, your
flight authorization will be canceled.
What illegal goods are you smuggling again?
Don't implicate me.
What do you mean "you"?
You think too highly of me.
[The captain of Mrs. Star
Seeker, a cargo spacecraft]
Only the captain knows
what's on board.
[Mrs. Star Seeker]
What are you still sitting there for?
Hurry up and find a solution!
If there's something wrong with the cargo,
you won't get a single penny.
Now you remember me.
We need to have a
serious talk about the bonus.
Ji Ya,
how much longer do we have to wait?
Thirty minutes.
You need to hurry.
Otherwise, our spot will be taken.
Those passengers illegally
carried in the cargo hold
were all arranged by you, right?
Some were looking for a cheap ride,
but others...
Besides,
that cargo container...
You know what I mean.
Of course I know.
Let's talk outside.
The profits need to be split
evenly between us this time.
You ungrateful kid.
I've arranged everything.
I'm well-connected
at the dispatch station.
It's so expensive.
They might as well just rob us.
Stop pretending to be clueless.
Even though it's always you getting
the lion's share, and I get the crumbs,
that's still my money.
You can't deny it.
Don't forget
you're the one who damaged
the seal on the Sailor Valley.
Besides me,
who dares to use a
wanted criminal like you?
You know I was innocent.
Why do you keep bringing
that up? Is it amusing to you?
Go check out a guy
named Xing Tian among
the people in the cargo hold.
Xing Tian?
Which one?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Twins.
Qin,
be sharp
and check what's inside.
Okay.
Twins.
It's me.
It's strange.
There's no reason to spend so much money
transporting an empty cargo container.
What is it?
Captain, save me!
Captain!
Don't leave me behind!
Lu Ming.
Xing Tian.
It's really you.
[Xing Tian, Interstellar Investigation Bureau
special agent, once comrades with Lu Ming.]
You know I was innocent.
Why are you still chasing after me?
I'm just a special agent.
Whether you were innocent
or not is for the law to decide.
So many people died.
If you truly believe you were innocent,
then come back with me
to prove your innocence.
Do you think I wanted to harm them?
I wanted to save them too.
I didn't want to collide.
I'm not here to find you this time.
There's someone more
dangerous on the spacecraft.
You just focus on being a fugitive.
I know.
- [The assassin of the Twins, a cloned assassin wanted by the Interstellar Investigation Bureau, ]
- [planned to sneak into an extraterrestrial colony.]
I warned you earlier,
but you wouldn't listen.
Now, no one can save him.
What was that just now?
A genetically synthesized combat monster.
It is invaluable.
That's illegal.
Nonsense,
or why would I come to you?
It's out of control.
The route has been adjusted now.
I'm not blackmailing you.
You can choose not to eat or drink,
but you can't choose not to breathe.
Don't forget
this is a cargo spacecraft.
The additional oxygen supply for us
has to be bought from the black market.
Hey.
Wasn't it agreed upon earlier?
You can't charge twice.
Then you can get off the ship.
Hey, what's with your attitude?
Are you in cahoots with Xing Tian?
[Chen Mo, the head of the Interstellar
Investigation Bureau's Special Operations Unit, ]
[assisting Xing Tian
in the arrest operation.]
We're not here to arrest you.
I advise you to mind your own business.
Have you traveled through a star gate?
Do you know what will happen?
Don't forget
I call the shots
on this spacecraft.
I know it's the first time for all of
you to travel through the star gate,
so listen carefully.
In order to ensure everyone's
safety during the journey,
if I say the color of coal
is not black but white,
you nod
and don't have your own thoughts,
understood?
Tell Xing Tian
that I am responsible
for everyone's safety.
If he wants to arrest those two women,
don't lay a hand on them on my ship.
Uncle,
are we in trouble?
This is for you.
My parents said
if we're in trouble,
it can help us.
Why do you have this?
Duo,
this is something your
mom and dad left for you.
Don't give it to others.
When a tragedy struck the Sailor Valley,
her parents and family
all died.
I adopted her,
and now I want to take
her to the New World,
hoping that we can start anew there.
You're feeling uneasy inside, aren't you?
Let me remind you,
this feeling
is called a guilty conscience.
Do you know the parents of the little girl?
Have you seen the badge?
Her parents and those who died
were all because of your
collision with the sealing hood.
You owe them for the rest of your life.
The top 10 most wanted list,
first place is the Twins,
with a reward of...
How dare you take on the
job of smuggling these people?
Cut the crap. Let's go.
Collision warning.
It is estimated that
collision time is 120 seconds.
Mrs. Star Seeker,
stop dawdling
and clear the airline quickly.
[The estimated collision point]
[Star Gate Airlines] [Star Gate]
The Enterprise wants to cut in line.
[The estimated collision point]
Lu Ming.
Don't slow down.
We're next.
Warning! Illegal operation!
Ji Ya, turn off the warning.
Don't get me in trouble.
I'll lose my license.
Illegal operation!
Turn off the warning.
Warning! Illegal operation!
Warning...
Switch to manual control.
Lu Ming,
if we lose, we're both done for.
Remember, as long as
it's in the sky, I've never lost.
That's true.
Otherwise, I wouldn't
have taken you in back then.
[Star Map Navigation]
Are you really confident?
Forget about the numbers.
There are only two outcomes for
this kind of thing: success or failure.
I've been flying in the
sky for so many years,
and no one can block my way.
[Enterprise] [Mrs. Star Seeker]
Attention, all passengers.
The spacecraft is about to
enter the Star Gate Airline.
There will be maneuvering
acceleration shortly.
Come on.
Don't be nervous.
Hold on tight.
Take a deep breath.
Mrs. Star Seeker,
if you don't stop the
ship, we're going to collide.
[Enterprise] [Mrs. Star Seeker]
Collision probability is 38%.
It is 42%.
You must decelerate.
How much acceleration can
this old spacecraft withstand?
It's as tough as me.
Stop!
[Star Map Navigation]
Slow down quickly,
the old spacecraft is going to fall apart.
Don't be afraid.
Even though this spacecraft
is older than your grandma,
it can handle it.
You must hold on.
Mrs. Star Seeker,
are you crazy?
If you don't decelerate,
we'll really collide.
Trust me,
that guy doesn't have the courage for this.
[Star Gate Airline] [Star Gate]
We won!
Haha.
We won.
[Mrs. Star Seeker]
We must give it a try.
Below is the protective
cover of the Sailor Valley.
Attention, all passengers.
The spaceship is about
to traverse the star gate,
estimated time for traversal is 20 minutes.
Attention, all passengers.
The spaceship is about
to traverse the star gate.
Grandma, have you
ever traversed a star gate?
No.
The traversal is beginning.
Once through the star gate,
we'll be in the new world.
There, we can start anew.
What exactly did you transport this time
that's worth taking such a big risk?
Some money should be earned,
and some money should not be earned.
Young man,
you just don't understand.
Why do I work hard running ships?
I was born on Earth,
but I never said I want to die on Earth,
you know?
Well,
if you fly five more trips,
you'll have enough money
to change your identity.
By then, you...
What's going on?
Navigation system is offline.
Control system is offline.
Power system is offline.
Artificial intelligence is offline.
[System error]
Life support system is offline.
The central computer has crashed.
Captain!
[System error]
Could it be...
It's impossible.
Star.
Abyss.
During the recent struggle
for the navigation route,
the transit program
couldn't synchronize in time.
The initially set transit
time was 30 minutes,
1,800 seconds.
Now, the transit time
has changed to 220 million seconds.
Calculating it,
we'll be trapped for 7 years.
Seven years?
We won't make it through.
The air and water on the ship
aren't enough for so
many people to last 7 years.
In the cabin, there are 2 smuggled killers.
To survive,
they will surely kill all of us.
Xing Tian and the people he
brought won't just sit idly by.
By then, the cabin will
definitely turn into a battlefield.
Come over here quickly.
Come here.
Duo.
In any case,
we need to take out the Twins first.
They are more dangerous than you think.
Calm down.
Don't go.
Follow me later.
Okay.
This is a cargo ship,
standardly designed to
accommodate only 4 people.
The maximum limit
is just 1 year.
Right now, we have 21 people on board,
which means,
we can last two months
at most.
If it really comes to that point,
I only ask you for one thing,
let me die quickly and painlessly.
I just have bad luck,
I accept my fate.
But there's still a little girl
on the spacecraft, she...
To survive,
we still have a way.
We still have 4 hibernation pods.
[Mrs. Star Seeker
Spaceship Hibernation Pods]
Who is the extra one for?
No matter how you calculate it,
only 4 of us can survive.
So, we need to take action first.
I'll deal with the
people in the cargo hold.
You deal with the 2 women.
Be careful.
You can't do this.
I know none of you are good people,
but can you act like humans?
The 2 women are not the biggest problem.
Do you know there's a
bio-soldier in the cargo hold?
He's here to capture the Twins,
and his subordinates are armed.
Do we have any chance
against them as just two people?
I can release the air in the container.
The bio-soldier can survive
for 30 minutes in a vacuum.
That's enough for him to kill you 3 times.
You must know him.
You definitely know him.
Then it will be solved.
I'll let him live
and he can
deal with those people.
Who gives you the right to decide
the life and death of others here?
This is my spacecraft.
You can't afford to be wrong again.
At least let that little girl live.
I'll choose
whoever can let me survive.
Lu Ming,
you can't be soft-hearted now.
Even if we don't take action,
they will end up killing each other.
Right now,
we need to find the person
who can help us survive.
- Drop the gun.
[Test results: Clones]
Don't shoot!
We need to figure out
what they've transported.
The spaceship is about to crash,
eject quickly!
There's only 1 escape pod.
Don't worry about me.
Let's go together.
I have to try.
Below lies the protective
shield of Sailor Valley.
If the spaceship crashes into it,
many people will die.
Have you made up your mind?
There are only 2
outcomes, success or failure.
Don't overthink it.
If
you were to descend from the sky
onto that doomed spaceship
and could save only 1 person,
among the remaining three
... a wounded soldier who could
survive with medical attention,
a commanding officer
with vital intelligence,
and a pilot who has saved many lives.
How would you choose?
It's very difficult, right?
Because any choice would be wrong.
I'm not a saint,
and I can't claim to be a good person.
Since any choice would be wrong,
I'll just choose someone I like.
This time,
I'm fighting for an equal
chance for everyone.
Ji Ya.
Equality?
What happened?
Someone is trying to kill us.
What should we do?
Let me check.
I'm fine.
Everyone, please calm
down and listen to us.
Lu Ming.
You go ahead.
We're trapped in the Star Abyss.
It will take 7 years
before we can break free.
What should we do?
You figure out a solution.
You are so useless!
I've told you that the ship would
run into trouble sooner or later.
Yeah, figure out a solution.
Let him finish talking.
Didn't you say
if I had abandoned the ship a bit later,
things might have been different?
This time, let's see
if it can be different.
It's all your fault.
In the past,
: all the passengers on the ships
trapped in the Star Abyss disappeared
because they killed each other to survive.
Now, on our ship,
there are also 2 killers
wanting to go down the same path.
But as long as everyone works
together, believes in each other,
and stops their plan,
we can definitely find
a way for everyone to survive.
As long as we release
the monster, kill the others,
and then lower the oxygen levels,
the two of us can survive.
Something is wrong.
Ji Ya,
quickly open the door.
Are there any animals on the ship?
They are not on the cargo list,
but this old guy
must be hiding something.
Come to me quickly.
Hurry!
Come.
Watch out.
Hurry up.
What are you waiting for?
Move quickly!
Zhanhui!
- Su Li!
- Zhanhui!
Save me!
Zhanhui!
Don't scare me, Zhanhui.
Where are you, Zhanhui?
Zhanhui.
Su Li.
Zhanhui!
Come out,
or else I'll shoot.
Walk over slowly.
Don't shoot!
I just want to survive.
Give me a reason not to kill you.
Because I have 4 hibernation pods.
You need me.
What is that?
Look.
It's Su Li.
Mom, what are you doing? Come back!
Mom!
- Mom!
- Come back!
Mom!
- Sit down.
- Mom.
Be quiet!
What's going on?
It's so scary.
Mom.
[Mrs. Star Seeker]
The Twins must be smuggling
genetically engineered monster.
Not only can it optically cloak,
but it can also
automatically repair wounds.
No matter what it is,
if it doesn't die, we will.
[Mrs. Star Seeker]
Du Xiao!
You fool, run!
She's already dead.
This is a trap.
Go! Another one is dead!
Go!
[Mrs. Star Seeker]
Go, Duo! Hurry!
Help!
Help me!
Calm down.
It wants to kill us all.
Let's get out of here first.
Cut off the head of the snake.
I'll go and find the Twins.
You stay here.
This monster is optically cloaked.
Once the torch is lit,
you'll be able to see it.
[Mrs. Star Seeker]
No more wasting time with them.
I'll remote control the monster directly.
Oh, right.
Don't kill that female
crew member just yet.
I still need her help
to modify the hibernation pods.
They'll soon know what a nightmare is.
Fujimoto, you bastard!
You bought these death-trap
tickets just to save money.
You're going to kill us all!
Zi.
I have a family to support,
and I have you to support.
Run.
What are you doing?
The monster's in here.
Why is it here?
I don't know.
Everyone else is in the cargo bay passage.
I'll take care of it.
You go deal with the bio-soldier.
I'll go deal with that bio-soldier.
Hey, keep the female crew
alive.
As long as she's alive,
correct?
It's coming.
Fire!
It's injured.
Take the others to the circulation chamber.
I'll stay here and kill it.
Xing Tian.
Originally, catching you requires evidence.
Now it's easy.
Wearing armor is cheating, is it?
Is it still easy now?
Run!
This is the secret to your immortality
as bio-soldiers.
Not only can I heal my wounds,
I can also...
How to kill that monster?
Tell me!
Go! Go!
Hurry!
The monster is catching up!
Grandma!
The door's broken. It won't lock.
Grandma.
Go!
We can't all die here.
Hurry up.
They can't die in vain.
Go!
Grandma!
Go. Hurry up.
To kill the monster,
you'll need the neurotoxin we've got.
Hand it over.
There's only one.
It's not here with me.
And.
Hurry up.
I can't hold on for long.
But I can still hold the door.
Without you,
those two girls won't make it out alive.
Leave now!
What is this?
This is military-grade nanite injection
that I extracted from myself.
No matter how heavily wounded you are,
as long as you're not
dead, it can heal you.
What about you?
What will you do if you get injured again?
Treat your injuries first.
If the monster doesn't die, we will.
You've got to survive for her sake.
This is the surveillance video
from back then.
With this, you can prove your innocence.
Let's go together.
I have to give it a try.
Below is the protective shield
of the Sailor Valley.
If the spaceship hits it,
many people will die.
Have you made up your mind?
There are only two possible outcomes,
success or failure.
What good is this to me now?
At least you can explain things clearly
to the girl.
Screw you!
If I die,
you have to let Ji Ya and Duo live.
Ji Ya went to the circulation chamber.
You go get her.
You won't make me go
empty-handed, will you?
A woman and two kids.
What a tough task.
Alright.
I've put all my bets on you guys.
Don't let me down.
For the bio-soldier,
we need to take him on together.
This neurotoxin can take down the monster
and it will definitely work on him as well.
[Mrs. Star Seeker cargo spacecraft,
circulation chamber]
Tingting.
Duo.
It's alright.
Everything is fine.
I'm here. Don't worry.
It's okay.
Someone is coming.
Get up.
You go first.
Hurry up.
Go! Be careful.
Come out.
Do you think I don't know
how big this place is?
Go!
Hurry up!
Tingting is injured.
She's bleeding.
Let's go. Take her away.
You go first.
Go. Go.
Go!
Be quick!
Hang in there.
Lu Ming will come to save us.
No one
can decide how I live
or how I die.
Leave them to me.
That monster is being controlled
by the Twins.
Once I take them down,
you'll be able to blow that monster up.
This...
I hope you won't need it.
Hey.
Stay alive.
You too.
As long as you survive,
you'll be free.
I'll see you in the nacelle.
Hurry up.
Duo!
Help!
Duo.
Warning.
Artificial gravity is off,
entering weightless state.
Warning.
Artificial gravity is on.
Artificial gravity is off,
entering weightless state.
Warning.
Artificial gravity is on.
If you weren't valuable,
I'd love to dismember you for free.
I may have lost,
but
you didn't win either.
Ji Ya!
Duo.
Uncle!
Let me go, you old bastard.
What are you looking at?
I, this old bastard,
have a daughter too.
This is a photo of my
daughter 30 years ago.
At that time,
We two talked about everything.
She trusted me the most.
But now,
I don't know where she is,
what kind of life she's living,
or what she looks like.
Don't you think it's cruel?
Cruel?
I think that's not nearly enough for you.
What did you say?
Get up.
Go.
I'm fine.
I lost the necklace,
and Ji Ya was taken away.
Only those who risked their lives
to rescue their comrades on the battlefield
are eligible to receive this medal.
Your parents gave this to you,
hoping that you would grow up
safe and sound.
Don't lose it again.
Let's go!
Come back!
There's a hatch over here.
A hatch.
Come on.
Let's go.
Duo, over there.
Let's go to the nacelle.
[Mrs. Star Seeker
cargo spacecraft, nacelle]
This is the airlock chamber.
Beyond that is the vacuum.
There's no way out.
I've activated the rescue signal.
Someone will definitely get you out later.
The hatch will open from the inside,
but you'll be safe.
What about you?
If you're injured,
it will save your life.
But you're already injured.
Take it. Don't lose it.
Hurry up.
I'll definitely block it.
You must survive, no matter what.
Duo.
I have to tell you something.
I got 80,000 people in Sailor Valley
and your parents killed.
I'm sorry.
Thank goodness you still remember
I can survive in the vacuum for 30 minutes.
I came here as soon as I saw the signal.
I thought you were lost.
Don't worry. She just needs some air.
She will wake up soon.
Move.
What's wrong?
She went into a coma due to a brain injury.
I have to reconnect with the monster
to wake her up.
What should we do?
The pilot and the bio-soldier are alive.
If you don't help me,
you are a dead man.
Fine.
What do you want?
This is a neurotoxin.
Inject it into the monster's body.
After sedating it,
we can reconnect with it.
Then I can wake her up.
My leg!
You had your chance,
and you wasted it.
Seems like I bet on the wrong person.
But luckily,
I have this.
Warning.
Patient's condition is critical.
What are you doing?
Warning.
Patient's condition is critical.
I have survived thus far
not by luck.
What are you doing?
The Captain just killed Twins.
Now,
he has the neurotoxin.
This is the only way to kill the monster.
There are only five of us left.
Lu Ming,
if you want those three to survive,
you have to kill the monster.
Otherwise,
everyone will die.
It's your choice.
[Mrs. Star Seeker]
So your kind can also die from bleeding.
You best behave yourself.
Don't waste the chance Lu Ming gave you.
Don't let me see you again.
It's your time to shine.
Reboot the AI system immediately.
Everything
will be over soon.
Come here!
I'm going to tear you apart!
If I had hung on a little longer last time,
those people wouldn't have died.
This time,
I won't give up.
Come on!
You will die.
Everyone will die.
Do you regret it?
I hope you won't need it.
System reboot completed,
starting automatic detection.
I already know your answer.
Do you want to know mine?
I'll let that wounded soldier take my place
and escape with the commander.
Then I will stay,
together with the pilot who has saved many,
to save more people.
If you get hurt,
it can save your life.
Hold onto it. Don't lose it.
He's dead.
He won't feel anything.
There are only
four people left on the ship.
Just accept it.
AI doesn't make mistakes.
Just let the kid do something for him.
You must believe in hope.
Let's go.
We will surely see him again.
It's your turn.
I wish you can hear their screams
every night from now on.
In this world,
it's easy to forget.
I don't want to live in such a world.
When you wake up,
the first thing you see will be good news.
I'll let that wounded soldier take my place
and escape with the commander.
Then I will stay,
together with the pilot who has saved many,
to save more people.
[Star Abyss]
Hi, Duo.
When you wake up,
I'll be seven years older,
but you're still seven. Isn't it fun?
There's nothing fun on this ship.
So you didn't miss anything.
Xing Tian.
You brat.
See? I planted them all.
I'm the only one left on the plane.
By lowering the air oxygen level,
I can live for seven years.
It's like I've been living
at high altitude with low oxygen level.
I'll get used to it soon.
Old man,
some of them found their way home,
some regained their freedom,
and some restored their hope.
But what about you?
I hope when you go to jail,
your daughter will visit you.
Ji Ya,
although
you thought I was dead at that time,
yet
I still heard it.
I'm very glad
to hear your answer.
The reason I kept going
is that I want to tell
you one day in person
that we made the right choice.
Duo,
I heard what you said as well.
Never
lose hope.
No matter what,
I will hold on,
because I promised you.
See you in the new world.