-You're late, Jacques.
-Sorry, Father.
Go fetch the wine.
Why don't
you go fetch the wine?
-Pardon?
-Er, nothing.
Let your spirit
come upon these gifts
to make them holy
so that they may become for us,
the body and blood of our Lord,
Jesus Christ.
Body of Christ.
Amen.
-The blood of Christ.
-Amen.
-Father.
-Yes?
-There's someone here.
-Where?
Who's there?
Whoever you are,
whatever you are here for,
you are in a house of God.
And He's watching you.
Get this under the other tire.
Sister Irene!
Sister Debra.
It's Sister Debra.
She's trouble.
Every day she's making trouble.
And now, she refused
to go to confession.
And you know why?
She did not think
she had anything to confess.
For that alone,
she should be confessing.
I will have a talk with her,
Reverend Mother.
Grazie, Sister.
Sister Debra?
Sister Irene.
This about confession?
You're going to give the Mother
a heart attack.
Well, then maybe
I'll have something to confess.
Your father
sent you here, right?
Yes. I was different.
Sending me away was easier than
trying to understand who I was.
What'd your mama
say about that?
I barely remember her.
But my father always said
I was just like her.
I don't think he meant it
as a compliment.
Well, my family's
from Mississippi,
but we ran into some trouble
down there.
When I was four, white folks,
they found where we were,
burned our house down.
After that,
my brothers joined the army.
My dad figured,
"My boys can serve country,
my daughter can serve God."
Never in my wildest dreams
did I think
I was gonna end up here.
Do I still have
to go to confession?
I think
you've confessed enough.
One by one,
the sisters
found themselves murdered.
Hanging from windows.
Throat slit open.
Acts of suicide.
Sometimes worse.
They learned
that beneath their remote abbey
was a terrible secret.
A gateway to hell.
And from this gateway,
a demon had escaped.
Now, we know that a demon
can take any form,
but they choose their form
to challenge your faith
and to weaken your spirits.
Now, for the nuns
of Saint Carta,
this demon
chose the most ungodly,
the most blasphemous form.
It chose
to look like one of them.
And then what happened?
Well, the Vatican sent in
a pair of demon hunters.
A priest and a nun.
-And how did they stop it?
-Great question.
They used an ancient relic,
a vial which contained
the blood of Jesus Christ.
So, they returned as heroes,
kissed the Pope's ring.
Priest was made a bishop.
What happened to the nun?
Well, no one really knows.
They say the experience
was too much for her.
Some say that she went mad.
The Vatican had to lock her up
in an asylum.
Gotcha! Quick!
Why does Madame
have so much wine?
This used
to be a monastery.
The monks were all fat drunks.
Everyone downstairs, please.
It's nearly eight o'clock.
Come on, now.
I got 'em.
Took you long enough.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners now
and at the hour
of our--
Jesus Christ!
Bloody hell!
Kate.
-Good morning.
-Hard at work already?
Always.
Good morning, Maurice.
Captain!
Come on now, Sophie.
-Hi, Maurice.
-Morning.
-Morning, Maurice.
-Ladies.
Hey, Maurice, do you wanna play
baseball with us today?
Course, I do. You know what?
I'll teach you how
to throw a knuckleball.
-Maurice. Maurice.
-Oh. Captain Sophie.
Lieutenant.
I made this for you.
It's a friendship bracelet.
Each bead represents
a different quality
of a good friend.
Wow. It's beautiful, Sophie.
Thank you.
Woo-hoo! Woo! Woo!
Are you proposing to
your boyfriend, little Sophie?
-Give it back.
-You can't make me.
You're not a teacher.
You're the servant.
Even the servant knows
you should treat everyone
with kindness and respect.
-Girls.
-Oui, Madame.
What do you think you're doing?
This is not a playground!
-Get to class!
-Oui, Madame.
-And you, Maurice.
-Mm?
There was a cockroach
in my quarters again.
Ah, that's unfortunate.
It's an infestation.
It's disgusting.
I'll tend to it right away.
-You'd better.
-I promise.
Captain! Captain! Wait.
How did you do that?
Skills I learned
from another life.
How do I look?
Come on, get to class. Come on.
Bonjour. Delivery.
Monsieur?
Are you okay?
Sister.
You have a visitor.
Reverend Mother?
Maurice?
Save me, Sister.
Irene! It's okay. It's okay.
You're fine. You're fine.
Your nose.
Sister Irene.
You have a visitor.
Your Eminence.
There has been an incident.
A series of them.
Szeleste, a small village
in Hungary.
A 90-year-old nun shot herself
on the steps of her church.
Graz, Austria.
A priest cut his throat open
with a rosary
during Christmas mass.
Edolo, Italy.
A novitiate threw herself
out a window.
Sound familiar?
Just a month ago,
in Tarascon, France,
another priest,
murdered inside his church.
Immolated.
Notice a pattern?
It's moving west across Europe.
But its origins point
to Romania.
-It can't be.
-The demon lives.
Have you spoken
with Father Burke?
Father Burke is dead.
-How?
-Cholera.
You are
the only person alive
who has dealt
with something like this.
The Church would like
you to investigate.
Find out what it wants
and where it's going next.
No.
I'm sorry?
I said, "No."
-I can't do it.
-Can't, or won't?
You don't know what happened
at Saint Carta.
I was lucky
to make it out alive.
You're right. I don't know
what you faced back there.
But in that abbey, Sister,
you performed a miracle.
The Church needs another.
-Here you are.
-Sister?
Was afraid I almost hopped
on the wrong train.
What are you doing here?
Looking after you.
-Someone's gotta.
-Sister, you could be expelled.
Why are you here?
My mama.
She died in the fire.
She was my church.
I want to believe in miracles.
But when I see
the priest stand up
and say he turned the wine
into the blood of Christ,
I mean,
it's kind of hard to believe.
It's an act of faith.
He just says a bunch
of words to wine.
The wine becomes the blood
of Christ because we believe.
The most extraordinary
parts of our faith
are only real
because we believe in them.
I guess so.
You're not ready.
Why?
An entire convent of nuns died
facing this thing.
Women who dedicated
their lives to their faith.
Then sacrificed their lives
because they believed
in something greater.
You need me.
I just hope you can find
your faith when the time comes.
"Why, get you gone.
Who is't that hinders you?"
"A foolish heart
that I leave here behind."
"What, with Lysander?"
"With Demetrius."
"Be not afraid. She shall not
harm thee, Helena."
"No, sir, she shall not,
though you take her part."
"O, when she is angry,
she is keen and shrewd.
She was a vixen
when she went to school.
And though she be but little,
she is fierce."
"Little again!
Nothing but low and little!
Why will you suffer her--"
Uh, let's take a break.
Fifteen minutes.
I was just getting
into character.
Yeah,
an awful character.
All right, girls.
Slowly, now.
Girls.
Sweetheart,
take these to the office.
You're the best.
I heard there was
a faulty cabinet in the area?
The latch won't open.
-May I?
-Oh, please.
Yeah. It's stuck.
Can you just, please,
put a little pressure here?
Yeah. Just here.
All right. Thanks.
Looks like we share
the latest fashion.
I guess we do.
Okay.
Oh!
Voila!
Thanks a many.
All right.
Okay.
She's a great kid.
You must be proud.
I am.
Need some help?
No, I'm okay.
Relax, Sophie.
We're not going to do anything.
Cross my heart.
That was pretty mean
of us earlier.
I was a bitch.
It's okay.
What are you doing after this?
We have to go back to class.
Not for another ten minutes.
Do you want to have some fun?
Madame says
the chapel is off limits.
I know.
-What are we doing here?
-Playing a game.
It's called "Defy the Devil."
I don't see any devil.
The devil is always here.
You're just not looking
carefully enough.
It depends on where you stand
and when you look.
At the right time of day...
the sun hits the glass
at just the right angle.
And if you're watching
carefully,
he looks right at you.
The rumor is, if you look away,
the devil will appear in
the form of a monstrous goat.
See?
He's watching you.
Whatever you do,
whatever you hear,
don't look away.
Let me out!
Sophie? What's going on?
What happened?
Hey, hey. It's okay.
Of course, her boyfriend comes
to her rescue.
Do you think it's funny?
Do you?
It's okay. It's over.
What happened in there?
You can tell me.
-Nothing.
-Sophie?
Why aren't you in class?
Oh, this isn't her fault.
The older girls
were playing some--
I'm sorry, Mom.
Excuse us.
Sure.
Are you all right?
Sister Astrid?
Welcome to Tarascon.
Please come in.
We still have mass,
but no one comes.
People believe
it was the devil.
They say our church is cursed,
that God has abandoned us.
This is where we found him.
Sister?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Can we see
Father Noiret's room, please?
Of course.
Creepy.
Saint Lucy.
Patron Saint of the blind.
She was murdered by pagans.
They lit her on fire,
but she wouldn't burn.
Before killing her,
they gouged out her eyes.
Found them. Please.
There was a boy that night?
A witness?
Yes. Jacques.
He saw everything.
Where can we find him?
His mother doesn't want him
talking about it.
But you might find him
playing football in town.
Was there anyone else
in the church?
We had a handyman.
He left the day
after it happened.
Do you know where he went?
I don't know.
But he was a world traveler.
He came from Romania.
That is where he got
his nickname.
They used to call him...
-"Frenchie."
-Frenchie.
Where are you
headed next?
Well, I have enough money
to get me to Hungary,
and from there,
the world is my oyster.
At least Hungary is.
-You saved my life.
-That? That was nothing.
No, you've just fell into a...
what do you call it? Um...
a life debt.
It's very simple.
You and I will be bound
together for all eternity.
I almost forgot.
It's nothing, just a thank you.
Tomato seeds. Thank you.
You said you wanted a farm
some day.
You have to start somewhere.
I'll miss you, Irene.
Irene?
Who is this Frenchie guy?
His name is Maurice.
Back at Saint Carta,
he was our guide.
When I faced the demon,
he came back for me.
He saved my life.
That's when
it happened.
It's how the demon escaped.
That's how it's moving,
doing these things.
So, he's... possessed.
Maurice.
Hi. Hello again.
I realized
I never said thank you.
-Sophie told me what you did.
-Oh. No.
Those girls
are little monsters.
They're not all bad. Just some.
Look... the chapel, why does
Madame keep it locked up?
Uh, it's dangerous.
Her son was killed inside
during the bombings.
Cedric. He was an altar boy.
I didn't know she had a son.
She doesn't talk about it.
Madame is a hard woman,
but she's been very good to us.
Ah. I should get back
to the children.
Sure, yes. And I should
get back to my work.
Caught you!
What were you doing?
-Nothing.
-You were spying.
-Maybe.
-Maybe?
Maybe, probably,
absolutely definitely.
-What were you talking about?
-Nothing.
It was something.
He was making you laugh.
That is none of your business.
Now, let's go. No more spying.
Hey!
Sophie?
Mom?
Come on now, girls. Quick.
Quickly.
Vite! Vite!
Sophie!
Where did you run off to?
-I've been looking for you.
-Mom?
Quick.
What's next?
Is this just a big dead end?
No. There's something here.
What? You...
You sense something?
Something like that.
My Sisters.
I have
a reservation,
under Irene Palmer.
Palmer?
Hm. I'm afraid I can't find it.
What? That's not possible.
I have a reservation.
Madam, it's not here.
Let me just take care of it.
Um, sir, can we please speak
to a manager?
-Certainly, madam.
-Thank you.
Vite! Vite!
Jacques?
You're the boy.
Don't be scared.
My name's Irene.
The Church sent me to help.
I know you were there
that night.
You saw it.
That night,
did you have a rosary?
No. It was Father Noiret's.
-What?
-I took it.
I'm sorry, I was scared.
Jacques! Wait!
Jacques?
Irene?
Irene!
Irene! Irene!
Irene, wake up!
Oh, my God. Wake up.
-We need a doctor.
-Help! Help!
Somebody help! I need a doctor!
Irene.
Somebody help!
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed are thou among women--
Maurice?
Maurice.
Madame Laurent?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
-I don't know.
-Go back to your room.
Yes.
-I'm sorry.
-It's fine.
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
Oh, my god!
Mama!
Who is in here?
Cedric?
Cedric.
Stop!
There she is,
back from the dead.
-Thank you, Doctor.
-You're welcome, Sister.
What happened last night?
We're close.
I had a vision.
I saw what the demon wants.
It's powerful.
Some coveted prize,
some ancient relic.
It's been using Maurice
to get it.
Driving him.
Draining him.
Keeping him alive
just to find this thing.
It's going to kill him
when it's done.
The altar boy.
I-I forgot to tell you,
I found him.
-What?
-Well, he found me.
He came by when you were out.
He gave me this.
Father Noiret's rosary.
The symbol, it...
it seems so familiar,
but I can't place it.
I can. The photos.
I think I saw that
on one of the victims.
Look.
It's a connection.
If we find out what this means,
we might be able to find out
where it's headed.
How are we gonna do that?
I have a friend
in the Catholic archives.
I can't find Sophie.
Have you seen her?
No, I...
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't worry. She can't be far.
I'll find her, all right?
Sophie!
Sophie.
Hey.
This is quite
a spot you've got.
May I join you?
What for?
Just to talk.
Madame never went
into the chapel.
I don't know why
she went in there last night.
There's something wrong
with this school.
There's something
that doesn't feel right.
It's like
there's something here...
that's not meant to be.
Sophie?
What happened?
Did you see something?
Anything?
N-no.
It's just a feeling.
Hey, it's okay to be scared.
I'm scared, too.
There's been times in my life
where fear has
made me do things
I never thought possible.
You kept my bracelet.
Yeah, well, I tried to sell it.
No one would buy it.
Come on,
we should head back down.
Your mother is worried, okay?
She's always worried.
Don't know why.
Maybe she loves you?
Come on. I just hope
she doesn't ground you.
-Excuse us.
-I'm so sorry. God bless you.
Where did
you find it?
Tarascon.
-This belonged to the priest?
-Yes, how did you know?
I've been speaking
to the Vatican.
They tell me the demon
of Saint Carta has returned.
It's a family crest.
Whose family?
Saint Lucy of Syracuse.
These victims
must be her descendants.
Saint Lucy?
I think I know what it wants.
What?
The eyes.
The eyes? W-What eyes?
When Lucy was murdered
by pagans, her family escaped.
They were hunted.
Scattered across the globe.
All this time, they've been
protecting a secret.
A holy relic.
The eyes of Saint Lucy.
So, the demon
is after a... pair of eyes?
-Why would it want that?
-It's a demon.
I'm just a glorified librarian,
I couldn't begin to guess.
But, if we're
sharing theories...
you might like to consider that
this demon was once an angel.
Rejected by God.
Stripped of his holy power
that God so casually
gave to His saints.
It wants that power back.
Demons are infinite.
It was there with Saint Lucy
and it's been hunting
the bloodline ever since.
This relic is an item
of great power.
In the hands of a demon,
it would be unthinkable.
But in your hands,
it could be a weapon.
Just as you used the blood
of Christ at Saint Carta.
This is the way you do it.
This is the way you send
that thing back to hell.
We just don't know where it is.
I might.
We've been
cataloguing these relics,
chasing down rumors and so on,
and if my memory
serves me correct,
this one found its way
to a monk.
Jean-Paul Redar.
According to letters
that he wrote to the Vatican,
he buried the eyes
somewhere within his monastery.
Saint Mary's, Aix-en-Provence.
-It's about an hour from here.
-Is it still a monastery?
No, it was sold to a winery
and now...
it's a boarding school.
Irene, wait. Whatever happens
tonight, don't hesitate.
We don't really know
what this relic can do.
The same goes for the demon.
It will take any form,
and it will choose its form
to prey on your fears,
and the fears
of those around you.
You must be prepared
to stop it, at all costs.
-What are you making?
-It's called feijoada.
-It's a Portuguese stew.
-What's in it?
Slugs.
And snails.
I lied to you.
About what?
I said I didn't remember
my mother.
But I do.
I remember everything
about her.
She was deeply religious.
She said that God
spoke directly to her,
that He showed her things.
Visions.
Like me.
My father didn't believe her.
He said she was insane.
Heretical.
What happened to her?
My father brought her
to a doctor.
Then they came back
and took her away.
I will always be with you.
I never saw her again.
Wow!
You always turn, make me turn.
My lady.
Mom, it's your turn.
No, I shouldn't.
Please?
All right.
Are you all right?
Yeah. It's... It's nothing.
-Okay.
-It's nothing.
Maurice!
There's
something under your skin.
Oh, no.
Come on! Come on!
We've gotta go! Come on!
This way! This way! Come on!
God! Sister.
Maurice!
It's back. It's here.
-Maurice, I need you to--
-Kate, this is Irene.
-No, Maurice, no, you need to--
-She's my friend.
-We've got to go.
-Get away from them!
What?
We need to go, now!
-It's you.
-What?
It's inside of you.
No.
-No.
-It's my fault.
Because you came back for me,
that's when it happened.
Oh, god! No!
-Maurice, what's happening?
-We can stop it.
Hello, Sister.
Maurice?
Irene, are you okay?
Stop him.
Out, demon!
In the name of God
and the Holy Spirit,
I command you, leave this man!
Let him be!
You think that'll hold him?
Let's work quick.
-Are you two okay?
-What was that?
-What's wrong with him?
-He's... sick.
We're going to help him,
but we need your help.
He was headed
in that direction.
What's in there?
That's the chapel.
What are you
looking for?
It's an ancient relic
left here by a monk
named Jean-Paul Redar.
-Ring any bells?
-I'm just a teacher.
No one's even allowed in here.
Redar would have left some way
for the descendants to find it.
What are you looking at?
The goat.
It's the devil.
It's just a game the kids play.
What kind of game?
The sun shines
through the window,
and it makes the goat's eyes
glow red.
It's the devil. It watches you.
Just there.
Anything?
No, not yet.
You're a little high.
Can you go lower?
Wait. Wait, wait!
Go back up slowly.
Stop!
That's it.
We got it.
We got it!
Sophie?
Celeste,
did you hear that?
There's someone upstairs.
Go take a look.
Wait.
Wait!
The eyes of Saint Lucy.
-Hi.
-Who are you?
It's okay,
I'm a friend of Kate's.
I think
there's someone upstairs.
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Who's that?
What is that thing?
It's the devil.
The girls!
Mom! Mom!
What's she doing?
It's Madame Laurent.
What?
She's standing in her room.
No! No!
Sophie?
Sophie, it's me, Maurice.
Don't be afraid.
I'm your friend.
Sophie! Sophie!
Sophie.
I would never hurt you.
Remember, Captain?
The eyes.
Sophie!
-Sophie!
-Irene!
Are you okay?
I have it.
Demon!
Irene!
Be gone!
You're hurting him!
Sister, please.
It's killing me.
No!
Where's Sophie?
Stay close.
Up, up!
Go, go!
The doors! The doors!
Save me, oh God, by thy name.
No!
Get that plank!
Get back in the chapel!
Simone, come with me.
Stay behind me.
No!
I will always
be with you.
Look at me.
Are you okay?
-Yes.
-That was a miracle.
The wine.
Sophie! Sophie!
-Irene!
-No. No, Maurice, no!
No!
Maurice, no! No!
Help me!
Stop!
Sister.
Pray with me.
This is the cup
of my blood.
When Lucy was murdered,
her family escaped.
They were hunted,
scattered across the globe.
The blood of the new
and everlasting covenant.
That will be shed for you
and for all
so that your sins
may be forgiven.
I said
I didn't remember my mother,
but I do.
Saint Lucy,
Patron Saint of the blind.
They lit her on fire,
but she wouldn't burn.
Do this in memory of me.
These victims
must be her descendants.
You have my eyes.
Amen.
Sister...
you saved me.
Maurice.
I'm sorry.
-I'm so sorry.
-It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Warren?
It's Father Gordon.
He says it's an emergency.
Yes, Father.
How can we help?